{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,u,r,e. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: r,e,y,m,o,u. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,g,t,h. Absents letters: i,m,o,y,r,e,u. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,g,t,h. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,n,b,m,o,u. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: m,o,r. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: m,o,r,y,t,h. ", "response": "sices", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: y,r,h,m,o,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: r,y,h,m,o,t,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: m,a,r. ", "response": "seism", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,r,m,o,a,u,d. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,r,z,m,o,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,r,y,z,b,m,o,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,s. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,o,e. Absents letters: l,s,c. ", "response": "preed", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e,p,d. Absents letters: l,s,c. ", "response": "pored", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e,p,d. Absents letters: m,s,t,l,c,u. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,r,e,c,u. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o. Absents letters: m,s,r,e,c,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,p,o. Absents letters: r,e,c,m,s,u,d. ", "response": "loppo", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,l,p. Absents letters: r,e,y,c,m,s,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: m,g. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: i,m,s,n,g,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: i,m,s,g,n,d. ", "response": "lexis", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: i,n,c,m,s,o,g,d. ", "response": "leaze", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: w. Absents letters: i,k,h,l. ", "response": "wax", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: w,e,n. Absents letters: i,k,s,t,l,h. ", "response": "enew", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: w,e,n. Absents letters: i,y,h,k,s,t,l. ", "response": "wax", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n,a,w,d. Absents letters: i,y,r,h,k,s,t,l. ", "response": "warre", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: a,b,g,n. ", "response": "bise", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: a,g,n,t,b. ", "response": "prees", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: n,b,g,l,t,a,u. ", "response": "sares", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: n,b,f,g,l,t,a,u. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: y,a,r,t. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,y,k,s,v,t,a. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,c,e. Absents letters: y,r,k,s,v,t,a. ", "response": "loic", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,c,e. Absents letters: r,y,n,k,s,v,t,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,s,r,t. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: i,m,s,r,y,t. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,m,s,g,t. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,o,a,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,m,s,g,t. ", "response": "opa", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,a,h. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: m,l,c,a,h,u. ", "response": "enact", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,t. Absents letters: i,c,h,m,s,l,a,u. ", "response": "tosh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,t. Absents letters: i,c,h,b,m,s,l,a,u. ", "response": "tosh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c. Absents letters: s,a,u,t. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,h,e. Absents letters: s,t,a,u. ", "response": "chefs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,c,h,e. Absents letters: s,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,c,h,e. Absents letters: b,s,o,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "cush", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,r,g,t,a. ", "response": "niger", "reward": -6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,f,r,g,t,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,e. Absents letters: i,r,y,a,o,g,t,f. ", "response": "hules", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,u. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,f,o,v,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "cuzes", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n. Absents letters: e,t. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,w,n. Absents letters: i,e,t,f. ", "response": "wwn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,n,w. Absents letters: i,y,e,t,p,f. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,w,s,o,g. Absents letters: i,a,y,e,t,p,f. ", "response": "gog", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: m,e,t. ", "response": "gog", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,s. Absents letters: m,e,t,l,d. ", "response": "abode", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,n,a. Absents letters: m,e,t,l,u,d. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,n,a. Absents letters: m,e,t,l,u,d. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t. Absents letters: s,a,z. ", "response": "thine", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t. Absents letters: s,o,n,z,a. ", "response": "thymi", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t. Absents letters: k,s,o,n,z,e,a. ", "response": "thymi", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,f,t. Absents letters: e,z,n,w,k,s,o,a. ", "response": "thil", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,a. Absents letters: i,h,t. ", "response": "coral", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,c. Absents letters: i,s,t,h,w. ", "response": "cabal", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,h,w,s,t. ", "response": "cauri", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,c. Absents letters: i,q,r,e,h,w,s,t,u. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: b,r,g. ", "response": "mares", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,l,a. Absents letters: i,r,g,b. ", "response": "loess", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,l,a. Absents letters: i,r,n,b,g,p,u. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,l,a. Absents letters: i,r,n,b,g,p,u. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,b,c. ", "response": "plo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,m,n,b,c,d. ", "response": "gales", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,y,n,c,b,m,u,d. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,a. Absents letters: i,y,n,z,b,c,m,u,d. ", "response": "pests", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: y,n,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e. Absents letters: i,t,y,n,p,c,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,s. Absents letters: i,y,n,c,t,l,p,d. ", "response": "sores", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,s. Absents letters: i,y,n,c,t,l,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "sores", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u. Absents letters: t,s,g. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u. Absents letters: k,s,n,g,t,a. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,r,u. Absents letters: k,s,g,n,t,a,h. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e,l,u. Absents letters: n,h,k,s,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: p,y,u,t. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: y,r,t,n,p,u. ", "response": "dices", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,l. Absents letters: r,y,n,b,s,t,p,u. ", "response": "bile", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,l. Absents letters: y,r,n,b,m,s,t,p,a,u. ", "response": "bile", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,r,y,w,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: y,r,w,o,d. ", "response": "gals", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,f. Absents letters: o,r,y,t,n,w,u,d. ", "response": "fests", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,f. Absents letters: y,r,n,w,o,t,u,d. ", "response": "fices", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: s,a. ", "response": "dyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: k,s,r,y,b,a. ", "response": "ensky", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n,t,c. Absents letters: k,s,a,y,r,e,b. ", "response": "citer", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t,c,n. Absents letters: y,r,e,b,k,s,o,l,p,a. ", "response": "tic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,h,y,g. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: y,n,c,h,s,g,l,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: y,n,c,h,s,o,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e. Absents letters: y,n,c,h,s,o,g,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: k,o,b. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: n,b,k,o,g,u,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: e,n,b,k,o,g,u,d. ", "response": "stabs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: i,e,n,b,k,o,g,u,d. ", "response": "thymi", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,d,y,n. ", "response": "fiche", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,y,x,n,s,l,a,d. ", "response": "fow", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,e. Absents letters: i,y,x,n,w,s,o,l,a,d. ", "response": "reiki", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,e. Absents letters: i,y,x,n,w,m,s,o,l,a,d. ", "response": "tik", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,c. Absents letters: k,r,n. ", "response": "cork", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,c,e. Absents letters: k,s,r,n,a,w,d. ", "response": "boce", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,l,c. Absents letters: r,y,n,w,k,s,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,l,c. Absents letters: y,r,n,w,k,s,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: o,q,u,e. ", "response": "brans", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: q,e,h,k,m,o,u. ", "response": "tifts", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,t. Absents letters: q,e,h,k,m,o,u. ", "response": "styt", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,t. Absents letters: i,q,e,h,k,m,o,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "tpy", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: l,m,s,d. ", "response": "fiche", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: r,e,m,s,l,p,d. ", "response": "bling", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,y,t. Absents letters: r,e,m,s,o,l,p,d. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,y,t. Absents letters: r,e,w,m,s,o,g,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: s,a,h. ", "response": "bing", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: r,c,h,m,s,a. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: r,x,e,c,h,m,s,a. ", "response": "quino", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,n. Absents letters: x,r,e,c,h,k,m,s,a. ", "response": "loing", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,z,y,d. ", "response": "nuts", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: i,y,z,m,s,o,p,d. ", "response": "fyt", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,t. Absents letters: i,y,z,m,s,o,p,d. ", "response": "biter", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,t. Absents letters: i,y,z,b,m,s,o,p,d. ", "response": "relet", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,o,r,e,t. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: m,o,s,r,e,t. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u,n. Absents letters: m,o,s,r,e,t,l. ", "response": "gunk", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,u,n. Absents letters: r,e,x,c,m,o,s,t,l. ", "response": "vinal", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,p,s,y. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: i,s,y,l,p,b,u. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,d. Absents letters: i,y,n,b,k,s,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "borg", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,g,r,d. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,b,k,s,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "dorm", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,x,r,e,f. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,x,e,n,c,h,o,f. ", "response": "kus", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: q,x,r,e,n,c,h,o,f,u. ", "response": "titch", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: q,r,x,e,n,c,h,o,s,f,u,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,o,v,e,a. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: e,w,f,m,o,v,s,a. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: e,w,k,m,o,v,s,a,f. ", "response": "tween", "reward": -6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,r. Absents letters: i,e,w,k,m,o,v,s,f,t,a. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: s,b. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,c,a. Absents letters: k,s,b. ", "response": "recit", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,c,a. Absents letters: k,i,s,f,t,b. ", "response": "recit", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,c,a. Absents letters: i,k,s,f,t,b. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: i,f,n. ", "response": "pyre", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: i,n,b,s,a,f,u. ", "response": "gyved", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,y. Absents letters: i,r,n,b,s,a,f,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,y. Absents letters: i,r,n,b,c,f,m,s,o,a,u. ", "response": "pygal", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: c,u,e,d. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,e,n,c,b,g,u,d. ", "response": "stul", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,h. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,b,c,g,t,u,d. ", "response": "loath", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,h. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,r,b,c,g,t,u,d. ", "response": "shal", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: s,n,t. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: s,g,n,t,b. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: s,g,a,n,t,b. ", "response": "horny", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: i,n,b,s,g,t,a. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: f,a. Absents letters: s,b. ", "response": "festa", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,f. Absents letters: s,n,l,b,u. ", "response": "taf", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: f,a. Absents letters: r,y,n,b,s,o,l,u,d. ", "response": "fiz", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,f,t. Absents letters: y,r,n,b,w,s,o,l,u,d. ", "response": "fath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: b,e,n. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: e,n,b,d. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,o. Absents letters: a,e,n,b,u,d. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,p. Absents letters: e,n,b,c,h,a,u,d. ", "response": "pso", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o. Absents letters: u,e,n. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o. Absents letters: i,e,n,z,h,g,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o. Absents letters: i,r,e,z,n,h,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,s. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,z,h,g,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,s,t,p,a. ", "response": "bum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n. Absents letters: m,s,g,y,t,p,a. ", "response": "enew", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,e,n. Absents letters: y,m,s,t,o,g,p,a,u. ", "response": "ratch", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,e,n. Absents letters: y,h,m,s,o,g,v,t,p,a,u. ", "response": "cline", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,v,t. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,v,t,p. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,a. Absents letters: i,v,r,t,l,p. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,a. Absents letters: i,r,c,v,t,l,p. ", "response": "shae", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,t,s,n. ", "response": "fad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: i,s,n,t,c. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,y,l,a. Absents letters: i,k,s,n,t,c. ", "response": "bery", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,r,e,l,a. Absents letters: i,n,c,k,s,v,t,u. ", "response": "bler", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: s,f,e,d. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: r,e,n,c,s,f,u,d. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,y,c,s,t,f,u,d. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,v. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,n,c,s,t,f,u,d. ", "response": "valet", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: p,o,c,s. ", "response": "nal", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: r,e,c,m,o,s,t,p. ", "response": "jugal", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: r,e,c,h,m,o,s,t,p,u. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,h,m,o,s,t,p,u. ", "response": "galvo", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: a,b,e,t. ", "response": "rogu", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: r,e,b,k,f,s,t,a. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: r,e,b,k,s,a,t,f,d. ", "response": "boing", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: i,r,e,b,k,f,s,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,e,n. Absents letters: o,s. ", "response": "enact", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n,p,u. Absents letters: o,s,z,f. ", "response": "enep", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,n,p,u. Absents letters: i,o,s,z,l,c,f. ", "response": "reng", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,n,p,u. Absents letters: i,z,c,o,s,t,l,f. ", "response": "bab", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: h,n. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: g,z,n,h,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: m,o,g,n,z,l,h,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,a. Absents letters: z,n,h,m,o,v,g,l,p,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,g,y,n,p. ", "response": "wuss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: m,o,g,s,y,n,p,b. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,l,a. Absents letters: y,n,b,m,o,s,g,p. ", "response": "albe", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,e. Absents letters: y,n,b,m,o,s,g,p. ", "response": "alate", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t. Absents letters: p,s,e. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,h,t. Absents letters: k,s,r,e,p. ", "response": "throb", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,h,t. Absents letters: r,e,k,s,l,p,a. ", "response": "thigh", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,f,h,t. Absents letters: r,e,k,s,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "thift", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,z. Absents letters: l,a. ", "response": "shiz", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,z. Absents letters: v,g,l,a. ", "response": "seaze", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,z. Absents letters: i,r,m,v,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "zex", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,z. Absents letters: i,r,m,o,v,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "zex", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: k,a,y,l,f. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,y,z,k,f,l,a,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,w. Absents letters: i,y,z,k,a,s,l,f,d. ", "response": "warst", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,w. Absents letters: i,y,e,z,k,f,s,l,a,d. ", "response": "wong", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e. Absents letters: x,d. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,s. Absents letters: x,l,a,w,d. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,e. Absents letters: x,g,l,a,w,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,e,p. Absents letters: f,x,g,l,a,w,d. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: m,b,g. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: f,m,a,x,g,b. ", "response": "sext", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e. Absents letters: x,b,m,a,g,l,p,f. ", "response": "seifs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e. Absents letters: x,b,f,m,v,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "sices", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: s,a,u,e. ", "response": "roosa", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: y,e,s,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "roopy", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: y,e,n,s,o,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "roopy", "reward": -6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: y,e,n,s,o,g,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: a,b,r. ", "response": "stol", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: a,o,r,b,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,t. Absents letters: o,a,v,r,e,n,b,d. ", "response": "thymi", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,t. Absents letters: r,e,n,b,w,o,v,a,d. ", "response": "tifts", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: o,c,t. ", "response": "nal", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,o,t,c,u. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,r,c,o,g,t,f,u. ", "response": "bax", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,r,c,o,g,t,f,u. ", "response": "sne", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: i,c. ", "response": "shog", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: i,a,r,y,g,c. ", "response": "shogs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,b,k,g,a,u. ", "response": "shogs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,h. Absents letters: i,y,r,b,c,k,g,p,a,u. ", "response": "shoh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: p,c,e. ", "response": "boors", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: e,t,n,p,c. ", "response": "golds", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: r,e,n,y,c,t,l,p. ", "response": "boors", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,g. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,n,c,t,l,p. ", "response": "gesso", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: k,s,b. ", "response": "tared", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,a. Absents letters: k,s,g,b. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e,t. Absents letters: n,b,k,s,o,g. ", "response": "tare", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,t,a. Absents letters: i,n,b,k,s,o,g,p,d. ", "response": "maron", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: y,u,d. ", "response": "roopy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,r. Absents letters: s,y,e,g,w,u,d. ", "response": "arcos", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,t,a. Absents letters: y,e,b,w,s,g,u,d. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,t,a. Absents letters: y,e,b,h,w,s,g,u,d. ", "response": "tort", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: k,d,a,n. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: k,i,r,n,a,d. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,k,a,d. ", "response": "salet", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,b,k,m,a,u,d. ", "response": "sling", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,d. Absents letters: r. ", "response": "dj", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,d. Absents letters: l,f,r,t. ", "response": "dices", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,d. Absents letters: r,m,o,t,l,f. ", "response": "dikes", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,d. Absents letters: r,b,m,o,a,s,t,l,f. ", "response": "dj", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,y,e,t,w. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: y,e,w,s,t,p,a. ", "response": "gry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: i,y,e,w,s,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "roopy", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: i,y,e,w,m,s,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "rogu", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: s,e,g. ", "response": "boong", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,r. Absents letters: s,e,g,c. ", "response": "lox", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,r,a. Absents letters: s,e,g,c,d. ", "response": "limax", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,r,a. Absents letters: x,e,c,s,g,t,d. ", "response": "limax", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n. Absents letters: p,o,d. ", "response": "bings", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n. Absents letters: o,r,t,p,d. ", "response": "enna", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n. Absents letters: o,g,r,t,p,d. ", "response": "nails", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e,n. Absents letters: r,y,h,o,t,g,p,d. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: m,e,n. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: m,r,e,n,y. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,n,m,t,f,u. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,r,m,t,f,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: f,r,e,t. ", "response": "wad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,r,e,t,f. ", "response": "alapa", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,a. Absents letters: i,k,r,e,t,f. ", "response": "pases", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,k,o,g,t,f,d. ", "response": "pases", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: j,e,d. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,a. Absents letters: r,e,n,j,d. ", "response": "pinas", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,p,a. Absents letters: r,e,n,j,c,d. ", "response": "lois", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,l,p,a. Absents letters: g,r,e,n,j,c,u,d. ", "response": "spial", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n. Absents letters: s,t. ", "response": "pine", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n. Absents letters: i,s,t,w. ", "response": "ennog", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e,n. Absents letters: i,s,g,t,a,w,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e,n. Absents letters: i,w,s,v,g,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: w,a,y,n. ", "response": "fow", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,d. Absents letters: y,e,n,l,a,w. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,d. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,w,l,a. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,d. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,c,w,l,p,a. ", "response": "modus", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,e,n,t,f. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,a,g,e,n,t,f. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,f,g,t,a. ", "response": "boing", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y,u. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,a,g,l,t,f. ", "response": "boomy", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,i. Absents letters: a,n. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,l. Absents letters: a,r,n. ", "response": "slily", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,l. Absents letters: r,n,p,a,w. ", "response": "slily", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,l. Absents letters: o,t,r,n,p,b,a,w. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: m,s,a. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: m,s,o,g,a,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: c,h,k,m,s,o,g,a,d. ", "response": "quine", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,n. Absents letters: c,h,b,k,m,s,o,g,l,a,d. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o. Absents letters: l,b,e. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o. Absents letters: s,a,e,l,c,b. ", "response": "moyle", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,r. Absents letters: i,e,b,c,s,l,a. ", "response": "coral", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,r. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,b,c,s,v,l,a. ", "response": "moor", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: g,r,n,a,w. ", "response": "titch", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,y,n,b,w,f,g,a. ", "response": "bum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: y,r,n,e,b,w,a,s,g,t,f. ", "response": "boomy", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: r,y,e,n,b,w,f,m,s,g,t,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: a,t. ", "response": "prees", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: m,o,e,t,a,d. ", "response": "kro", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,u. Absents letters: m,o,e,t,n,a,d. ", "response": "gri", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,c,u. Absents letters: e,n,m,o,t,a,d. ", "response": "girs", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: k,d,y,g. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: k,s,y,n,g,w,d. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,y,n,w,k,s,g,t,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,y,n,j,w,k,s,o,g,t,d. ", "response": "leaze", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,s,e,n,w. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,e,n,w,s,l,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y. Absents letters: i,e,n,w,s,l,p,d. ", "response": "pyats", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a,y. Absents letters: i,e,n,w,s,l,p,d. ", "response": "maray", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,v,s,e,c. ", "response": "tich", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: o,v,s,e,c,h. ", "response": "jugal", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: e,c,h,k,o,v,s,p. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,i,r. Absents letters: e,c,h,k,o,v,s,t,p. ", "response": "lifer", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d. Absents letters: s,a,r,t. ", "response": "bidy", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,d. Absents letters: f,s,r,y,t,l,a. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,d. Absents letters: y,r,s,a,g,t,l,f. ", "response": "idola", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,d. Absents letters: r,y,n,f,m,s,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "deism", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: k,s,y,r,a. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t,o,n. Absents letters: k,s,y,r,c,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n,t. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,k,s,a. ", "response": "torot", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t,o,b,n. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,k,s,l,a,u. ", "response": "loast", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,n. Absents letters: a,c. ", "response": "bling", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,n. Absents letters: m,a,s,g,c,u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e,n. Absents letters: m,s,a,g,c,u. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e,n. Absents letters: m,s,a,g,t,c,u,d. ", "response": "nier", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: s,b,w,n. ", "response": "abuna", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: s,y,n,t,b,w. ", "response": "dik", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: s,y,e,n,t,b,w. ", "response": "aguti", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: y,e,n,z,b,w,s,t. ", "response": "aguti", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,e,b,u,d. ", "response": "tween", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,m,e,b,u,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: i,y,e,b,k,m,o,u,d. ", "response": "bries", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: i,y,e,z,n,b,k,m,o,u,d. ", "response": "pians", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,a,c,d. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h. Absents letters: i,a,o,t,l,c,d. ", "response": "shale", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h. Absents letters: i,c,k,o,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "shy", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h. Absents letters: i,c,k,o,t,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "shy", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: o,v,h. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: k,m,o,v,y,h,u. ", "response": "gages", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: y,r,b,h,k,m,o,v,u. ", "response": "gales", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,p,a. Absents letters: i,r,y,b,h,k,m,o,v,l,u. ", "response": "gapes", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: i,p,e. ", "response": "tifts", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n,t. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,p. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,t,a,n. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,s,p. ", "response": "marly", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,n,t,a. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,c,s,p. ", "response": "tank", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,a,w,e. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: e,l,p,a,w,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,r. Absents letters: e,w,m,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,r. Absents letters: e,c,w,m,v,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "porns", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: a,c,r,t. ", "response": "bip", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: a,r,t,c,u. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: r,c,s,t,p,a,u. ", "response": "gyved", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,y,n. Absents letters: r,c,s,o,t,p,a,u. ", "response": "ensky", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,g,h,n. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,b,h,g,l. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,b,h,s,g,l. ", "response": "faugh", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,b,h,m,s,g,l,t. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,e,c,h,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,e,c,h,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,e,c,h,t,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": -8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,h,g,t,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,s,a,r,f. ", "response": "bump", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,r,c,w,f,s,a,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n. Absents letters: i,r,c,w,s,a,f,u,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,o,e,n. Absents letters: i,r,c,w,f,s,a,u,d. ", "response": "preon", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,v,n. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,v. ", "response": "alder", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,q,r,e,n,v,u. ", "response": "alapa", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,q,r,e,n,s,v,u. ", "response": "galal", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: l,v,u,g. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: y,j,b,m,v,g,l,u. ", "response": "boomy", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,o. Absents letters: y,n,j,b,k,m,v,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "poo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,o. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,j,b,k,m,v,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "loipe", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: w,e,t. ", "response": "gry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: y,e,t,c,b,w. ", "response": "warbs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: y,e,c,b,w,s,t,l,f,u. ", "response": "marra", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: y,e,b,c,w,s,o,t,l,f,u. ", "response": "karri", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: w,r,e,t. ", "response": "kills", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: r,e,n,b,c,w,t,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: r,e,n,c,b,w,k,t,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: r,e,n,b,c,w,k,t,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: v,y,g. ", "response": "robed", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,s,e. Absents letters: i,v,y,n,g,p. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,r,e. Absents letters: i,v,g,y,n,p,a,d. ", "response": "roes", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,s,r,e. Absents letters: i,y,n,v,g,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "moyl", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: k,f,l. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,g. Absents letters: k,e,l,b,f. ", "response": "gag", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r,g. Absents letters: k,f,o,e,n,l,b. ", "response": "tars", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,g,a. Absents letters: y,e,n,b,k,o,t,l,f,d. ", "response": "srug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u. Absents letters: c,h,n. ", "response": "pieta", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t,a,u,d. Absents letters: e,n,b,c,h. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t,l,a,u,d. Absents letters: s,r,e,n,b,c,h. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t,l,a,u,d. Absents letters: r,e,n,c,b,h,s,p. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: i,t,s,n. ", "response": "gyved", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y. Absents letters: i,n,s,t,p. ", "response": "abyes", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y. Absents letters: i,n,m,s,o,g,t,p. ", "response": "pyran", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y. Absents letters: i,n,h,m,s,o,p,g,l,t,u. ", "response": "bgy", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,a,c,w. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d. Absents letters: i,e,c,b,w,k,a. ", "response": "gourd", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: g,d. Absents letters: i,e,n,c,b,w,k,m,a,u. ", "response": "gued", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d,g. Absents letters: i,e,n,b,c,w,k,m,s,l,a,u. ", "response": "gued", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: m,a,y,n. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,u. Absents letters: k,m,q,y,r,n,a. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,c,u,d. Absents letters: q,y,r,n,h,k,m,o,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,c,u,d. Absents letters: q,r,y,n,h,k,m,o,p,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: a,c,e,n. ", "response": "slily", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: e,n,c,g,a,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o. Absents letters: i,x,e,n,c,g,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,s. Absents letters: i,x,e,n,c,k,m,g,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: w,r,d. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: r,t,p,a,w,d. ", "response": "loof", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,b,s. Absents letters: i,r,e,w,t,p,a,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,b,s. Absents letters: i,r,e,w,t,p,a,d. ", "response": "lobus", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,k,s,n. Absents letters: g. ", "response": "kinks", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,k,s,n. Absents letters: m,r,g,b,a. ", "response": "kinks", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,k,s,n. Absents letters: r,b,h,m,g,a,u. ", "response": "kink", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,k,s,n. Absents letters: r,b,h,c,m,g,p,a,u. ", "response": "kinks", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d. Absents letters: k,o,n. ", "response": "waked", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u,d. Absents letters: k,m,o,n. ", "response": "sarod", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u,d. Absents letters: x,n,k,m,o,a. ", "response": "seeld", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,u,d. Absents letters: x,n,k,m,o,f,l,a. ", "response": "seise", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: g. Absents letters: i,v,e,d. ", "response": "faugh", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n,g. Absents letters: i,v,e,c,h,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,g,r,n. Absents letters: i,e,c,h,s,v,p,u,d. ", "response": "agria", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,g,r,n,a. Absents letters: i,e,c,h,s,v,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: p,a,c,h. ", "response": "gog", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: x,e,n,c,h,s,t,p,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: x,e,n,c,h,s,t,p,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: x,e,n,c,h,s,t,p,a. ", "response": "boing", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,e. Absents letters: k,l. ", "response": "mesic", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,e. Absents letters: k,s,y,t,l,f. ", "response": "mecca", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,o,e. Absents letters: y,r,k,s,v,a,t,l,f. ", "response": "oj", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,o,e. Absents letters: r,y,n,k,f,s,v,t,l,a. ", "response": "oxim", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: e,c,b,u,d. ", "response": "bight", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: e,c,b,o,s,u,d. ", "response": "kaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: e,z,n,c,b,k,o,s,u,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: e,n,z,b,c,k,o,s,t,l,u,d. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,n,a,u,d. ", "response": "tween", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,m,s,n,a,u,d. ", "response": "bry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,n,m,s,a,u,d. ", "response": "ber", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: v,r,e. Absents letters: i,m,s,n,a,u,d. ", "response": "valet", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,a,u. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: l,p,a,u. ", "response": "shelf", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: m,g,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: h,m,g,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: x,a,r,t. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: k,r,x,t,y,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e. Absents letters: y,r,x,n,k,o,g,t,p,a. ", "response": "shise", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e. Absents letters: r,y,n,x,k,o,p,g,t,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,r,g,j,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,o,r,g,p,j,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,r,j,o,g,p,a. ", "response": "deked", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,r,j,h,o,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: o,s,b. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: k,o,s,a,b. ", "response": "bet", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: e,b,k,m,o,s,l,a. ", "response": "twerp", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: r,e,y,b,k,m,o,s,l,p,a. ", "response": "fyt", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,t. Absents letters: k,h. ", "response": "sitar", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,t. Absents letters: k,m,o,g,p,a,h. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,t. Absents letters: y,h,k,m,o,g,p,a. ", "response": "seity", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,t. Absents letters: y,h,w,k,m,o,g,p,a,u. ", "response": "tices", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: i,s,a,w. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: i,n,c,h,w,s,o,a. ", "response": "tween", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,r. Absents letters: i,n,c,h,w,m,s,o,a. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,r. Absents letters: i,n,c,h,w,k,m,s,o,a. ", "response": "perry", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: p,a,r. ", "response": "sewel", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c,e. Absents letters: r,p,a,u. ", "response": "skets", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c,e. Absents letters: r,n,g,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "cides", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c,e. Absents letters: r,n,k,o,t,g,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "sce", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: f,v,u. ", "response": "wared", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: m,v,r,p,f,u. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,a. Absents letters: r,c,m,v,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,r,j,c,w,m,v,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "sake", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,e. Absents letters: l,y. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,e,a. Absents letters: y,l,p,c. ", "response": "maise", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,e,a. Absents letters: y,r,c,g,l,p,u. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,e,a. Absents letters: r,y,c,o,g,l,p,u. ", "response": "maise", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,r. Absents letters: k,e. ", "response": "galvo", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,a. Absents letters: k,e,g,l,u. ", "response": "ars", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,o,a,r. Absents letters: e,k,g,l,t,f,u. ", "response": "ars", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,y,a. Absents letters: i,e,b,k,s,g,l,t,f,u. ", "response": "boomy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: l,r,t. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,s. Absents letters: g,r,e,t,l. ", "response": "loirs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,s. Absents letters: r,e,y,g,l,t,u. ", "response": "loirs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,s. Absents letters: y,r,e,w,g,l,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: y,w,e,n. ", "response": "guss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: g,y,e,n,w,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: y,e,n,w,k,o,g,d. ", "response": "slunk", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,l,u. Absents letters: y,e,n,w,k,m,o,g,a,d. ", "response": "slugs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: k,z,y,n. ", "response": "diz", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: y,e,n,z,b,k,o,l. ", "response": "pians", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: y,e,z,n,x,b,c,k,o,l,u. ", "response": "gri", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,r. Absents letters: x,y,n,e,z,b,c,k,o,l,u. ", "response": "pirai", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: m,s,g. ", "response": "dik", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: m,s,o,r,e,g. ", "response": "hight", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,b. Absents letters: r,e,m,s,o,g. ", "response": "boing", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,b,n. Absents letters: r,e,m,s,o,v,g,a. ", "response": "boing", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: k,p,s. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,t. Absents letters: k,s,o,l,p,b. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,r,t. Absents letters: e,b,k,s,o,l,p,f. ", "response": "tar", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,r,t,a. Absents letters: e,b,c,k,s,o,l,p,f,u. ", "response": "marri", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: s,a,r. ", "response": "nix", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: f,s,r,a. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: s,a,r,c,f. ", "response": "nix", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: i,r,c,s,a,f. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,p,r,e. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,r,e,y,n,m,o,p. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,n,m,o,p,u. ", "response": "gales", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,w. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,r,h,m,o,p,f,u. ", "response": "warbs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: k,e,g. ", "response": "tray", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y. Absents letters: k,e,g,l,p,u. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y. Absents letters: e,n,h,w,k,g,l,p,u. ", "response": "sy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y. Absents letters: e,n,h,w,k,o,g,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "pyats", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: k,o,r,s. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: k,o,s,r,t,f. ", "response": "wax", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: r,n,j,c,k,o,s,t,f,u. ", "response": "leany", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: r,n,j,c,b,k,o,s,t,f,u. ", "response": "heame", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,s,a,u. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,s,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "tich", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: m,s,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "envo", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n. Absents letters: b,m,s,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "toney", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,y,u. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c. Absents letters: y,e,l,u. ", "response": "scots", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,c. Absents letters: o,y,e,l,b,u. ", "response": "tifs", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,c. Absents letters: y,e,r,b,o,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "tic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,e,p,c,u. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b. Absents letters: r,e,c,w,o,p,u. ", "response": "bo b", "reward": -11.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,b. Absents letters: r,e,y,c,w,k,o,s,p,u. ", "response": "bight", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,b. Absents letters: y,r,e,n,c,w,k,o,s,p,u. ", "response": "bight", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: l,p,x,e. ", "response": "envo", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: x,e,y,n,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "dices", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: y,x,e,n,c,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: x,y,e,n,r,c,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "kui", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: k,h,e,t. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: e,h,k,m,s,t,a. ", "response": "sext", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,e,z,b,h,w,k,m,s,t,a. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,e,z,b,h,w,k,m,s,t,a. ", "response": "sebum", "reward": -8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: b,r. ", "response": "stil", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,y. Absents letters: r,c,e,l,p,b. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,y. Absents letters: r,e,n,b,c,l,p,a. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,v,y. Absents letters: r,e,n,c,b,l,p,a. ", "response": "vys", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p. Absents letters: i,o,r. ", "response": "elope", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p. Absents letters: i,o,s,r,l,a. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p. Absents letters: i,r,b,o,s,g,l,a. ", "response": "bum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p. Absents letters: i,r,e,b,k,o,s,g,l,a. ", "response": "bum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,a,b,t. ", "response": "dorm", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: a,s,t,l,j,b. ", "response": "bake", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: j,b,s,o,t,l,a. ", "response": "enact", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e. Absents letters: j,b,o,s,t,l,a. ", "response": "mewed", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: t,u,n. ", "response": "boors", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: m,o,v,e,n,t,u. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: e,n,c,m,o,v,t,u. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: y,e,n,c,m,o,v,t,u. ", "response": "gales", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: a,f,y. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: a,y,e,t,p,f. ", "response": "gou", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: a,y,e,t,r,p,f,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: r,y,e,f,m,t,p,a,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b. Absents letters: i,m,e,d. ", "response": "boors", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,b,n. Absents letters: i,m,s,e,d. ", "response": "abuna", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,a,n. Absents letters: i,e,m,s,o,p,d. ", "response": "boans", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,b,n. Absents letters: i,e,c,m,s,o,p,d. ", "response": "balmy", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,s,u,n. ", "response": "fiche", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,r,n,s,o,t,u. ", "response": "waker", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,r,n,s,o,t,p,u. ", "response": "bided", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,r,n,z,s,o,t,p,u. ", "response": "bed", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: o,n,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: o,y,n,l,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: o,y,n,l,a,d. ", "response": "bries", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: y,n,o,s,g,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "reef", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: w,t. ", "response": "relet", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: y,t,f,w,d. ", "response": "siler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,a. Absents letters: y,n,t,f,w,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,a. Absents letters: y,n,j,w,o,g,t,f,u,d. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: o,e,n. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,k. Absents letters: o,e,n,c,h. ", "response": "kinks", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,k. Absents letters: e,n,c,h,w,o,g,d. ", "response": "siker", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,k,s,p. Absents letters: e,n,c,h,w,o,g,a,d. ", "response": "kiers", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p. Absents letters: i,r,e,n. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,j,b. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,j,b,o,g. ", "response": "panax", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,j,b,h,o,g,l,u. ", "response": "pases", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: m,c,p,u. ", "response": "gry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,r. Absents letters: m,s,e,p,c,u. ", "response": "durry", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,r. Absents letters: x,e,c,m,s,p,u,d. ", "response": "lark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,i,r. Absents letters: x,e,c,m,s,t,p,u,d. ", "response": "metal", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,s,c,u,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,c,h,o,s,u,d. ", "response": "stil", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,r,z,c,h,o,s,t,u,d. ", "response": "stol", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,r,e,z,c,h,o,s,t,p,u,d. ", "response": "gilly", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: l,h. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,t. Absents letters: l,a,h,f. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,t. Absents letters: y,n,b,h,f,l,a,u. ", "response": "siter", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,t,d. Absents letters: y,x,n,b,h,a,l,f,u. ", "response": "tides", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u. Absents letters: y,t. ", "response": "saris", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u. Absents letters: o,y,e,t,f,d. ", "response": "gur", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u. Absents letters: y,e,o,s,a,t,l,p,f,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u. Absents letters: y,e,c,f,o,s,t,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,d. Absents letters: l,o,r. ", "response": "loirs", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,d. Absents letters: r,o,s,g,l,u. ", "response": "loid", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,d. Absents letters: r,b,h,o,s,g,l,t,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,d. Absents letters: r,b,h,o,s,g,l,t,u. ", "response": "loid", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,t. Absents letters: l,a,r. ", "response": "twerp", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t. Absents letters: r,l,a,u. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t. Absents letters: r,y,c,k,l,a,u. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,k,l,a,u. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: w,o,r,t. ", "response": "skull", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: r,e,w,o,t,p,u. ", "response": "gals", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: r,e,b,w,k,o,t,p,u. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,b,w,k,o,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: k,s,h. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: k,s,l,h,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,r. Absents letters: k,s,e,l,h,d. ", "response": "arcos", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,r. Absents letters: e,n,h,k,s,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "aru", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: d,a,t. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,e. Absents letters: t,b,a,d. ", "response": "loes", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,o,e,p. Absents letters: d,a,b,t. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,o,e,p. Absents letters: a,g,t,l,b,d. ", "response": "kop", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: l,h,e,t. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,d. Absents letters: e,t,l,p,c,h. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,a,d. Absents letters: r,e,t,l,p,c,h. ", "response": "diz", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,a,d. Absents letters: r,e,c,h,m,s,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "abide", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: m,r,n. ", "response": "tic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,l. Absents letters: m,g,r,n,a. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,l. Absents letters: r,y,n,b,c,m,g,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,l. Absents letters: y,r,n,c,b,m,g,a,d. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,b. ", "response": "sne", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n,a. Absents letters: i,b. ", "response": "sna", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,n. Absents letters: i,e,t,b,u. ", "response": "sango", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,t,l,b,h,u. ", "response": "sna", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,r,e. Absents letters: g. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,c. Absents letters: s,w,g. ", "response": "reef", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,r,e. Absents letters: i,j,w,s,g,f,u. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,c,r,e. Absents letters: i,j,w,s,o,g,f,u,d. ", "response": "bce", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,t. Absents letters: l,a. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,e,t. Absents letters: r,l,b,a,u. ", "response": "tke", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,e,t. Absents letters: a,r,n,g,l,b,u. ", "response": "ket", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,e,t. Absents letters: r,n,b,m,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "kets", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: a,n. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: k,o,t,y,n,c,a. ", "response": "gents", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: y,n,c,w,k,o,t,l,a. ", "response": "ges", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: y,n,c,w,k,o,t,l,a. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: o,s,c. ", "response": "bing", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,n. Absents letters: m,o,s,r,e,c. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,n. Absents letters: r,e,c,m,o,s. ", "response": "nix", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n,a. Absents letters: r,e,c,m,o,s,p. ", "response": "bling", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: k,t,e,n. ", "response": "pungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,e,n,k,g,t,l. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: i,e,n,k,g,l,t,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: i,e,n,b,h,k,g,l,t,u,d. ", "response": "sar", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: p,s,a,n. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e. Absents letters: i,s,g,n,p,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,c,e. Absents letters: i,n,s,t,g,p,a,u. ", "response": "cask", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,c. Absents letters: i,x,n,s,g,t,p,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: i,c. ", "response": "lexis", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,e. Absents letters: i,o,p,c,u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,l,a. Absents letters: i,o,n,g,p,c,u. ", "response": "sel", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,l,a. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,k,o,t,g,p,u. ", "response": "loes", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,e,z,a,d. ", "response": "bum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,e,z,o,l,a,d. ", "response": "barks", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,e,z,o,t,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,e,z,o,t,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "gnats", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: a,r,u. ", "response": "siler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,s,t. Absents letters: o,a,r,u. ", "response": "sist", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,s,n,t. Absents letters: o,r,g,a,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,s,n,t. Absents letters: r,f,o,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "minos", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y. Absents letters: l,d. ", "response": "pyats", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y. Absents letters: r,l,h,d. ", "response": "pyats", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y. Absents letters: r,e,l,b,h,d. ", "response": "tyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y. Absents letters: r,e,b,h,w,l,d. ", "response": "s gy", "reward": -11.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,p,a,e. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,e,n,c,l,p,a. ", "response": "guss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,u. Absents letters: i,e,n,c,o,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "gur", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,u. Absents letters: i,e,n,c,o,t,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "shur", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: p,m,y,g. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: m,y,g,p,u. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,a. Absents letters: y,n,b,m,o,g,p,u. ", "response": "sals", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,l,a. Absents letters: y,n,b,m,o,g,p,u. ", "response": "sek", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y. Absents letters: k,h. ", "response": "enact", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,a,y,t. Absents letters: k,s,b,h,u. ", "response": "prate", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,r,t,a. Absents letters: k,m,s,b,h,u. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,y,t,a. Absents letters: b,h,k,m,s,l,u. ", "response": "prate", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,e. Absents letters: o,h,r. ", "response": "peels", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,e. Absents letters: i,o,r,y,t,h. ", "response": "pwn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,h,o,t,a. ", "response": "premy", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,h,o,t,a. ", "response": "pecke", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n. Absents letters: e. ", "response": "gin", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,n. Absents letters: i,a,f,e. ", "response": "dyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,n. Absents letters: i,f,e,l,b,a. ", "response": "kests", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,n,t. Absents letters: i,e,b,a,l,f. ", "response": "dices", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: m,f,u,t. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: w,m,o,t,f,u. ", "response": "came", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,c,h,w,m,o,t,f,u. ", "response": "bales", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,n,c,h,w,m,o,t,f,u. ", "response": "bales", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,v,r. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: k,v,r,l,b,a. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: r,b,c,k,v,l,a. ", "response": "bese", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e. Absents letters: r,b,c,k,v,l,a. ", "response": "sma", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: e,l,b,u,d. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: a,e,l,b,u,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m. Absents letters: e,b,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "sume", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,p,t. Absents letters: i,e,b,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "maror", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: t,u,n. ", "response": "gales", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,y,e. Absents letters: c,n,t,a,u. ", "response": "lofty", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,y,e. Absents letters: m,a,n,t,c,h,u. ", "response": "gly", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,i,y,e. Absents letters: n,c,h,m,s,t,a,u. ", "response": "vinyl", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: l,c,h. ", "response": "rorie", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: n,l,p,c,h. ", "response": "ars", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: i,n,c,h,o,l,p. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: i,n,c,h,o,s,l,p. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,a,r. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b. Absents letters: i,r,t,a. ", "response": "boobs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,b. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,t,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,c. Absents letters: o,e. ", "response": "scops", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,p,c. Absents letters: m,o,e,f. ", "response": "pals", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c,p,a. Absents letters: r,e,b,h,m,o,f,u. ", "response": "pach", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,p,c. Absents letters: r,e,b,h,m,o,v,l,f,u. ", "response": "paces", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n. Absents letters: i,o,x. ", "response": "ennog", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e,n. Absents letters: i,o,x,t,f,u. ", "response": "pans", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n,a. Absents letters: i,x,c,h,o,t,l,f,u. ", "response": "sena", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e,n. Absents letters: i,x,r,c,h,w,o,t,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "pyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,o,h. ", "response": "gourd", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: o,e,g,l,b,a,h. ", "response": "kiers", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,r. Absents letters: e,b,h,c,o,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "kier", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,r. Absents letters: y,e,c,b,h,o,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "kiers", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,s,a,t,b. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: n,b,o,s,t,a. ", "response": "bry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,n,b,o,s,t,p,a,d. ", "response": "rorie", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,n,z,b,o,s,t,p,a,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,r,e. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: m,o,v,r,e,n. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y,d. Absents letters: r,e,n,m,o,v,s,t. ", "response": "cadgy", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y,d. Absents letters: r,e,n,m,o,v,s,t,l. ", "response": "adyl", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: k,d. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e. Absents letters: k,o,y,d. ", "response": "sices", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,r,e. Absents letters: k,o,y,n,a,d. ", "response": "seirs", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e,s,v. Absents letters: k,o,y,n,l,a,d. ", "response": "tiers", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: l,s,t. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,r. Absents letters: i,s,t,l. ", "response": "arcos", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,r. Absents letters: i,m,s,y,t,l. ", "response": "arbor", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,a. Absents letters: i,y,m,s,t,l,p,d. ", "response": "boor", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: d,n. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,r,e. Absents letters: t,n,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,r,e. Absents letters: i,m,n,t,c,d. ", "response": "loess", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,r,e. Absents letters: i,m,k,a,n,t,c,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: k,s,y,c,u. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: k,i,s,y,c,h,u. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,h,k,s,f,u. ", "response": "agley", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,h,k,s,f,u,d. ", "response": "leaze", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,o,y,b,c. ", "response": "bce", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u. Absents letters: i,m,o,y,e,c,b. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u. Absents letters: i,y,e,b,c,h,m,o,s. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u,t. Absents letters: i,y,e,c,b,h,m,o,s,l. ", "response": "prunt", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: o,v,r,e. ", "response": "bun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: r,e,c,o,v,a. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n. Absents letters: o,v,a,r,e,l,c. ", "response": "sna", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n. Absents letters: r,e,c,m,o,v,l,a. ", "response": "sna", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,a,y. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: y,t,l,a. ", "response": "gus", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,y,x,n,f,t,l,a. ", "response": "seaze", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,y,x,n,r,a,t,l,f,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: p,o,s. ", "response": "bunya", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: o,s,y,p,a,w. ", "response": "enact", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t,n. Absents letters: i,y,w,o,s,p,a. ", "response": "enact", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,r,n,t. Absents letters: i,y,w,o,s,p,a. ", "response": "rents", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,a,r. Absents letters: l,o. ", "response": "paras", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,c,p,a. Absents letters: l,o,b. ", "response": "pards", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,c,p,a. Absents letters: o,y,l,b,u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,c,e,p,a. Absents letters: o,y,t,l,b,u. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: s,t. ", "response": "relet", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: s,o,t,l,u. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: y,n,s,o,t,l,u. ", "response": "swer", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,r,e. Absents letters: y,n,s,o,t,l,u. ", "response": "preed", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: i,a,x,n. ", "response": "hules", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: i,x,n,b,o,s,g,a. ", "response": "bum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: i,x,r,n,e,z,b,o,s,g,a,d. ", "response": "bum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: i,x,e,n,r,z,b,o,s,g,a,d. ", "response": "bum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: b,c,h,a. ", "response": "pyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: n,c,b,h,o,a. ", "response": "shme", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: n,j,c,b,h,o,s,t,a,u. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: y,n,j,b,c,h,o,s,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: k,c,h,n. ", "response": "envo", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: n,c,h,k,s,l,a,u. ", "response": "diz", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,y,r. Absents letters: n,c,h,k,s,l,a,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,y,r. Absents letters: n,c,h,k,s,l,a,u. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,l. Absents letters: o,c,n. ", "response": "tic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,l. Absents letters: n,c,m,o,g,a,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,l. Absents letters: n,c,m,o,s,g,a,u,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e,l. Absents letters: n,c,m,o,s,g,a,u,d. ", "response": "relet", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: o,h,t. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y. Absents letters: o,n,t,a,h. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,s,y. Absents letters: o,n,t,a,h,w,d. ", "response": "syl", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,r. Absents letters: i,n,h,w,o,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "syl", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: t,o,h,z. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,e. Absents letters: i,m,o,g,z,t,h. ", "response": "albe", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,l,a. Absents letters: i,y,z,h,m,o,g,t. ", "response": "lazel", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,z,h,m,o,v,g,t. ", "response": "albe", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,t,e,n. ", "response": "bocks", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,m,g,e,n,t. ", "response": "fards", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,u. Absents letters: i,e,n,m,g,t. ", "response": "sau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,u. Absents letters: i,e,n,m,g,t. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,r,t,f,h. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,g. Absents letters: i,v,r,e,t,f,h. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,g. Absents letters: i,r,e,y,h,v,t,p,f. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n,g,b,a. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,h,v,t,p,f. ", "response": "boong", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: o,h,y,t. ", "response": "gum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: y,e,h,o,t,p. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u. Absents letters: y,e,h,m,o,t,p. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u. Absents letters: y,e,h,k,m,o,t,l,p. ", "response": "dray", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,p,o,d. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,y,k,o,l,p,d. ", "response": "nark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,s,a. Absents letters: i,y,k,o,l,p,d. ", "response": "cages", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r,e,c. Absents letters: i,y,x,h,k,o,l,p,d. ", "response": "tared", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,t. Absents letters: a,h,e. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,r,t. Absents letters: f,e,n,a,h. ", "response": "twerp", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,s,y,t. Absents letters: i,a,e,n,f,h,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,r,t. Absents letters: i,e,n,h,f,m,g,a,d. ", "response": "sy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,g. Absents letters: s,r. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,g. Absents letters: s,o,r,c,u. ", "response": "gin", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,g. Absents letters: m,s,o,a,r,c,u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,g. Absents letters: r,c,m,s,o,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,k,g,n. ", "response": "nulla", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,e,n,c,h,k,g,p. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,e,n,c,h,k,g,p. ", "response": "marls", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,r,a. Absents letters: i,q,e,n,c,h,k,o,g,p. ", "response": "maror", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,c. ", "response": "rej", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,x,u. Absents letters: i,c,l. ", "response": "exons", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: x,r,e,u. Absents letters: i,k,s,o,l,c. ", "response": "exile", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,x,e,u. Absents letters: i,c,k,o,s,l,a,d. ", "response": "erugo", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d. Absents letters: m,a,u,n. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,c,d. Absents letters: m,q,n,a,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,c,d. Absents letters: q,n,m,o,g,a,u. ", "response": "skids", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,c,d. Absents letters: q,n,h,m,o,g,a,u. ", "response": "dikes", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,e,t. Absents letters: i. ", "response": "sne", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,t,n. Absents letters: i,d. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,o,e,t. Absents letters: i,l,w,d. ", "response": "ennog", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,e,t,n. Absents letters: i,l,f,w,d. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,s,f,w. ", "response": "abode", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: e,h,w,s,l,p,f,d. ", "response": "abode", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: e,h,w,s,l,p,f,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,o,a. Absents letters: i,y,e,h,w,s,t,l,p,f,d. ", "response": "boke", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: a,t. ", "response": "nud", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,o,v,t,l,a. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,r,f,o,v,t,l,a. ", "response": "sne", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,r,y,m,o,v,a,t,l,f. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c. Absents letters: i,m,o,h. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c. Absents letters: i,h,k,m,o,s,l,p. ", "response": "bling", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,r,e. Absents letters: i,y,h,k,m,o,s,l,p,d. ", "response": "crith", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,r,e. Absents letters: i,y,h,k,m,o,s,t,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "crice", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: k,p,o,r. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: k,i,o,r,e,t,p. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,r,e,y,n,k,o,t,p. ", "response": "gim", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,n,c,k,o,t,l,p. ", "response": "fests", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,t. Absents letters: m,p,d. ", "response": "shirk", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,t. Absents letters: i,m,r,p,f,d. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,t,a. Absents letters: i,m,v,r,l,p,f,d. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,t,a. Absents letters: i,r,b,m,v,l,p,f,d. ", "response": "tares", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: s,o,u,t. ", "response": "bider", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: n,s,o,t,u,d. ", "response": "bider", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: n,w,s,o,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "bry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: n,w,s,o,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,g. Absents letters: b,r,e. ", "response": "boing", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,g. Absents letters: s,t,r,e,y,p,b. ", "response": "faugh", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,g. Absents letters: y,r,e,b,c,s,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "gin", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,u,g. Absents letters: r,y,e,c,b,s,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "bing", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,n. Absents letters: w,r. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,n. Absents letters: r,t,a,w. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,n,c. Absents letters: r,t,a,w,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,s,o,n. Absents letters: r,y,t,b,a,w,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: i,o,h. ", "response": "gors", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,b,a. Absents letters: i,o,x,h. ", "response": "brans", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r,b. Absents letters: i,o,x,e,n,h. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,r,b,a. Absents letters: i,x,e,n,y,c,h,o,u. ", "response": "bards", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: y,g,l,f,u. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: s,y,g,l,b,f,u. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,n. Absents letters: y,e,b,s,g,l,t,f,u. ", "response": "dong", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,n. Absents letters: y,e,b,s,p,g,l,t,f,u. ", "response": "boans", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,i. Absents letters: v,e. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n,l. Absents letters: o,v,e,w,u. ", "response": "gin", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n,l. Absents letters: o,v,e,t,w,u. ", "response": "gil", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n,l. Absents letters: e,w,o,v,t,a,u. ", "response": "slink", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: a,c,n. ", "response": "gry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,u. Absents letters: a,n,t,c,d. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,u. Absents letters: a,o,n,t,c,d. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,u. Absents letters: n,c,o,v,t,a,d. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: m,j,b,u. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: r,e,j,b,m,s,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,o. Absents letters: r,e,j,b,m,s,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "boke", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,o,n. Absents letters: r,e,y,j,b,m,s,g,l,t,a,u. ", "response": "nork", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d. Absents letters: i,g,y,n. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,f,r,d. Absents letters: i,g,y,n,t,u. ", "response": "fards", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,f,d. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,p,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "skiff", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,f,d. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,k,t,g,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "fards", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: m,e. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: k,m,e,c. ", "response": "maric", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: k,m,e,g,p,c. ", "response": "pians", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,r,s. Absents letters: e,n,c,k,m,g,l,p. ", "response": "arcos", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,a,h,d. ", "response": "fests", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,e,z,n,b,h,l,a,d. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: i,e,n,z,b,h,m,s,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,u. Absents letters: i,e,z,n,b,h,m,s,o,g,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "quy", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: p,o,c,h. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: o,a,p,c,h,u. ", "response": "tires", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,r. Absents letters: n,c,h,o,t,p,a,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,r,e. Absents letters: n,z,c,h,o,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "shier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: p,s,r,t. ", "response": "fad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,c,a. Absents letters: k,s,r,y,t,p,w. ", "response": "caica", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,c. Absents letters: y,r,w,k,s,g,t,p,u,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,c,h. Absents letters: r,y,w,k,s,p,g,l,t,u,d. ", "response": "cach", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: a,s,f,n. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: y,n,c,s,a,l,f. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: y,n,c,s,a,l,f. ", "response": "diker", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: y,n,c,s,a,l,f. ", "response": "dices", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,e,n,t,a. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: y,e,n,b,s,v,t,a. ", "response": "dik", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: y,e,n,b,s,v,o,g,t,l,a. ", "response": "biffs", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: y,e,n,b,c,h,s,v,o,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "kib", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u. Absents letters: p,e,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u. Absents letters: y,e,p,b,d. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u. Absents letters: y,e,b,c,p,d. ", "response": "boong", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u,n. Absents letters: i,y,e,b,c,p,a,d. ", "response": "tus", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,a,n,b,u. ", "response": "sebum", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,a,v,r,n,b,u. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,e. Absents letters: i,r,x,n,b,v,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,e. Absents letters: i,r,x,n,b,v,l,a,u. ", "response": "sso", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: m,r,e,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: m,r,e,y,l,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,a. Absents letters: m,y,r,e,l,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,s,b. Absents letters: i,r,y,e,m,l,u,d. ", "response": "boaks", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: r,j,y. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: k,y,r,n,j,u. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,j,k,m,s,u. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,j,k,m,s,v,a,u,d. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: o,b,d. ", "response": "kro", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,r. Absents letters: o,a,c,b,h,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,r. Absents letters: b,c,h,o,t,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,s,r. Absents letters: c,b,h,w,o,t,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "kiers", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: m,g,u,n. ", "response": "nal", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: r,n,m,s,g,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: r,n,b,m,s,g,l,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: r,n,b,m,s,o,g,l,u,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,k,o,s,j. ", "response": "sext", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,r,y,j,k,o,s. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,y,r,j,c,k,o,s,p,u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,t. Absents letters: i,y,r,j,c,k,o,s,g,p,u. ", "response": "hefty", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: w,v,r,e. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,s. Absents letters: v,r,e,a,h,w. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,l,c,u. Absents letters: v,r,e,a,h,w. ", "response": "lobus", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,l,c,u. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,h,w,v,t,a. ", "response": "locks", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: a,v,r,e. ", "response": "bling", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,v,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,y,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,v,a,d. ", "response": "slily", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,y,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,k,o,v,a,d. ", "response": "stly", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: l,g. ", "response": "tared", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: o,y,g,l,a,h. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: y,h,o,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: y,h,o,g,l,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: l,a. ", "response": "siler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,o. Absents letters: m,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,o. Absents letters: r,e,h,m,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "gos", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,o. Absents letters: r,e,n,h,m,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: l,y,g. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: v,y,e,g,l. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,t. Absents letters: v,y,e,g,l,p,c. ", "response": "boans", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,t. Absents letters: y,e,n,c,b,w,v,g,l,p. ", "response": "rats", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c. Absents letters: l,x,e. ", "response": "coria", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c. Absents letters: s,x,e,l,a. ", "response": "boppy", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c. Absents letters: x,e,s,l,p,a. ", "response": "corny", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,c,g. Absents letters: x,e,n,m,s,l,p,a. ", "response": "gog", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: k,y,r,s. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,r,k,m,s,g,u. ", "response": "fad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: r,y,k,m,s,g,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,l,p,a. Absents letters: y,r,k,m,s,g,u,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: o,d,n. ", "response": "arame", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: o,s,n,h,d. ", "response": "maror", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: o,s,n,t,b,h,d. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: y,n,b,h,o,s,t,l,d. ", "response": "arvee", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,s,f,n. ", "response": "leany", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,y,n,k,s,f,u,d. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,y,n,c,h,k,s,a,t,f,u,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,y,n,c,h,k,f,s,g,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,s. Absents letters: i,n. ", "response": "lobus", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,s,e. Absents letters: i,x,r,n,l,a. ", "response": "bode", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,s,e. Absents letters: i,x,r,n,y,v,l,a. ", "response": "bum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,s,e. Absents letters: i,y,x,n,r,v,l,p,a. ", "response": "moes", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,o,r,s. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: r,o,s,v,t,l. ", "response": "bonie", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n. Absents letters: i,r,o,v,s,t,l,a. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n. Absents letters: i,r,o,v,s,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "dyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n. Absents letters: h,w,e. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,n. Absents letters: i,e,l,h,w,u. ", "response": "spink", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,n. Absents letters: i,e,b,h,w,k,l,u. ", "response": "pans", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n,p,a. Absents letters: i,e,b,h,w,k,t,l,u. ", "response": "gon", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,k,s,l,f. ", "response": "bip", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: i,k,s,a,g,l,f. ", "response": "rogu", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e. Absents letters: i,k,f,s,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,o,r,e. Absents letters: i,k,s,a,g,l,t,f. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: a,c,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: f,a,s,j,c,d. ", "response": "tine", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: r,j,c,h,s,a,t,f,d. ", "response": "bonie", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,n. Absents letters: r,j,c,h,f,s,o,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "niger", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,c,i. ", "response": "dices", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,r,y,l,p,c,h. ", "response": "aglee", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,c,h,b,l,p. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: v,e,a,u. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,c,h,b,s,l,p. ", "response": "vau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: k,y,r. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: k,y,r,e,t,j. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,s,a. Absents letters: k,o,y,e,r,l,t,j. ", "response": "sma", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,s,a,d. Absents letters: y,e,r,j,k,o,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "sma", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: a,t. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: t,l,c,b,a. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,e. Absents letters: a,t,l,c,b,h. ", "response": "kook", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,e. Absents letters: r,b,c,h,k,t,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "gos", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: a,r,e,d. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: r,e,a,d. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t,s,l. Absents letters: o,r,e,p,a,d. ", "response": "slily", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,l,t. Absents letters: r,e,c,o,p,a,d. ", "response": "sluit", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,c,h,g. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,y,g,p,c,h. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: y,c,h,k,o,g,p,a. ", "response": "seels", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: y,c,h,k,o,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "secco", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: k,h. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,s. Absents letters: k,i,v,e,h,w. ", "response": "dork", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,r,g. Absents letters: i,e,h,w,k,v,t,a. ", "response": "gor", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,r,g. Absents letters: i,e,c,h,w,k,v,t,l,a. ", "response": "rogu", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: m,a,r. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: m,r,t,p,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: m,r,y,t,p,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,e. Absents letters: y,r,c,m,t,p,a. ", "response": "leves", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: p,s,y,u. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,r,t. Absents letters: s,o,y,g,p,a,u. ", "response": "crith", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,r,e,t. Absents letters: y,b,f,s,o,g,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "tinct", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,t,c. Absents letters: y,b,s,o,a,g,l,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "tinct", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,s,w. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,t. Absents letters: i,s,o,r,w,u. ", "response": "belt", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,t. Absents letters: i,r,c,w,k,s,o,p,u. ", "response": "belt", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,t. Absents letters: i,r,c,h,w,k,s,o,p,u. ", "response": "tal", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s. Absents letters: k,y,e. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,o. Absents letters: k,y,e,j,b. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,o. Absents letters: i,y,e,z,j,b,k,a. ", "response": "progs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,o. Absents letters: i,y,e,z,r,j,b,k,a,d. ", "response": "bops", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: s,n. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,s,n,l,p,f. ", "response": "aboma", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: i,r,n,s,l,p,f. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: i,r,x,n,e,b,s,l,p,f. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,e,l,p,a. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: s,e,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "coder", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: r,e,s,t,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: r,e,b,s,t,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "quine", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,g,t,c,h. ", "response": "fad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,h,o,g,t. ", "response": "pores", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,h,m,o,g,t,u. ", "response": "yells", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,h,m,o,v,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "sy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b. Absents letters: l,o,c,e. ", "response": "boart", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b,a. Absents letters: i,k,o,e,t,l,c. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,b,u. Absents letters: i,q,r,e,c,k,o,t,l. ", "response": "abuse", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b,a,u. Absents letters: i,q,r,e,c,k,o,t,l,f. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e. Absents letters: x,p,y. ", "response": "boe", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e. Absents letters: i,y,x,g,n,p. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,e. Absents letters: i,g,y,x,n,p,f. ", "response": "bough", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,e,t. Absents letters: i,x,y,n,b,a,g,p,f. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: w,e,d. ", "response": "porns", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: i,e,n,c,w,m,a,d. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: i,e,n,c,w,m,s,g,a,d. ", "response": "rogu", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: i,e,n,z,c,w,m,s,g,a,d. ", "response": "porns", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: k,a,l,c,u. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: r,c,b,h,k,l,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,d. Absents letters: i,r,b,c,h,w,k,l,a,u. ", "response": "doups", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,d. Absents letters: i,r,c,b,h,w,k,s,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "tiled", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: s,r,e. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,s,o,r,e,y. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,y,m,s,o,g. ", "response": "blain", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,m,s,o,g. ", "response": "galvo", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: g. Absents letters: a,r,e,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: g. Absents letters: r,e,s,l,a,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: g. Absents letters: i,r,e,s,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,y,g. Absents letters: i,r,e,h,s,o,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "gyppy", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: k,o,a,n. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c. Absents letters: k,o,n,l,a. ", "response": "cask", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c,e. Absents letters: k,o,r,n,l,t,a. ", "response": "cask", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c,e. Absents letters: r,n,k,o,t,l,a. ", "response": "cides", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e. Absents letters: l,u. ", "response": "mesic", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e. Absents letters: s,a,l,f,u. ", "response": "meath", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e,d. Absents letters: i,s,a,x,l,f,u. ", "response": "mewed", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e,d. Absents letters: i,x,h,f,s,l,a,u. ", "response": "mewed", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: o,b,t. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,e. Absents letters: o,a,t,b,h. ", "response": "meime", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,e. Absents letters: f,o,a,t,c,b,h. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,e. Absents letters: b,c,h,o,a,s,t,f. ", "response": "merit", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: b,e,d. ", "response": "galas", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,a. Absents letters: s,e,n,b,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,a. Absents letters: y,e,n,b,h,s,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,t,l,a. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,b,h,s,g,d. ", "response": "tool", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,o,y,t. ", "response": "gals", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: y,r,n,w,o,t,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: r,y,n,e,w,o,t,a,d. ", "response": "shog", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: y,r,e,n,c,w,o,t,a,d. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,p,c,t. ", "response": "wak", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,d. Absents letters: o,s,g,t,l,p,c. ", "response": "deary", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,w,e,d. Absents letters: c,h,m,o,s,t,g,l,p,u. ", "response": "wared", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,a,w,d. Absents letters: c,h,m,o,s,g,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "wked", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,c,u,g. ", "response": "niger", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: r,c,h,m,s,g,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: r,c,h,m,s,g,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y. Absents letters: r,e,j,c,h,m,s,g,u,d. ", "response": "boppy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: o,v,e,t. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: x,e,o,v,s,t,p. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,r. Absents letters: x,e,o,v,s,t,l,p. ", "response": "karzy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,r. Absents letters: x,e,o,v,s,t,l,p. ", "response": "rar", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: y,r,d. ", "response": "pests", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,r,y,p,d. ", "response": "pes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,l,p,d. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,z,k,l,p,d. ", "response": "sake", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,o,h,s. ", "response": "rorie", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,e. Absents letters: i,b,h,m,o,s,l. ", "response": "tony", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,y,e. Absents letters: i,b,h,c,m,o,s,t,l. ", "response": "premy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,y,e. Absents letters: i,r,c,b,h,m,o,s,t,l. ", "response": "patte", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: j,o,d. ", "response": "leish", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: o,r,j,a,h,d. ", "response": "elves", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: r,y,n,j,h,o,g,a,d. ", "response": "tiled", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,i,e. Absents letters: y,r,n,j,h,o,g,a,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: o,c,h,n. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: y,n,c,h,o,a,f. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,y,n,c,h,k,o,a,l,f,d. ", "response": "sices", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,c,h,k,f,o,l,a,d. ", "response": "seers", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,m,l. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,t. Absents letters: i,m,r,l,c,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,t. Absents letters: i,r,c,k,m,s,l,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,t. Absents letters: i,r,c,k,m,s,l,a,d. ", "response": "tos", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,s,r,l,a. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,s,r,l,a. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,r,k,s,t,l,a. ", "response": "flock", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,r,n,h,w,k,s,t,l,a. ", "response": "boing", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: c,r,e,t. ", "response": "dices", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n. Absents letters: a,r,e,t,c,d. ", "response": "kains", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n. Absents letters: r,e,z,c,k,o,t,a,d. ", "response": "vines", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n. Absents letters: r,e,z,c,b,k,o,t,a,d. ", "response": "gin", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: l,r,u,g. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: r,e,c,g,l,t,u. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,y,s. Absents letters: r,e,g,l,t,c,u,d. ", "response": "sma", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,s,y. Absents letters: r,e,c,g,t,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "enarm", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,s,g,n. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,s,g,n,l. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,n,w,s,o,v,g,l. ", "response": "mazed", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,n,w,s,o,v,g,l,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: y,r,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,r,y,p,a,d. ", "response": "shute", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,s,t,p,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,s,t,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: p,b,y,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: s,y,l,p,b,w,u. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: y,b,w,s,g,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "nork", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,o. Absents letters: i,y,e,b,w,s,g,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "kob", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,o,b. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: m,o,a,l,p,b. ", "response": "gou", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: j,b,m,o,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: y,j,b,w,m,o,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "nix", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: d,g,r,n. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t,s,l. Absents letters: r,n,g,u,d. ", "response": "tils", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,l,t. Absents letters: r,y,n,e,g,u,d. ", "response": "til", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,t,l. Absents letters: y,r,e,n,g,f,u,d. ", "response": "lis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,t. Absents letters: s,z. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,t. Absents letters: s,o,e,z,l,c. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,t,a. Absents letters: s,o,y,e,z,l,c,d. ", "response": "titar", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,t,a. Absents letters: y,e,z,c,s,o,l,p,d. ", "response": "tug", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: t,s,h,n. ", "response": "aboma", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: e,n,c,h,s,t,p. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,e,n,c,h,s,t,p,u. ", "response": "karzy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,r. Absents letters: i,e,n,c,h,w,m,s,t,p,u. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,h. Absents letters: c,y. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,h,n. Absents letters: o,y,r,e,b,c. ", "response": "shuns", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n,a,h. Absents letters: k,m,o,r,y,e,c,b. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n,a,h. Absents letters: y,r,e,j,c,b,k,m,o,p. ", "response": "sna", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: c,a,n. ", "response": "gourd", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s. Absents letters: r,n,c,a,u. ", "response": "spill", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s. Absents letters: i,a,r,n,c,u,d. ", "response": "bops", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,k,m,a,u,d. ", "response": "bumps", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,y,h,w,d. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: y,h,w,m,o,s,u,d. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: y,h,w,m,o,s,u,d. ", "response": "pieta", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n,t. Absents letters: y,h,w,m,o,s,l,u,d. ", "response": "tanga", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,b,y,d. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: k,s,y,l,b,d. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: y,r,b,k,s,o,v,l,u,d. ", "response": "pecke", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: r,y,b,w,k,s,o,v,l,u,d. ", "response": "pee", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,s,v,o,n. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,d. Absents letters: i,s,v,o,y,n,l,u. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,d. Absents letters: i,y,n,s,v,o,l,u. ", "response": "adios", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,d. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,m,s,v,o,l,u. ", "response": "wax", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: t,s,n. ", "response": "bed", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: w,e,d. Absents letters: s,r,n,t,f. ", "response": "wared", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,a,w,d. Absents letters: s,r,n,t,b,f. ", "response": "awed", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,a,w,d. Absents letters: r,n,b,s,v,t,f. ", "response": "awed", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c. Absents letters: s,a,y,u. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,i,c. Absents letters: s,y,a,u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,c,i. Absents letters: y,b,m,s,o,a,u. ", "response": "tic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,i,c. Absents letters: y,b,h,m,o,s,t,a,u. ", "response": "cline", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,s,b,e. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: r,e,b,w,s,o,l. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: r,e,b,w,s,o,v,l,u. ", "response": "taff", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: r,e,b,c,w,k,m,s,o,v,l,u. ", "response": "pieta", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: w,d. Absents letters: i,a,n. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,w,d. Absents letters: i,r,n,p,a,u. ", "response": "boaw", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,w,d. Absents letters: i,s,r,n,p,b,a,u. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,w,e,d. Absents letters: i,r,n,b,k,s,p,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,m,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: m,l,f,h,u,d. ", "response": "bise", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: h,m,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: r,b,h,m,t,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "sises", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,o,b. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: m,o,a,y,l,b. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: y,b,h,m,o,v,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t. Absents letters: y,b,h,m,o,v,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: b,r,u,t. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: r,b,o,v,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "shme", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,e. Absents letters: r,b,o,v,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "gry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,e. Absents letters: r,b,f,o,v,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "bic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,l,v,g. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,n,w,v,g,l. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,w,v,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,w,f,v,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "shme", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: s,t. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,k,s,r,t. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: i,k,s,r,t,p,u. ", "response": "abode", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: i,r,c,k,s,t,p,u. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d. Absents letters: i,g,y,n. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,d. Absents letters: i,s,g,y,n,p,a. ", "response": "bled", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,d. Absents letters: i,y,n,b,w,s,g,p,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,v,e,l,d. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,b,w,s,g,p,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: f,n. ", "response": "skugs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c,u. Absents letters: o,n,l,f. ", "response": "screw", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c,u,d. Absents letters: o,a,e,n,l,f. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t,c,u,d. Absents letters: o,a,e,n,l,f. ", "response": "cud", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,g,y,n,a. ", "response": "fad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: y,e,n,k,s,g,a. ", "response": "hunk", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: y,e,n,k,m,s,g,a. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,u. Absents letters: y,e,n,r,k,m,s,v,g,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,g. Absents letters: i,l,n. ", "response": "teg", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,g. Absents letters: i,y,n,l,t. ", "response": "bugs", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e,g. Absents letters: i,v,y,n,l,t. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,g,a. Absents letters: i,y,n,o,v,t,l,f,d. ", "response": "warre", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,o,r,e,f. ", "response": "biffs", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,r,e,h,m,o,a,g,f. ", "response": "biff", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,r,e,n,h,f,m,o,g,a,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,r,e,n,h,m,o,a,v,g,f,d. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,g,r,n,a. ", "response": "sarks", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: m,o,g,r,n,a,h. ", "response": "kiers", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: r,n,h,m,o,g,t,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e. Absents letters: r,n,h,m,o,p,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: t,s,d,n. ", "response": "bide", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,c. Absents letters: m,s,o,n,t,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,c. Absents letters: e,n,w,m,s,o,t,l,d. ", "response": "biff", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,c,r. Absents letters: y,e,n,w,m,s,o,t,l,d. ", "response": "cared", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: i,s,u,d. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: i,h,s,o,a,u,d. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: i,h,s,o,a,u,d. ", "response": "enact", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: i,b,h,m,s,o,a,u,d. ", "response": "tifts", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,o,r,j,a. ", "response": "stile", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: i,o,s,r,j,a,h. ", "response": "enarm", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n. Absents letters: i,r,j,h,o,s,p,a,d. ", "response": "ennog", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n. Absents letters: i,r,y,j,h,o,s,p,a,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: p,o,q,h. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: q,r,n,h,w,o,p. ", "response": "sewen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,d. Absents letters: o,q,r,n,p,c,h,w. ", "response": "dikes", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,d. Absents letters: q,r,n,c,h,w,m,o,p,a. ", "response": "deism", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,p,t. ", "response": "shirk", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,s,o,t,p,h. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,h,s,o,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "reef", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: i,n,h,k,s,o,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "arvee", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,o,e,d. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,w,n. Absents letters: o,y,e,l,f,d. ", "response": "warns", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,w,n. Absents letters: y,e,k,o,s,l,f,d. ", "response": "warns", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,w,n. Absents letters: y,e,k,o,s,l,p,f,d. ", "response": "warns", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: j,r,g. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: s,r,e,g,l,j. ", "response": "kh", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: r,e,y,j,s,o,g,l. ", "response": "bia", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: y,r,e,j,b,k,s,o,g,l. ", "response": "niz", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: w,e,t. ", "response": "gals", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: y,e,r,c,w,t,d. ", "response": "loof", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,l. Absents letters: a,r,y,e,t,c,w,d. ", "response": "slily", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,l. Absents letters: y,r,e,c,w,t,a,d. ", "response": "slily", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: b,h,u. ", "response": "stil", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: m,o,b,h,u. ", "response": "slur", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: y,b,h,m,o,g,u. ", "response": "seals", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: y,b,h,c,m,o,g,u,d. ", "response": "slush", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: w,y,r,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: r,y,e,p,w,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: y,r,e,b,w,t,p,u,d. ", "response": "boaks", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: r,y,e,b,w,f,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,s,f,y. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: s,v,y,l,f,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,q,y,s,v,a,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "bonie", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,q,y,c,f,m,s,v,o,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u. Absents letters: s,f. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,a,r,u. Absents letters: s,e,f,d. ", "response": "paras", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,p,a,u. Absents letters: s,e,l,f,d. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,p,a,u. Absents letters: e,m,s,l,f,d. ", "response": "porad", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: s,o,h,u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: i,h,s,o,t,f,u. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,r,e. Absents letters: i,b,h,s,o,t,f,u,d. ", "response": "ruler", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,l. Absents letters: i,b,h,c,s,o,a,t,f,u,d. ", "response": "bry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d,n. Absents letters: w,o,r. ", "response": "dial", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,d. Absents letters: o,s,r,e,a,w. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d,n. Absents letters: i,r,e,w,o,s,t,p,a. ", "response": "gid", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,d. Absents letters: i,r,e,w,o,s,g,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: p,y,t. ", "response": "boke", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,c. Absents letters: m,s,y,t,p,b. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,c,r. Absents letters: y,e,b,m,s,t,p,a. ", "response": "rogu", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,n,c. Absents letters: y,e,b,m,s,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "porns", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,g,n,u,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: n,m,o,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "biff", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: n,c,m,o,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "seifs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,y,n,c,h,f,m,o,s,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b. Absents letters: k,o,c. ", "response": "blats", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b,a. Absents letters: k,m,o,y,l,c. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b,a. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,n,c,k,m,o,l. ", "response": "boons", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,b,h. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,r,c,k,m,o,l. ", "response": "abush", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: a,e,t. ", "response": "skugs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: y,e,t,n,a,h. ", "response": "guss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: y,e,n,r,h,m,v,t,a,u. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,s,o. Absents letters: i,r,y,e,n,h,m,v,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "bock", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: i,s,f,l. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,s,l,p,f. ", "response": "reef", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,w,s,a,t,l,p,f. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,r,e. Absents letters: i,w,f,s,v,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: o,w,s. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: o,s,w,d. ", "response": "elope", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: r,w,m,o,s,a,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: r,j,w,m,o,s,a,d. ", "response": "elope", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: o,b,r,s. ", "response": "envo", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: r,b,o,s,u,d. ", "response": "pieta", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,n. Absents letters: r,e,b,m,o,s,l,u,d. ", "response": "nix", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,n. Absents letters: r,e,b,m,o,s,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: p,a,h,y. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: f,e. Absents letters: k,s,y,n,p,a,h. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,l,f. Absents letters: y,r,n,h,k,s,p,a. ", "response": "flier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,f,e,l. Absents letters: r,y,n,j,h,k,s,t,p,a,u. ", "response": "flier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,y,e,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: y,e,r,l,a,d. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: r,y,e,l,n,a,d. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: y,r,e,n,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: s,d. ", "response": "rifle", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: s,q,a,u,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: q,h,s,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "siler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: q,e,n,h,k,s,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,d. Absents letters: i,g. ", "response": "tared", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,r,e,d. Absents letters: i,y,g,w. ", "response": "loo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,l,d. Absents letters: i,y,c,w,k,s,g. ", "response": "bride", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,l,u,d. Absents letters: i,y,c,h,w,k,s,g. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,a,n,c,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,a,n,l,b,c,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t. Absents letters: i,n,c,b,m,o,l,a,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t. Absents letters: i,n,b,c,m,o,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "setes", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: a,c,h,t. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,s. Absents letters: i,f,a,n,t,c,h. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,e. Absents letters: i,n,c,h,a,t,f. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,h,k,a,t,f. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n. Absents letters: b,u,e. ", "response": "maron", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,n. Absents letters: m,s,e,b,u. ", "response": "boans", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,n. Absents letters: r,e,b,m,s,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n,a. Absents letters: i,m,s,r,e,c,b,u. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n. Absents letters: s,w,t. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n. Absents letters: m,s,e,t,c,w,u. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,g,n. Absents letters: e,c,w,m,s,t,a,u. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n,g. Absents letters: e,c,h,w,m,s,t,a,u. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: f,a,b,r. ", "response": "stogy", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,e,b,f,o,l,a. ", "response": "sarks", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,e,b,o,a,l,f,d. ", "response": "sis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,u. Absents letters: r,e,b,f,o,t,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "shme", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: m,n. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,m,t,y,n,p. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,g. Absents letters: i,y,n,m,t,p,u,d. ", "response": "geg", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,g. Absents letters: i,y,n,c,h,k,m,t,p,u,d. ", "response": "gose", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,o,x,e,t. ", "response": "yar", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,s,o,x,e,t,y,d. ", "response": "karzy", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,x,e,y,s,o,t,d. ", "response": "warre", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,y,x,e,s,o,t,l,d. ", "response": "karri", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,d,f,t. ", "response": "shake", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,e. Absents letters: i,o,t,p,f,d. ", "response": "ked", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,e. Absents letters: i,c,o,a,t,l,p,f,d. ", "response": "deked", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,m,s,e. Absents letters: i,c,f,o,t,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "kms", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,a. Absents letters: i,n. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,l,a. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,c. ", "response": "galvo", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,l,a. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,x,c,w. ", "response": "galas", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,l,a,d. Absents letters: i,x,y,e,n,c,w,p,u. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: c,y,t. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: i,o,y,t,j,c. ", "response": "bries", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,a. Absents letters: i,o,y,t,l,j,c. ", "response": "rexes", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,a. Absents letters: i,y,j,c,o,t,l,p. ", "response": "sares", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: m,s,g. ", "response": "fad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: m,s,o,g,l,t. ", "response": "nark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: m,s,o,e,g,l,t,f. ", "response": "maril", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: e,n,w,m,s,o,g,l,t,f. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: h,w,e,n. ", "response": "titch", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,y. Absents letters: o,e,n,t,h,w. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,a,r. Absents letters: i,e,n,h,w,o,v,g,t. ", "response": "bayer", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,a,y. Absents letters: i,e,n,h,w,m,o,v,g,l,t,u. ", "response": "bray", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: a,n. ", "response": "syt", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: k,o,n,a. ", "response": "sht", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t. Absents letters: k,o,r,n,c,a,h. ", "response": "sket", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t. Absents letters: r,n,c,h,k,o,a,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: p,o,y. ", "response": "slugs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,e. Absents letters: o,y,r,g,p. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,e. Absents letters: o,r,y,g,n,p,a. ", "response": "bls", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,e. Absents letters: y,r,n,f,o,g,p,a,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,g,n,f,u. ", "response": "titch", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: s,g,n,b,f,w,u. ", "response": "aboh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,d. Absents letters: r,e,n,b,w,s,g,f,u. ", "response": "loid", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,d. Absents letters: r,e,n,b,w,s,v,g,f,u. ", "response": "loid", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: k,s,t. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: k,s,v,r,t,u. ", "response": "wax", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,e. Absents letters: r,c,k,s,v,o,t,u,d. ", "response": "leaze", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,e. Absents letters: r,c,h,k,s,v,o,t,f,u,d. ", "response": "leaze", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,x. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,x,l,b,c,u. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,x,b,c,o,g,t,l,u. ", "response": "sared", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,e,a. Absents letters: i,x,c,b,k,o,g,l,t,u. ", "response": "seyen", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,b,y,l. ", "response": "bices", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: i,y,b,l,d. ", "response": "ters", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h,r. Absents letters: i,k,y,l,b,w,d. ", "response": "shots", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,a,h. Absents letters: i,k,y,l,b,w,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: b,y,g. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: a,y,g,b,u,d. ", "response": "seels", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,s,o,e. Absents letters: y,x,b,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,e,c. Absents letters: x,y,b,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "tices", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: r,e,n. ", "response": "aguti", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,m,r,e,n,l,f. ", "response": "wadd", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,g,a. Absents letters: i,m,r,e,n,l,t,f. ", "response": "gapes", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,g,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,m,v,t,l,f. ", "response": "gapes", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n. Absents letters: p,x. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n. Absents letters: i,o,x,r,p,h. ", "response": "ennog", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n. Absents letters: i,x,r,y,e,h,w,o,p. ", "response": "panax", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,n. Absents letters: i,y,x,e,r,h,w,o,s,p. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,d,a,n. ", "response": "shute", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,x,n,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "gaff", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,x,n,z,f,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "shake", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,x,z,n,w,a,l,p,f,d. ", "response": "ber", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: f,u,g. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,l. Absents letters: o,a,g,f,u. ", "response": "slirl", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,r. Absents letters: f,k,o,g,a,u. ", "response": "sewel", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,l. Absents letters: k,f,o,g,a,u. ", "response": "seh", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: l,n. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,t. Absents letters: l,o,h,n. ", "response": "skets", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,t. Absents letters: i,o,n,l,p,h,d. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,t. Absents letters: i,y,n,b,h,o,l,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,o,r,p,u. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: r,c,m,o,p,u,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: r,c,m,o,s,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: r,c,h,w,m,o,s,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: v,e. Absents letters: l,s,a. ", "response": "vinal", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: v,e. Absents letters: s,o,g,l,a. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: v,e. Absents letters: i,c,h,m,s,o,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "vex", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: v,u,e. Absents letters: i,c,h,m,s,o,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: p,r,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,a. Absents letters: r,p,c,h,d. ", "response": "limax", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,n,a. Absents letters: s,r,p,c,h,u,d. ", "response": "limax", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,n,a. Absents letters: r,c,h,k,s,p,u,d. ", "response": "limax", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: o,h,w,t. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: o,y,t,l,b,h,w. ", "response": "nares", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: y,j,b,h,w,o,t,l. ", "response": "bries", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: y,n,j,b,h,w,o,t,l,u,d. ", "response": "saris", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: f,w,e,t. ", "response": "hunk", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: e,t,l,j,f,w,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: e,j,w,a,t,l,f,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: i,q,e,j,w,f,t,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "golds", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: v,r,e. ", "response": "bh", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: v,r,e,y,p. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,v,g,p,u. ", "response": "alib", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,k,s,v,g,p,u. ", "response": "galvo", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,b. Absents letters: n. ", "response": "boiers", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,b. Absents letters: i,p,f,n. ", "response": "boaks", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t,s,o,b. Absents letters: i,e,n,h,w,p,f. ", "response": "boaks", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,t,b. Absents letters: i,e,n,h,w,a,g,p,f,u. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: b,e,d. ", "response": "porns", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,s. Absents letters: k,f,e,b,d. ", "response": "boors", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u,r,s. Absents letters: i,e,n,b,k,a,f,d. ", "response": "tus", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,r,u. Absents letters: i,e,n,b,k,f,p,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,v,y,e,w. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,y,e,c,w,k,o,v. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b. Absents letters: i,y,e,c,w,k,m,o,v,a. ", "response": "slubs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b,u. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,c,w,k,m,o,v,a,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: t,o,p,n. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,e. Absents letters: m,o,t,r,n,p. ", "response": "bared", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,y,e. Absents letters: r,n,c,h,k,m,o,t,p. ", "response": "b b", "reward": -13.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,y,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,z,c,h,k,m,o,t,p,a. ", "response": "bun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,a,g,n. ", "response": "skull", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,n,h,g,l,a,d. ", "response": "fests", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s. Absents letters: i,y,n,h,m,g,l,a,d. ", "response": "bump", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,e. Absents letters: i,y,n,z,h,m,g,l,a,d. ", "response": "spine", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: p,v,r,e. ", "response": "bh", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: v,t,r,e,y,p. ", "response": "abode", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: y,r,e,m,v,t,p. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,n. Absents letters: r,y,e,m,v,t,p,d. ", "response": "boans", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: v,b,r. ", "response": "pests", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: a,v,r,n,l,b. ", "response": "tices", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: r,n,b,v,l,a,u. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: r,n,b,f,o,v,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: k,y,c,u,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n. Absents letters: k,i,y,e,t,c,u,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,n. Absents letters: i,y,e,c,h,k,o,t,u,d. ", "response": "nans", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,n. Absents letters: i,y,e,c,h,b,k,o,t,u,d. ", "response": "sango", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: p,e,t. ", "response": "boors", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,f,s. Absents letters: k,e,t,p. ", "response": "lofs", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,l,f. Absents letters: k,i,e,t,p,c,h. ", "response": "loof", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,l,f. Absents letters: i,e,c,h,k,t,p,a. ", "response": "loof", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,b,y,t. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c. Absents letters: y,e,b,h,o,s,t,u. ", "response": "clung", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,c,g. Absents letters: y,e,b,h,o,s,t,u. ", "response": "clung", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,g,l,c. Absents letters: y,e,b,h,m,o,s,t,u,d. ", "response": "gil", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: d,f,r,n. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,c,e. Absents letters: a,r,n,l,f,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,c,e. Absents letters: r,n,f,m,l,a,d. ", "response": "cog", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,e,c. Absents letters: r,n,m,a,l,f,d. ", "response": "citer", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: o,b,w,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,r,b,w,m,o,g,d. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,r,b,w,m,o,s,g,u,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,r,b,w,m,o,s,g,u,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: a,f,y,e. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,r. Absents letters: i,m,a,y,e,f. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,r. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,f,m,g,a. ", "response": "proll", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,p. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,m,a,g,t,f,u. ", "response": "sppy", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: i,l,a,g. ", "response": "nork", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: i,s,p,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "nork", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,r,e. Absents letters: i,y,s,p,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "bared", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,r,e. Absents letters: i,y,x,m,s,t,o,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "bared", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: s,e,z. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: s,g,e,z,l,a,h. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: r,e,z,b,h,m,s,g,l,a. ", "response": "tik", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: r,e,z,b,h,m,s,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,s,b,k. ", "response": "niche", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,y,b,k,s,a,d. ", "response": "sext", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,y,b,h,k,s,v,a,d. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,y,x,n,b,h,k,s,v,g,a,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: k,j,a. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: k,m,s,z,j,a. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: z,n,j,k,m,s,f,g,a. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: n,z,j,k,m,s,a,g,t,f. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: w,c,r,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,g. Absents letters: r,n,c,w,l,a,d. ", "response": "gog", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,g. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,w,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "gou", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,g. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,w,k,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "gou", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: e,g. ", "response": "saris", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: e,g,l,n,a. ", "response": "fuss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: e,n,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: i,e,n,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: m,o,s,t. ", "response": "bume", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: e,m,o,s,t,l,f. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u. Absents letters: r,e,m,o,s,v,t,l,f. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u. Absents letters: r,e,m,o,s,v,t,l,f. ", "response": "boaw", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d. Absents letters: a,c,r,e. ", "response": "bidet", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u,d. Absents letters: a,v,r,e,g,c,h. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,u,d. Absents letters: i,r,e,y,c,h,v,g,t,a. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,p,u,d. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,c,h,v,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "spud", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: k,o,r,s. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: r,k,o,s,g,l. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: r,n,w,k,o,s,g,l,u. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y. Absents letters: r,e,n,w,k,o,s,g,l,u. ", "response": "pyran", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: m,t. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,e,d. Absents letters: i,m,o,r,t. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n,l,d. Absents letters: i,m,o,s,r,t,w. ", "response": "dung", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,d,e,n. Absents letters: i,r,w,m,o,s,t,p,a,u. ", "response": "nix", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: a,r,g. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b. Absents letters: m,r,g,j,a. ", "response": "boobs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b. Absents letters: i,r,j,k,m,g,a,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b. Absents letters: i,r,y,n,j,k,m,o,g,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "bices", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: f,y,e. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: v,y,e,p,f. ", "response": "roopy", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: k,m,v,y,e,p,f. ", "response": "tic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,r. Absents letters: y,e,k,m,v,p,f. ", "response": "shirk", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t,n. Absents letters: o,g. ", "response": "tinas", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n,t. Absents letters: o,r,e,g,a. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t,n. Absents letters: r,e,h,w,o,g,p,a. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n,t. Absents letters: r,e,z,h,w,o,g,p,a. ", "response": "bling", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e. Absents letters: b,r,g. ", "response": "boche", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e. Absents letters: s,r,g,l,b. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e. Absents letters: s,a,r,g,l,b,h. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,c,e. Absents letters: r,b,h,s,g,l,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d. Absents letters: m,b,u,e. ", "response": "pong", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y,d. Absents letters: m,e,c,p,b,u. ", "response": "ady", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y,d. Absents letters: m,o,p,e,c,b,u. ", "response": "dray", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y,d. Absents letters: i,e,b,c,m,o,p,u. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,s,o,u. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: n,m,s,o,t,u,d. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,e. Absents letters: n,m,s,o,t,u,d. ", "response": "pee", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,p,e. Absents letters: i,n,m,s,o,t,u,d. ", "response": "leep", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: m,e,d. ", "response": "trows", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,r. Absents letters: m,s,e,a,w,d. ", "response": "boomy", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,r. Absents letters: e,w,m,s,l,a,d. ", "response": "boomy", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,b,r. Absents letters: e,w,m,s,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "boche", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: e,b,u,t. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,e,b,w,m,s,t,a,u. ", "response": "boing", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,e,b,w,m,s,t,a,u. ", "response": "boomy", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,e,b,w,f,m,s,t,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,a. Absents letters: v,r. ", "response": "kalis", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,a,o. Absents letters: m,v,r,c,h,u. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,o,a. Absents letters: r,c,h,m,v,t,l,u. ", "response": "oj", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,o,a. Absents letters: r,y,c,h,m,v,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,m,a,u. ", "response": "mia", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,n,c,m,l,a,u. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,n,c,h,k,m,l,a,u. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,n,c,h,w,k,m,s,l,a,u. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: a,t,l,p,c. ", "response": "shirk", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: i,a,t,l,p,c. ", "response": "rogu", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: i,c,h,t,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e. Absents letters: i,c,h,b,t,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "bores", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: i,b,t. ", "response": "aboma", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,s. Absents letters: i,t,c,b,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,s. Absents letters: i,e,c,b,h,g,t,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,a. Absents letters: i,y,e,b,c,h,k,g,t,u,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: c,h,e,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,m,f,e,c,h,d. ", "response": "agars", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,m,f,e,c,h,d. ", "response": "karri", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,e,c,h,m,g,t,f,d. ", "response": "marra", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,r. Absents letters: i,a,u. ", "response": "peres", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,p,d. Absents letters: i,a,u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e,p,d. Absents letters: i,m,s,a,u. ", "response": "loipe", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e,p,d. Absents letters: i,n,m,s,t,a,u. ", "response": "dork", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,a,r,e,b. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,d. Absents letters: s,a,r,e,n,b,h. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,d. Absents letters: r,e,n,b,h,c,s,g,a. ", "response": "loid", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,d. Absents letters: r,e,n,b,h,c,m,s,g,a. ", "response": "loid", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,q,u. ", "response": "bling", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: i,k,q,t,a,u. ", "response": "loof", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,l. Absents letters: i,k,q,t,p,a,u. ", "response": "gor", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,r,e,l. Absents letters: i,q,w,k,t,p,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d. Absents letters: s,a,r,g. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,r,h,s,g,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,e,d. Absents letters: i,r,h,k,s,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "bidet", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,e,d. Absents letters: i,r,n,j,h,k,s,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "dyed", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: y,v,r,e. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: v,r,y,e,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,r,e,c,v,g,d. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,a. Absents letters: r,y,e,c,v,g,t,d. ", "response": "boals", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: m,o,w. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s. Absents letters: m,o,e,c,w,d. ", "response": "skags", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s. Absents letters: e,c,h,w,m,o,l,d. ", "response": "kests", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,t,a. Absents letters: e,n,c,h,w,m,o,g,l,d. ", "response": "tkes", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: a,o,b,t. ", "response": "bise", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: x,y,b,o,s,t,a. ", "response": "royst", "reward": -6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u. Absents letters: y,x,b,o,s,t,a,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u,n. Absents letters: x,y,e,b,o,s,g,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "maron", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b. Absents letters: j,a,h,e. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b. Absents letters: i,e,j,c,h,a. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,j,c,h,g,a. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,b,d. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,j,c,h,w,s,g,a. ", "response": "boody", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,d. Absents letters: a. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,d. Absents letters: o,v,r,t,a. ", "response": "sured", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,d. Absents letters: o,v,r,y,t,l,n,a. ", "response": "gled", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,d. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,c,o,v,t,l,a. ", "response": "dices", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c. Absents letters: l,p,e. ", "response": "batch", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c. Absents letters: e,n,l,p. ", "response": "scots", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c. Absents letters: i,e,n,w,k,l,p. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c. Absents letters: i,e,n,h,w,k,t,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "cask", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: b,r,u,n. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: i,r,n,b,u. ", "response": "fests", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,t. Absents letters: i,k,m,r,n,b,u. ", "response": "gales", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t,a,h. Absents letters: i,r,y,n,b,k,m,u. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: p,o,h,n. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,e. Absents letters: r,y,n,h,o,t,p. ", "response": "bared", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,e. Absents letters: y,r,n,h,o,v,t,p. ", "response": "bells", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,e. Absents letters: i,r,y,n,z,h,o,v,t,p. ", "response": "bared", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,m,a. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,m,f,r,a. ", "response": "loid", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,m,a,r,y,l,j,f. ", "response": "deism", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,p,d. Absents letters: i,y,r,j,f,m,o,l,a. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: p,a,d. ", "response": "loof", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: v,g,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,n. Absents letters: e,h,f,v,g,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,n. Absents letters: r,e,c,h,a,v,g,l,p,f,d. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: k,r,e. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: k,i,m,r,e,h. ", "response": "pales", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,a. Absents letters: i,k,m,r,e,t,h. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,p,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,j,c,h,k,m,t. ", "response": "sne", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,v,r,l. ", "response": "fests", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,v,r,t,l,f,w. ", "response": "sake", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,r,y,w,k,v,t,l,f. ", "response": "boke", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,w,k,v,t,l,f,d. ", "response": "gales", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,p,e,n,t. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: e,n,m,t,p,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: i,e,n,m,v,t,p,d. ", "response": "slums", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,m,v,t,p,u,d. ", "response": "gals", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: h,r,u. ", "response": "stich", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: f,r,l,a,h,u. ", "response": "stinks", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: r,c,h,f,m,o,l,a,u. ", "response": "sties", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: r,c,h,m,o,a,v,l,f,u. ", "response": "sitar", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,m,b. ", "response": "galas", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,b,c,h,k,m,t,u. ", "response": "stol", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,n,c,b,h,k,m,g,t,p,u. ", "response": "halid", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,e. Absents letters: i,n,b,c,h,k,m,p,g,t,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u,t. Absents letters: k,y. ", "response": "suts", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u,t. Absents letters: k,i,y,l,a,h. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u,t. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,h,k,g,l,a. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u,t. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,h,w,k,o,g,l,a. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: k,s,y,e,t. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,y,e,r,k,m,s,g,t. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,k,m,s,g,t,f. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,n. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,k,m,s,g,t,f,d. ", "response": "uncap", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,a,w,n. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: k,r,n,l,a,w. ", "response": "sists", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: k,o,r,n,l,a,w. ", "response": "sitar", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: r,n,w,k,m,o,l,p,a. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,r,u,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,y,e,m,u,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: i,m,y,r,e,u,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,t. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,w,m,l,u,d. ", "response": "sated", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,a,l,f,w. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,e. Absents letters: s,a,v,l,f,w. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,c,e. Absents letters: y,r,w,f,s,v,t,l,a. ", "response": "coc", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,c. Absents letters: r,y,w,s,v,a,t,l,p,f. ", "response": "cep", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,a,r,l,c. ", "response": "shirk", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: r,c,o,s,l,a. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,n. Absents letters: r,c,o,s,t,l,a. ", "response": "deman", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e,n. Absents letters: r,c,o,s,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "mezen", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r. Absents letters: b,t. ", "response": "ars", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r. Absents letters: g,e,t,b,w,d. ", "response": "ars", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,c,a. Absents letters: i,p,e,g,t,b,w,d. ", "response": "boors", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r,c. Absents letters: i,e,b,w,o,g,t,l,p,d. ", "response": "arced", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,t. Absents letters: i,b,r. ", "response": "throb", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,e,t. Absents letters: i,k,m,s,a,r,b. ", "response": "heath", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,e,t. Absents letters: i,r,y,b,k,m,s,a. ", "response": "heath", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,e,t. Absents letters: i,y,r,b,k,m,s,o,a. ", "response": "heath", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: l,s,u,e. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: e,k,m,s,l,u,d. ", "response": "envo", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: e,z,k,m,s,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "tic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,c. Absents letters: r,e,z,k,m,s,t,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "citer", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: k,s,w. ", "response": "nappa", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: k,s,r,l,w. ", "response": "tich", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: k,s,r,l,w,d. ", "response": "agami", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: r,e,w,k,s,t,l,d. ", "response": "agria", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: h,w,d. ", "response": "pians", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,g,b. Absents letters: h,w,d. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,g,b. Absents letters: m,y,e,n,h,w,d. ", "response": "boog", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,r,g,b. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,h,w,m,d. ", "response": "boart", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: l,w,t. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: r,t,l,w. ", "response": "sices", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: r,b,w,m,t,l,u,d. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,r,z,n,b,w,m,t,l,u,d. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,c,r,e. Absents letters: s. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e,c. Absents letters: s,o,v,n. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e,c. Absents letters: s,o,v,n,h. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e,c. Absents letters: k,s,o,v,n,b,h,u. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: o,h. ", "response": "skets", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: o,r,n,c,h. ", "response": "sitar", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,t. Absents letters: o,a,r,n,p,c,h. ", "response": "sist", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,t. Absents letters: r,n,c,h,w,f,o,p,a. ", "response": "sist", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,f,r,n. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,h,f,d. ", "response": "wadd", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,h,o,t,f,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,h,w,o,t,f,d. ", "response": "sma", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: s,v,e. ", "response": "fad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,s,v,r,e,n,d. ", "response": "wadd", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,s,v,d. ", "response": "aboma", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,s,v,p,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,p. Absents letters: t,u,n. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,l,p,a. Absents letters: n,t,u. ", "response": "lax", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,l,p,a. Absents letters: z,r,n,t,u. ", "response": "palet", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,l,p,a. Absents letters: s,z,r,n,t,h,u. ", "response": "pile", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: j,c,t. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: v,r,t,j,c. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: r,y,j,c,w,v,g,t,a. ", "response": "teg", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: y,r,n,j,c,w,o,v,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "sieve", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: m,e,t. ", "response": "skull", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: m,o,z,r,e,t. ", "response": "skugs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: r,e,z,x,m,o,t. ", "response": "skugs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,u. Absents letters: x,r,z,e,m,o,g,t. ", "response": "sau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,p,s. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,s,o,g,r,t,p. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,r,b,s,o,g,t,p. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,r,y,b,s,o,p,g,l,t. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: a,u,e,t. ", "response": "skull", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,e,n,t,a,u. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,j,t,a,u. ", "response": "skull", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,j,t,p,a,u. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: m,s,u. ", "response": "bride", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: m,s,o,r,p,u. ", "response": "tiled", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,e,d. Absents letters: r,c,m,s,o,p,a,u. ", "response": "dek", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d,e,n. Absents letters: r,c,w,m,o,s,p,a,u. ", "response": "enew", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: h,u,e,t. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: e,n,h,o,v,t,u. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: e,n,h,o,v,t,u. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: e,n,c,h,o,v,t,u. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,o,y,r,g. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,y,e,c,m,o,s,g,a. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: y,r,e,c,h,w,m,o,s,g,t,a. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,u. Absents letters: r,y,e,c,h,w,m,o,s,g,t,a. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: a,g,z. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: i,g,z,a,h,w. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,s. Absents letters: i,z,h,w,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,r,e. Absents letters: i,z,h,w,m,v,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "roops", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: m,s,r,t. ", "response": "nappa", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: k,m,s,r,t,c. ", "response": "nark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: r,y,c,k,m,s,t,f,u. ", "response": "galah", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: y,r,n,c,k,m,s,t,f,u. ", "response": "pel", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,p,e,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,x,e,p,d. ", "response": "pals", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,x,e,p,c,d. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,a. Absents letters: i,x,e,c,t,p,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,i. Absents letters: o,n. ", "response": "slier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,i. Absents letters: m,o,r,e,n. ", "response": "siler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,l. Absents letters: m,o,r,e,n,p. ", "response": "tails", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,l. Absents letters: r,e,n,m,o,t,p,a. ", "response": "slily", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,c,h,y. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,y,c,h,t,l. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,y,j,c,h,m,t,l,a. ", "response": "seaze", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u,e. Absents letters: i,q,y,r,j,c,h,k,m,t,l,a. ", "response": "gus", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,v,e. ", "response": "fad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: s,v,e,n,l,h. ", "response": "boart", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: i,e,n,h,m,s,v,l. ", "response": "oared", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: i,e,n,c,h,m,s,v,l. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,n. Absents letters: b. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n,a. Absents letters: i,k,b,t. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d,s,a,n. Absents letters: i,b,h,k,o,g,t,u. ", "response": "nuts", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n,a,d. Absents letters: i,z,b,h,k,o,g,t,u. ", "response": "sna", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,t. Absents letters: i. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t,l. Absents letters: i,h. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,t. Absents letters: i,r,n,g,h,u. ", "response": "slant", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t,l. Absents letters: i,o,g,r,n,c,h,u. ", "response": "slane", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,t. Absents letters: p,r,e. ", "response": "boart", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,v,l,p,d. ", "response": "boht", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,x,n,v,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "stol", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,x,w,v,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,m. ", "response": "halos", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,m,o,s,b,d. ", "response": "plane", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,w. Absents letters: i,y,n,b,m,o,s,d. ", "response": "waraw", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,w. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,b,c,m,o,s,v,d. ", "response": "warre", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: a,g,t. ", "response": "bings", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: m,g,e,t,a,h. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: r,e,h,m,p,g,t,a. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,o. Absents letters: i,r,e,y,h,m,t,g,p,a. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: b,y,u,g. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,r,b,m,g,p,u. ", "response": "fad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: r,y,b,m,t,g,p,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: y,r,e,b,h,m,g,t,p,u,d. ", "response": "galas", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,a,r,t,f. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u. Absents letters: i,k,a,r,t,f. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,u. Absents letters: i,r,y,k,f,g,t,a. ", "response": "bode", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,s,u. Absents letters: i,y,r,k,a,p,g,l,t,f. ", "response": "bum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,a. Absents letters: h,e. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,g,l,a. Absents letters: e,b,h,u. ", "response": "glog", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n,g,l,a. Absents letters: k,e,b,h,u. ", "response": "galon", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,g,n,l,a. Absents letters: k,e,p,b,h,u. ", "response": "galvo", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,t,g,n. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e. Absents letters: i,x,n,c,g,t. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,s. Absents letters: i,g,x,n,l,t,c. ", "response": "bode", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,s. Absents letters: i,x,n,c,k,g,l,t. ", "response": "sox", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: l,p,t. ", "response": "sy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: e,t,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "boors", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,e,t,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,x,e,t,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: p,s,e. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: s,e,l,p,c,h. ", "response": "dik", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: r,e,c,h,b,s,l,p. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: r,e,b,c,h,s,l,p,d. ", "response": "bight", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,d. Absents letters: l,o,c. ", "response": "dh", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,d. Absents letters: k,o,y,x,l,c. ", "response": "dikes", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,d. Absents letters: y,x,r,c,h,k,o,l,a. ", "response": "sided", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,d. Absents letters: x,y,r,e,c,h,k,o,l,a. ", "response": "dj", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,a,i,t. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,r,e,h,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: i,r,e,y,h,g,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "skunk", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,u,n. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,h,g,l,t,a,d. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: l,s,c. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,n. Absents letters: s,l,c,u,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,n. Absents letters: i,e,c,s,t,l,u,d. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,n. Absents letters: i,e,c,h,s,t,l,u,d. ", "response": "porns", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,v,e,d. ", "response": "gim", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h. Absents letters: k,v,e,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "shy", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,h. Absents letters: e,k,v,g,t,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "shogs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,s,h. Absents letters: e,b,k,v,g,t,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "shms", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: k,s,r,e. ", "response": "tich", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: r,e,k,s,g,d. ", "response": "nark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: r,e,y,k,m,s,g,d. ", "response": "marls", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: y,r,e,c,h,k,m,s,o,g,d. ", "response": "galvo", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: k,a,r,u. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,c,h,k,o,t,a,u. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,y,c,h,k,o,t,a,u. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,h,k,m,o,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "seels", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: a,s,f,t. ", "response": "dyk", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,s,a,t,l,f,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,e,n. Absents letters: i,h,w,f,s,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,e,n. Absents letters: i,h,w,s,a,o,t,l,f,d. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,m,p. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: i,m,p. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,t. Absents letters: i,m,g,l,p. ", "response": "tares", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t,a,u. Absents letters: i,m,r,n,g,l,p. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: m,a,c,r. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,r,c,b,m,a. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n. Absents letters: i,m,a,r,c,b,h. ", "response": "pyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n. Absents letters: i,r,y,b,c,h,m,l,a. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: r,n,t. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: k,f,r,n,t,c. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: r,n,c,b,k,o,s,t,f. ", "response": "wax", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: r,n,b,c,k,o,s,v,g,t,f. ", "response": "wax", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: m,b,u,e. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y. Absents letters: m,e,n,t,b,u. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,g. Absents letters: i,e,n,b,m,t,l,u. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,g. Absents letters: i,e,n,b,c,m,t,l,u. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,o,n. ", "response": "reef", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,r,e. Absents letters: i,o,n,t,b. ", "response": "yares", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,y,e. Absents letters: i,n,b,c,o,t,l,p. ", "response": "saris", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,r,e. Absents letters: i,n,c,b,o,g,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "sy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,d,y,t. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: o,y,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: y,w,m,o,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,r,e. Absents letters: y,w,m,o,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: m,y. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,m,y,e,t,c. ", "response": "maron", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,m,y,e,t,c. ", "response": "parge", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,y,e,c,h,m,o,t,p. ", "response": "marls", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r. Absents letters: u. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,a. Absents letters: l,u,t. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r. Absents letters: e,g,t,l,u. ", "response": "ars", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,n,a. Absents letters: m,y,e,g,l,t,u. ", "response": "maron", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: d,f,n. ", "response": "sigh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: k,a,n,f,d. ", "response": "locks", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,o. Absents letters: k,a,n,l,f,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,o,b. Absents letters: e,n,k,f,m,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "boaks", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: l,e,g. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: s,e,g,l,t,w. ", "response": "kia", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: e,w,k,m,s,g,l,t. ", "response": "niz", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: e,w,k,m,s,g,l,t,u. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: p,s,o,t. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e,d. Absents letters: s,o,t,p,u. ", "response": "dared", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,a,d. Absents letters: i,s,o,q,t,p,u. ", "response": "cared", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,a,d. Absents letters: i,q,y,n,s,o,t,p,u. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d. Absents letters: i,y,t. ", "response": "dj", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,d. Absents letters: i,o,y,r,t,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u,d. Absents letters: i,y,r,f,o,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "skud", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u,d. Absents letters: i,y,r,o,a,t,l,p,f. ", "response": "dud", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: l,j,u. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: s,e,t,l,j,w,u. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,r. Absents letters: e,j,c,h,w,s,t,l,u. ", "response": "porad", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,r. Absents letters: i,e,j,c,h,w,s,t,l,u. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: b,u. ", "response": "pso", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: m,o,v,e,b,u. ", "response": "yirks", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,a,y. Absents letters: m,o,v,e,b,h,u. ", "response": "tray", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,r,a. Absents letters: e,b,h,m,o,v,t,u. ", "response": "bry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: m,h,y,e. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,h,m,l,a. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,u. Absents letters: i,q,y,e,n,h,m,g,l,a. ", "response": "bough", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,u. Absents letters: i,q,y,e,n,h,m,g,l,a,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: l,c,h,n. ", "response": "dices", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: v,r,n,l,c,h. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: v,r,n,l,c,h,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: r,y,n,c,h,v,l,a,d. ", "response": "siler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,k,s,a,u. ", "response": "sewel", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,r,e,k,s,g,a,u,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,r,e,k,s,g,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,r,e,b,k,s,g,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: i,e,g. ", "response": "saris", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: i,v,e,g,c. ", "response": "bards", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r. Absents letters: i,v,e,g,l,t,c,u. ", "response": "arris", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,y,p,a. Absents letters: i,e,c,h,v,g,l,t,u. ", "response": "sarks", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y. Absents letters: t,w,n. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y. Absents letters: r,n,t,a,w. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,y. Absents letters: r,n,t,a,h,w,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y,g,l. Absents letters: r,n,h,w,m,t,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d. Absents letters: i,f,u,l. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,a,v,r,l,f,u. ", "response": "deked", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,f,o,v,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "deked", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,r,y,n,c,o,v,a,s,t,l,f,u. ", "response": "defer", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,k,s,y,r. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,y,r,e,k,s,g,l,d. ", "response": "tich", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,n. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,b,k,s,o,g,l,d. ", "response": "bun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,n. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,b,k,s,o,g,l,p,d. ", "response": "nix", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: k,m,r,e,a. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,e,k,m,t,a. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,e,n,k,m,f,t,a. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: q,r,e,n,h,k,m,a,t,f,u. ", "response": "gos", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: l,p,a,e. ", "response": "gitch", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: e,c,s,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "twerp", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,t. Absents letters: e,n,j,c,s,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "tok", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,t. Absents letters: i,e,n,j,c,s,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "thaw", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,k,s,t,a. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,k,f,s,t,a. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,r,n,k,s,a,t,f,u,d. ", "response": "bonie", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,y,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,k,f,s,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "gyppy", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,t,h,g. ", "response": "slane", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,e,n,h,w,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,h,w,o,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "loof", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,h,w,o,p,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "slunk", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t,d. Absents letters: i,o,h. ", "response": "tiled", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,d,e,t. Absents letters: i,o,q,n,h,u. ", "response": "warre", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,t,a,d. Absents letters: i,q,n,b,h,o,u. ", "response": "dared", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,t,a,d. Absents letters: i,q,n,b,h,o,s,f,u. ", "response": "taded", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,s,w. ", "response": "rorie", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,t. Absents letters: s,r,l,w,d. ", "response": "enact", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,t. Absents letters: r,w,s,l,u,d. ", "response": "enact", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,t,n,a. Absents letters: i,r,w,m,s,g,l,u,d. ", "response": "tna", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,a,r,c,d. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n. Absents letters: i,a,r,t,c,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n. Absents letters: i,r,y,c,k,m,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,s,n. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,k,m,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,o,c,r. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: g. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,o,l,d. ", "response": "gum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: g. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,o,l,d. ", "response": "gou", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,g. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,o,t,l,d. ", "response": "gamin", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,p,s,e. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,m,s,e,n,p. ", "response": "dong", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,m,s,g,l,p,u. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,c. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,r,m,s,g,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "cob", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: m,a,r,n. ", "response": "shute", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,r,n,w,f,m,a,d. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,w,m,a,o,f,d. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,w,f,m,o,a,d. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: m,o,s,n. ", "response": "maril", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: k,m,o,s,n. ", "response": "tater", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: n,k,m,o,s,d. ", "response": "pirai", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: n,k,m,o,s,d. ", "response": "maror", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,d. ", "response": "nal", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: m,y,r,p,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,a. Absents letters: m,r,y,t,l,p,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,h,m,t,l,p,d. ", "response": "gales", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: e,g,t,h,u. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: m,e,g,c,t,a,h,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,o,s. Absents letters: e,c,h,m,g,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "porns", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,s,p. Absents letters: e,c,h,m,g,l,t,a,u. ", "response": "porns", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,p,h,t. ", "response": "skull", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,r,h,k,t,p,d. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n. Absents letters: i,r,e,h,k,t,p,d. ", "response": "mung", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n. Absents letters: i,r,e,h,k,t,p,d. ", "response": "gon", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: s,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "tich", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t. Absents letters: m,s,o,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "thymi", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t. Absents letters: y,m,s,o,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: k,s,n. ", "response": "boart", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: k,s,e,n,a. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: e,n,b,k,s,g,t,a. ", "response": "porns", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,r. Absents letters: e,n,b,h,k,s,g,t,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,g. Absents letters: u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e,g. Absents letters: p,u,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e,g. Absents letters: i,v,p,c,u,d. ", "response": "tore", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e,g. Absents letters: i,a,v,n,p,c,u,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: x. Absents letters: l,a,g. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: x,e. Absents letters: f,z,y,g,l,a. ", "response": "deism", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: x,e. Absents letters: i,y,z,m,a,g,l,p,f. ", "response": "exile", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,x,e. Absents letters: i,y,z,f,m,s,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "exode", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,o,c,v. ", "response": "wands", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: i,o,v,s,l,c,w. ", "response": "enate", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,a,n,t. Absents letters: i,r,c,w,k,o,v,s,l. ", "response": "tapes", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,t,e,p,a. Absents letters: i,r,c,w,k,o,v,s,l. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,v,s,e,d. ", "response": "kaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: e,n,m,o,v,s,a,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: e,n,k,m,o,v,s,a,d. ", "response": "bleep", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,h,t. Absents letters: e,n,k,m,o,v,s,g,a,d. ", "response": "thine", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: k,s,o,d. ", "response": "darer", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y. Absents letters: r,w,k,m,s,o,d. ", "response": "nancy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,a,y. Absents letters: i,r,z,w,k,m,s,o,d. ", "response": "bared", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,b,y. Absents letters: i,r,e,z,c,h,w,k,m,s,o,t,d. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: r,u. ", "response": "stich", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,t. Absents letters: r,y,e,u. ", "response": "pests", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,t. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,u,d. ", "response": "sluit", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,t. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,c,a,u,d. ", "response": "bpt", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o. Absents letters: p,e. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,a. Absents letters: s,e,n,p,w,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,a. Absents letters: r,e,n,w,s,g,p,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,b,c,w,s,g,p,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: b,h,t. ", "response": "pales", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: f,o,g,r,t,b,h. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,r,b,h,o,g,t,f. ", "response": "pales", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,b,h,o,g,t,f. ", "response": "p k", "reward": -13.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,w,r. ", "response": "fests", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,s,a,r,c,w. ", "response": "decks", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,d. Absents letters: i,r,c,w,s,p,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,d. Absents letters: i,r,c,h,w,s,t,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: w,v,y,e. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: y,e,j,b,w,m,v. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: y,e,r,j,b,h,w,m,v,a. ", "response": "tic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: r,y,e,j,b,h,w,k,m,v,t,a. ", "response": "biffs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,c. Absents letters: k,u,l. ", "response": "nancy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,a,e. Absents letters: k,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "cag", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e,c,a. Absents letters: k,s,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "meted", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e,c,a. Absents letters: i,k,s,o,g,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,s,o,t. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,e,k,s,o,t. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,b. Absents letters: i,r,e,k,o,s,t,f,u. ", "response": "abirk", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,a,y. Absents letters: i,r,e,k,o,s,t,f,u. ", "response": "bagy", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,p,n. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,g,n,l,p,b. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,a. Absents letters: i,n,b,c,t,g,l,p,d. ", "response": "sared", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,n,c,b,o,g,t,l,p,f,d. ", "response": "shale", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: p,s,r,u. ", "response": "tich", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,y,k,s,p,f,u. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,y,r,b,k,s,t,p,f,u. ", "response": "wuss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,y,r,b,k,s,t,p,f,u. ", "response": "wadd", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: z,n. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: m,o,z,n,f. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,r. Absents letters: m,o,z,s,n,t,f. ", "response": "galvo", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,r. Absents letters: z,n,m,o,s,t,f,d. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n. Absents letters: p,e,t. ", "response": "gin", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n. Absents letters: o,r,e,t,p. ", "response": "sinks", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n. Absents letters: o,r,e,t,p,a. ", "response": "sinks", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n. Absents letters: r,e,c,o,t,p,a. ", "response": "kyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,a,r,d. ", "response": "gou", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,h,o,a,d. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,h,o,a,d. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,h,o,l,a,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,s,t. ", "response": "dared", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: s,o,t,l,p. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,h,s,o,t,l,p. ", "response": "dy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,h,s,o,t,l,p. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,y,r,u. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n. Absents letters: i,m,r,y,c,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,n. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,c,m,g,u. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,n,a. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,c,h,m,g,p,u. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: s,d,e,n. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: s,o,e,n,b,c,d. ", "response": "karzy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,r. Absents letters: e,n,c,b,w,s,o,d. ", "response": "galvo", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,r. Absents letters: y,e,n,b,c,w,s,o,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: p,e,u,d. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: e,h,o,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "arrah", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,k,a. Absents letters: r,e,b,h,o,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "kia", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,k,a. Absents letters: r,e,b,h,o,s,v,t,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: o,h,e,n. ", "response": "pores", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,r. Absents letters: o,e,n,t,c,h. ", "response": "karzy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,r. Absents letters: e,n,c,h,o,s,t,f. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,b,a. Absents letters: e,n,c,h,o,s,t,f. ", "response": "boing", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: b,r,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,s. Absents letters: r,y,n,b,d. ", "response": "kiers", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,e. Absents letters: g,y,r,n,p,b,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,e. Absents letters: r,y,n,b,h,g,p,d. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: m,c,h,e. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n. Absents letters: m,r,e,g,c,h. ", "response": "bings", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,n. Absents letters: r,e,c,h,m,g,l,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,n. Absents letters: r,e,y,c,h,b,m,g,l,a. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: n,a,u,g. ", "response": "seels", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,e. Absents letters: v,n,g,a,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,o,v,g,a,u,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,b,o,v,g,a,u,d. ", "response": "leese", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: o,c,u,d. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: y,c,o,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: i,y,n,c,o,g,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,a. Absents letters: i,y,n,c,o,g,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,k,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,k,s,d. ", "response": "ber", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,n,k,s,a,d. ", "response": "bry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,n,k,s,a,d. ", "response": "ber", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b. Absents letters: o,r. ", "response": "bocks", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b. Absents letters: o,a,r,y,f. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b. Absents letters: y,r,n,w,o,a,g,f. ", "response": "bices", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b. Absents letters: r,y,n,w,f,o,g,t,a. ", "response": "boons", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c. Absents letters: i,s,u,t. ", "response": "corer", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,r. Absents letters: i,n,s,t,l,u. ", "response": "coral", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,r,e. Absents letters: i,n,b,s,o,g,t,l,u. ", "response": "crice", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,c,d. Absents letters: i,n,b,s,o,g,l,t,a,u. ", "response": "recid", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: m,d. ", "response": "pirog", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: k,m,s,o,c,d. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,a,r. Absents letters: e,c,k,m,s,o,u,d. ", "response": "parch", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,a,r. Absents letters: e,c,k,m,s,o,v,g,u,d. ", "response": "parge", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: p,y,u,g. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: y,e,g,p,u. ", "response": "tis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: o,t,y,e,g,p,u. ", "response": "sifts", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n. Absents letters: y,e,o,g,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "kains", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,a,b,e. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: i,a,e,n,l,b. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: i,e,n,b,h,m,v,l,a. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: i,e,n,b,h,f,m,v,t,l,a. ", "response": "gu", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: o,c,u,g. ", "response": "shake", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: c,b,k,o,s,g,u. ", "response": "niche", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: z,n,c,b,k,o,s,g,u,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: n,z,b,c,k,m,o,s,g,l,u,d. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,d. Absents letters: s,a,y. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,d. Absents letters: s,y,a. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,d. Absents letters: s,a,y. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,d. Absents letters: s,y,b,a. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,s,l,n. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,n,h,s,g,l. ", "response": "bride", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,h,s,g,l. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,d. Absents letters: i,r,n,h,s,g,l,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: t,w,z. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: x,e,z,t,w,d. ", "response": "gog", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: x,e,z,r,w,s,t,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: r,x,e,z,b,w,f,s,t,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: p,e,n. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,r,t. Absents letters: y,e,n,p,a. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,r,t. Absents letters: y,e,n,m,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,r,t. Absents letters: y,e,n,m,v,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "torrs", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,o,q,u. ", "response": "sext", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: q,m,o,s,l,p,u. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: q,m,o,s,l,p,u. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: q,n,m,o,s,t,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "rorie", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,r. Absents letters: m. ", "response": "ars", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,a. Absents letters: k,m,p,l. ", "response": "arcos", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,r. Absents letters: k,m,i,s,l,p. ", "response": "boart", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,a. Absents letters: i,n,k,m,s,l,p. ", "response": "tater", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,m,r,l. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,q,r,m,s,t,l,u. ", "response": "heame", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,q,r,m,s,o,t,l,u,d. ", "response": "nark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,q,r,c,h,m,s,o,t,l,u,d. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,a,r,t. ", "response": "loipe", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,r,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o. Absents letters: i,r,e,j,b,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "loipe", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o. Absents letters: i,r,e,z,j,b,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: b,r,e,t. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n. Absents letters: r,e,t,y,b,u. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n. Absents letters: y,r,e,b,c,t,u,d. ", "response": "panax", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n. Absents letters: r,y,e,c,b,o,s,t,u,d. ", "response": "panax", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,c,r,e. Absents letters: g. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,r,e,c. Absents letters: x,t,w,g. ", "response": "cared", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,r,e,c. Absents letters: o,x,g,t,w,u,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,r,e,c. Absents letters: x,n,w,m,o,g,t,u,d. ", "response": "cared", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: m,a,g. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: f,m,r,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: r,c,m,a,g,l,t,f,u. ", "response": "shirk", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: r,c,f,m,g,l,t,a,u. ", "response": "shirk", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,r,e,g. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: m,r,e,g,t,h. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,e,c,h,m,g,t,u. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,h,m,p,g,t,u. ", "response": "kh", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,a,u,g. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: h,m,o,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: x,h,m,o,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: x,n,h,w,m,o,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "tices", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,e. Absents letters: a,q,u. ", "response": "tik", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,e. Absents letters: i,m,q,p,a,u. ", "response": "skets", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,e. Absents letters: i,q,f,m,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,e. Absents letters: i,q,c,m,a,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: m,c,h. ", "response": "bant", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: i,m,o,b,c,h. ", "response": "pests", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y,n,t. Absents letters: i,m,o,r,e,c,b,h. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,n,t,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,x,c,b,h,m,o. ", "response": "tans", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: r,b,y,n. ", "response": "perea", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: f,y,r,n,t,b. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: r,y,n,z,b,m,t,f,u. ", "response": "pash", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,l. Absents letters: y,r,z,n,b,m,o,t,f,u. ", "response": "sals", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: v,e,z. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: v,y,e,z,l,f. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: y,e,z,b,m,a,v,g,l,f. ", "response": "shirk", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: y,e,z,b,f,m,s,v,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "kro", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: m,o,w,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,r,w,m,o,d. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,r,w,k,m,o,t,d. ", "response": "peats", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,r,w,k,m,o,g,t,d. ", "response": "peage", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,m,s,l,p. ", "response": "nix", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,e,n. Absents letters: i,m,s,l,p. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,e,n. Absents letters: i,r,m,s,l,p,a. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y,e,n,h. Absents letters: i,r,m,s,l,p,a. ", "response": "ensky", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: h,y,e,d. ", "response": "pians", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: s,y,e,n,h,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,r,h,s,d. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,u. Absents letters: i,r,y,e,n,h,s,d. ", "response": "ural", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,a. Absents letters: o,u,g. ", "response": "bic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,c,d. Absents letters: o,r,e,g,p,u. ", "response": "bic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,a,d. Absents letters: r,e,h,o,t,g,p,u. ", "response": "cadgy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,c,a,d. Absents letters: r,e,b,h,o,g,t,p,u. ", "response": "candy", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: m,y. ", "response": "saris", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,r,e. Absents letters: m,o,y,d. ", "response": "stair", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e,a. Absents letters: m,o,q,y,n,u,d. ", "response": "stair", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e,a. Absents letters: q,y,n,m,o,g,p,u,d. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: c,h,e. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: v,r,e,c,h. ", "response": "gin", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: r,e,c,h,v,t,p,a. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,l. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,h,b,v,t,p,a. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,p,a. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n. Absents letters: v,y,e,l,p,a. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n. Absents letters: y,e,r,f,v,l,p,a. ", "response": "gin", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n. Absents letters: r,y,e,a,v,l,p,f,u. ", "response": "sna", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,e,l,b,u. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: m,r,e,l,b,u. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: r,e,n,j,b,w,m,l,u. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: r,e,n,j,b,h,w,m,l,u,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: p,y,r,e. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,y,e,k,p,u,d. ", "response": "gnats", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,k,g,p,u,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,n,k,g,p,u,d. ", "response": "fests", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: f,s,a,l,c. ", "response": "diker", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,d. Absents letters: f,k,s,a,y,l,c. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,w,d. Absents letters: y,c,k,s,a,l,f. ", "response": "dwed", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,w,e,d. Absents letters: y,c,k,s,a,o,l,f. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,h,e,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s. Absents letters: i,o,e,f,h,u,d. ", "response": "sp p", "reward": -11.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s. Absents letters: i,e,n,h,o,a,f,u,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,t. Absents letters: i,e,n,h,f,o,a,u,d. ", "response": "slush", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,s,y,n,h. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,s,o,y,n,p,h. ", "response": "titch", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,r,n,h,m,s,o,p. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,d. Absents letters: r,y,n,h,m,s,o,p. ", "response": "deary", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,e,s,g. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: x,e,o,s,g,t. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: x,e,o,s,g,l,t. ", "response": "kui", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,a. Absents letters: x,e,r,o,s,g,l,t. ", "response": "limax", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: k,p,r. ", "response": "shute", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e. Absents letters: k,s,o,r,p. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a,e. Absents letters: r,b,k,s,o,p,d. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a,e. Absents letters: r,z,n,b,k,s,o,p,d. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: k,s,u,t. ", "response": "boing", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,p,y. Absents letters: k,i,s,n,t,u. ", "response": "leppy", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,p,y. Absents letters: i,n,k,s,t,a,u. ", "response": "gyppy", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,e,l,p. Absents letters: i,n,h,k,s,t,a,u. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,f,r,e. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: o,r,e,t,f. ", "response": "gim", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,e,b,o,t,f,u. ", "response": "sals", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,n. Absents letters: r,e,b,o,a,t,f,u. ", "response": "minos", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: o,a,t. ", "response": "slur", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: c,h,m,o,t,p,a. ", "response": "sewel", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,i. Absents letters: c,h,m,o,t,p,a. ", "response": "seifs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,v,e,l. Absents letters: m,o,a,n,t,p,c,h. ", "response": "vinyl", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: l,m,t. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,r,b. Absents letters: l,m,e,t. ", "response": "boors", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,r,b. Absents letters: e,n,h,m,g,t,l,a. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,b,r,s. Absents letters: y,e,n,h,m,g,l,t,a,d. ", "response": "porns", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h,r. Absents letters: p,a. ", "response": "sherd", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h,r. Absents letters: o,l,p,a,w. ", "response": "loids", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,h,u. Absents letters: o,e,l,p,a,w. ", "response": "rishi", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h,r,u. Absents letters: e,z,w,o,l,p,a. ", "response": "shrew", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,i,y,n. ", "response": "gourd", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,y,n,c,t,l. ", "response": "fad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,d. Absents letters: i,o,y,n,l,t,c. ", "response": "dices", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,d. Absents letters: i,y,n,j,c,w,o,t,l,a. ", "response": "sewed", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,p. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: i,p,l. ", "response": "rexes", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: i,l,p,w. ", "response": "rexes", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,r,e. Absents letters: i,x,n,w,t,l,p. ", "response": "loes", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,g. Absents letters: p,y,d. ", "response": "gourd", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,u,g. Absents letters: i,y,e,l,p,d. ", "response": "gunk", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,u,g. Absents letters: i,y,e,c,b,o,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "gunk", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,u,g. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,b,c,o,t,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "gou", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,e,j,w,d. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: r,e,j,b,c,w,o,a,d. ", "response": "tic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: r,e,y,n,j,c,b,w,m,o,a,d. ", "response": "tich", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: y,r,e,n,j,c,b,w,m,o,v,a,u,d. ", "response": "gents", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: f,g,n. ", "response": "bise", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,l. Absents letters: a,g,n,t,f. ", "response": "shine", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,l. Absents letters: f,g,n,t,b,a. ", "response": "seifs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,l. Absents letters: r,n,b,c,a,o,g,t,f. ", "response": "shine", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: s,b,w,a. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: b,w,s,t,a,u. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: q,b,w,s,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "bider", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: q,e,b,h,w,s,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "kiers", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,o,h,t. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,g. Absents letters: o,y,t,l,h. ", "response": "gamin", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,g. Absents letters: o,y,t,l,c,h,u. ", "response": "gag", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,g. Absents letters: i,y,c,h,o,t,l,u. ", "response": "gags", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: s,a,r,e. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t. Absents letters: r,e,c,s,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "tic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t. Absents letters: r,e,n,c,s,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "thine", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t. Absents letters: r,e,n,c,s,o,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "thi", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,r,e,t,h. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c. Absents letters: m,r,e,t,a,h,u. ", "response": "cides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,c. Absents letters: r,e,n,h,m,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,c. Absents letters: r,e,n,h,w,m,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "skie", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: t,s,d,n. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,s,n,t,b,d. ", "response": "leany", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,b,s,t,d. ", "response": "aglee", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,b,s,v,t,d. ", "response": "fad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: y,r,t,a,d. ", "response": "pong", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: r,y,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,n,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "slunk", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,o. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,r,b,c,k,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "lobos", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,p,a,h. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,f,n,p,a,h,u. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: i,n,h,f,m,t,p,a,u. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: i,r,n,b,h,m,a,t,p,f,u. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b. Absents letters: l,c,h,e. ", "response": "boaks", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b. Absents letters: k,e,l,c,h. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b,u. Absents letters: k,e,l,c,h. ", "response": "bah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b,u. Absents letters: e,n,c,h,k,m,o,l,a,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: j,o,g. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,y,n. Absents letters: o,s,g,p,j,a. ", "response": "bing", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t,y,n. Absents letters: j,h,k,o,s,g,p,a. ", "response": "enact", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,y,n,t. Absents letters: r,j,h,k,o,s,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "enact", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: p,s,e,t. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: s,e,t,n,p,a,h. ", "response": "boomy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y. Absents letters: e,n,c,h,k,s,t,p,a. ", "response": "boody", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y,d. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,h,k,s,v,t,p,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,a,w,e. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: r,e,y,h,w,k,a. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n. Absents letters: y,r,e,h,w,k,o,v,a,d. ", "response": "nix", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n. Absents letters: r,y,e,h,w,k,m,o,v,l,a,d. ", "response": "sinks", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: w. Absents letters: a,r,e. ", "response": "wuss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,w. Absents letters: g,r,e,t,l,a. ", "response": "swish", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,w. Absents letters: r,e,k,s,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "swink", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,w. Absents letters: r,e,k,s,g,l,t,a,d. ", "response": "swink", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,h,w,s. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m. Absents letters: o,s,r,e,c,h,w. ", "response": "jugum", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,h,w,o,s. ", "response": "bum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,h,w,o,s,t. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,d. Absents letters: y,e,g. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,d. Absents letters: y,e,h,k,o,s,g. ", "response": "cadal", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,n,d. Absents letters: y,e,h,k,o,s,g,a. ", "response": "nald", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,d,n. Absents letters: y,e,h,k,f,o,s,g,p,a. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: k,i,t. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,b,a. Absents letters: k,i,w,t. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e,n,b. Absents letters: i,y,w,k,m,o,t. ", "response": "nuts", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e,n,b. Absents letters: i,y,w,k,m,o,g,t,l,p. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,k,f. ", "response": "cuifs", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: k,a,y,n,g,l,f. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e. Absents letters: i,y,n,c,k,f,g,l,a. ", "response": "bode", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e. Absents letters: i,y,n,c,w,k,a,g,l,t,f. ", "response": "dors", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,a,b,t. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: y,b,t,l,a. ", "response": "gus", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: y,n,b,o,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u,e. Absents letters: y,r,n,b,o,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "skugs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,p,a,d. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,m,g,p,a,d. ", "response": "shme", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: i,e,m,g,p,a,d. ", "response": "kro", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,r,t. Absents letters: i,e,n,m,g,p,a,d. ", "response": "loirs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,m,o,c,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: i,m,o,k,y,c,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,u. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,c,k,m,o,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,u. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,c,k,m,o,l,a,d. ", "response": "gri", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: c,r,n. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y,s. Absents letters: c,r,e,n. ", "response": "boomy", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y,s. Absents letters: r,e,n,c,l,a,u. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y,s. Absents letters: r,e,n,c,w,m,l,a,u. ", "response": "boomy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,f,r,e. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,h,w,t,f. ", "response": "boaks", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,h,w,t,p,f. ", "response": "gales", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,h,w,t,p,f. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,o,r,e,f. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,d. Absents letters: m,o,r,e,n,f. ", "response": "wad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,d. Absents letters: r,e,n,m,o,v,l,f,u. ", "response": "wad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,d. Absents letters: r,e,n,m,o,v,l,f,u. ", "response": "sadd", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,f,e,t. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,u. Absents letters: o,y,e,t,l,f. ", "response": "kills", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,p,a,u. Absents letters: y,e,c,h,m,o,t,l,f. ", "response": "pach", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,p,a,u. Absents letters: y,e,c,h,w,m,o,g,t,l,f. ", "response": "kas", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,e,t. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a. Absents letters: r,e,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "paw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,a. Absents letters: r,e,t,l,p,n,u. ", "response": "gomer", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,a. Absents letters: r,e,n,y,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "sma", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: a,b,y. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: a,o,s,y,b,u. ", "response": "tiled", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: y,b,o,s,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "deice", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: g,e,d. Absents letters: y,b,o,s,t,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "segni", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: p,o,b,r. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s. Absents letters: o,r,e,l,p,b. ", "response": "sma", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s. Absents letters: r,e,b,h,o,l,p,d. ", "response": "stich", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,s,a. Absents letters: r,e,b,h,o,l,p,d. ", "response": "sma", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: p,o,r,d. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,r,o,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,o,v,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b,g. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,o,v,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "gogs", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,o,s,e,h. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: i,m,o,s,e,n,h. ", "response": "thaw", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,a,t. Absents letters: i,e,n,h,m,o,s. ", "response": "patin", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t,p,a. Absents letters: i,e,n,h,m,o,s,u. ", "response": "pated", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: p,u,t. ", "response": "gales", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,i,e. Absents letters: t,p,c,u. ", "response": "ler", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,i,e. Absents letters: c,o,t,p,a,u. ", "response": "kiers", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,n,l. Absents letters: r,c,o,g,t,p,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,f,y,g. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e,d. Absents letters: o,y,g,f,h. ", "response": "dared", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e,d. Absents letters: y,b,h,w,o,g,t,f. ", "response": "sared", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e,d. Absents letters: y,b,h,w,o,a,s,g,t,f. ", "response": "sared", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: o,h. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: o,z,b,h,u. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: z,b,h,f,o,a,u,d. ", "response": "sires", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: z,n,b,h,w,m,o,a,f,u,d. ", "response": "seise", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,e,l,p,u. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: e,b,s,o,l,p,f,u. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,e,b,o,s,l,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,b,c,o,s,l,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,r. Absents letters: a,e,n. ", "response": "rogu", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,y. Absents letters: m,s,e,n,a. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,y,r. Absents letters: i,m,s,e,n,a,u. ", "response": "proll", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,p,y. Absents letters: i,e,n,k,m,s,a,u. ", "response": "proll", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,b. Absents letters: s,a. ", "response": "boomy", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,b. Absents letters: s,n,a,d. ", "response": "boom", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,e,b. Absents letters: i,s,v,n,l,a,d. ", "response": "boke", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,b,e. Absents letters: i,n,c,s,v,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "boume", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,n,l,f,w. ", "response": "bab", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,s,n,l,t,f,w. ", "response": "hight", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: n,j,w,o,s,t,l,f. ", "response": "dek", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: r,n,z,j,w,o,s,t,l,f. ", "response": "bride", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: p,o,c. ", "response": "skull", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: e,c,o,t,p,d. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h,u. Absents letters: r,e,c,b,o,t,p,d. ", "response": "shuck", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h,u. Absents letters: r,e,y,b,c,o,t,p,d. ", "response": "shiver", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: k,c,t. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e,s. Absents letters: k,z,t,c. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,r,e. Absents letters: z,n,c,b,w,k,t,l. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,r,e. Absents letters: n,z,b,c,w,k,v,t,l. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: s,u,d. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,r,e,t. Absents letters: s,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "twerp", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,t,l. Absents letters: s,y,g,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "shrew", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,t,l. Absents letters: y,s,g,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,a. Absents letters: r,t. ", "response": "pans", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,p,a. Absents letters: i,m,r,t,l. ", "response": "sapes", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,p,a. Absents letters: i,m,k,r,t,l. ", "response": "pases", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,p,a. Absents letters: i,r,n,k,m,o,t,l. ", "response": "pals", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,o,s,g. ", "response": "nark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,o,s,g,l,p,u. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n. Absents letters: i,y,o,s,g,l,p,u. ", "response": "bant", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,n. Absents letters: i,y,o,s,t,g,l,p,u. ", "response": "ennog", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p. Absents letters: a,z,u,n. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,p. Absents letters: z,n,l,b,a,u. ", "response": "tices", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,p,e. Absents letters: r,z,n,b,l,a,u. ", "response": "pekin", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,p,e. Absents letters: r,z,n,b,m,l,a,u. ", "response": "pique", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: a,r,t. ", "response": "shine", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: v,r,t,p,a,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: r,x,o,v,t,p,a,d. ", "response": "shake", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: x,r,o,v,s,t,p,a,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: c,h,r,t. ", "response": "nal", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,d. Absents letters: r,n,t,b,c,h. ", "response": "wad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,d. Absents letters: r,y,n,c,b,h,o,t,l,f. ", "response": "deary", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,d. Absents letters: y,r,n,b,c,h,o,v,t,l,f. ", "response": "deked", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,y,r,g. ", "response": "wak", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,r,m,s,g,l,u. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: r,y,m,s,g,l,u,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: y,r,m,s,g,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: p,s,y. ", "response": "diker", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,a. Absents letters: s,y,r,e,p,h. ", "response": "limax", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,a. Absents letters: r,y,e,c,h,s,t,l,p. ", "response": "maror", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,g,a. Absents letters: y,r,e,c,h,s,t,l,p. ", "response": "limma", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,o,g,n. ", "response": "wuss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,n,o,g,l,p. ", "response": "aru", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: y,n,o,g,l,p. ", "response": "sak", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,a. Absents letters: o,g,y,e,n,l,p,d. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,a. Absents letters: b. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,a. Absents letters: i,m,t,b,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,l,a. Absents letters: i,m,t,b,u,d. ", "response": "oval", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,a,s. Absents letters: i,y,b,c,k,m,t,u,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,t. Absents letters: a,b. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u,s,t. Absents letters: m,a,e,l,b. ", "response": "tonne", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t,o,u,s. Absents letters: r,e,b,m,v,l,a. ", "response": "toust", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,o,s,t,u. Absents letters: r,e,b,m,v,l,a. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: s,f,y,u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: y,b,s,f,u. ", "response": "bry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: f,s,y,p,b,u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: y,b,s,o,p,f,u. ", "response": "tared", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p. Absents letters: s,a,y,t. ", "response": "pling", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p. Absents letters: y,n,s,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "premy", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,o. Absents letters: y,n,z,s,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,o. Absents letters: y,r,z,n,k,s,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: o,e,z. ", "response": "boans", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,a,r. Absents letters: i,k,o,e,z. ", "response": "slur", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,l,a. Absents letters: i,e,z,n,k,o,g,u,d. ", "response": "slart", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: f,s,r,l,a. Absents letters: i,e,n,z,c,k,o,g,u,d. ", "response": "furls", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: k,w,a,y. ", "response": "rogu", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: y,w,k,s,l,a,d. ", "response": "boomy", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,t. Absents letters: y,e,c,w,k,s,l,a,d. ", "response": "tol", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,t. Absents letters: y,e,c,b,w,k,s,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "tosh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,b,r,u. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,n,l,b,u. ", "response": "gogs", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,e,n,b,c,h,t,l,u. ", "response": "sifts", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: r,e,n,c,b,h,m,t,l,u. ", "response": "sices", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,u. Absents letters: o,f,r. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,u. Absents letters: i,r,c,o,g,f. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,u. Absents letters: i,r,c,o,s,g,t,f. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,u. Absents letters: i,r,c,h,m,o,s,g,t,f. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: t,c,h,u,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n. Absents letters: i,t,l,c,h,u,d. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n. Absents letters: i,e,c,h,t,l,u,d. ", "response": "sna", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,g,n. Absents letters: i,e,c,h,t,l,u,d. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,u,n. ", "response": "bayer", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,d. Absents letters: i,v,n,l,u. ", "response": "dared", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,a,d. Absents letters: i,o,v,n,l,f,u. ", "response": "sared", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,a,d. Absents letters: i,n,k,o,v,l,p,f,u. ", "response": "tared", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: s,d,h,z. ", "response": "rogu", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u,e. Absents letters: s,r,z,h,d. ", "response": "tride", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u,e. Absents letters: k,s,r,y,z,a,h,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,o,v,g,u. Absents letters: y,r,z,h,k,s,a,d. ", "response": "vog", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: o,x,e,n. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,x,e,n,r,o,g,l,a. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,r,x,e,n,o,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,x,b,o,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "fests", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: f,y,g. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: v,y,g,l,f. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: i,y,c,k,v,g,l,f,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,s. Absents letters: i,y,c,k,m,v,g,l,p,f,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: r,u,t. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: k,o,r,y,t,b,u. ", "response": "noles", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: y,r,e,b,k,o,t,p,u,d. ", "response": "shays", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,h. Absents letters: r,y,e,b,w,k,o,t,p,u,d. ", "response": "shish", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: p,s. ", "response": "bride", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,s,z,p,h. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: v,e. Absents letters: i,y,z,h,s,t,p,a. ", "response": "vex", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,v,e. Absents letters: i,y,z,h,s,g,t,p,a. ", "response": "vile", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: a,r. ", "response": "stots", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,e,p,a. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,e,p,a,u. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,r,e,m,v,p,a,u. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: k,s,h,e. ", "response": "maron", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: k,m,s,e,g,h,u. ", "response": "thali", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: r,e,y,n,h,k,m,s,o,g,u,d. ", "response": "tharm", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,t. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,n,c,h,k,m,s,o,g,u,d. ", "response": "nal", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,l. Absents letters: v,y,e. ", "response": "gin", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,l,d. Absents letters: s,v,y,e,a. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,l,d. Absents letters: y,e,n,w,s,v,a. ", "response": "loid", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,r,l,d. Absents letters: y,e,n,b,w,s,v,a. ", "response": "dh", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: y,g,p,u,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: y,g,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "bries", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: m,y,g,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: y,c,m,o,t,g,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b. Absents letters: y,e,z. ", "response": "boomy", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,b. Absents letters: y,e,z,l,h. ", "response": "bax", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,b,u. Absents letters: k,y,e,z,l,h. ", "response": "bh", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,b,u. Absents letters: y,e,z,h,w,k,s,g,l. ", "response": "bh", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,f,e,n. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,e,n,m,l,f,u. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,s,a. Absents letters: i,e,n,h,m,l,f,u. ", "response": "scary", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c,a. Absents letters: i,e,n,h,m,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: a,r,e,z. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: r,e,z,h,m,g,a. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,b. Absents letters: r,e,z,h,m,g,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,b. Absents letters: r,e,z,h,f,m,g,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,v,e. ", "response": "gats", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: v,e,l,p. ", "response": "sinks", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: e,n,c,o,v,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "shiso", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: e,n,c,o,v,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "shis", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: a,r,t. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,h,s. Absents letters: r,e,t,a,w. ", "response": "hock", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,c,h. Absents letters: i,r,e,t,a,w,d. ", "response": "chops", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,c,h. Absents letters: i,r,e,w,f,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "chaws", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: i,y,e,l. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: i,y,e,z,l. ", "response": "roopy", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: w,o,r. Absents letters: i,y,e,z,l. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,o,w. Absents letters: i,g,y,e,z,l,u. ", "response": "warow", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: k,r,u. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: k,r,y,g,p,u. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: k,y,r,g,e,p,b,u. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: y,e,r,b,h,k,g,p,u. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: m,o,e,t. ", "response": "enarm", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: r,e,b,k,m,o,t. ", "response": "sne", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: r,e,b,k,m,o,t,p,a. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: g,u,n. Absents letters: r,e,b,k,m,o,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "ungsung", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: k,o,h,s. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a. Absents letters: r,n,h,k,o,s. ", "response": "maror", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a. Absents letters: r,e,n,b,h,k,o,s,v. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a,t. Absents letters: r,e,n,b,h,k,o,s,v. ", "response": "tame", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: m,s,a,r. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: r,y,e,m,s,g,l,a. ", "response": "boong", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u,d. Absents letters: y,r,e,n,m,s,g,l,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u,d. Absents letters: r,y,e,n,h,m,s,g,l,a. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: o,c,u,s. ", "response": "enact", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: o,s,c,h,u. ", "response": "ennog", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: r,c,h,o,s,a,u,d. ", "response": "nix", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: r,y,c,h,o,s,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,w,e,n. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,r. Absents letters: k,e,n,l,b,w. ", "response": "arcos", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,a. Absents letters: e,n,b,w,k,m,g,l. ", "response": "boart", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,r. Absents letters: e,n,z,b,w,k,m,s,g,l. ", "response": "maror", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: t,u,e,n. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: f,s,a. Absents letters: k,e,n,t,u. ", "response": "fards", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,f,a. Absents letters: k,e,n,t,b,u. ", "response": "festa", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,a,r,f. Absents letters: e,n,b,k,o,t,p,u. ", "response": "firs", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: k,s,r,e,n. ", "response": "titch", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,r,e,n,k,s,o,f. ", "response": "biff", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,r,e,n,k,s,o,t,f. ", "response": "hight", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,h,k,s,o,t,f. ", "response": "uv", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: h,w,e. ", "response": "rogu", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r. Absents letters: o,e,n,l,h,w. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r. Absents letters: e,n,h,w,o,g,l,f. ", "response": "ars", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,a. Absents letters: e,n,h,w,k,o,g,l,p,f,u. ", "response": "boors", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,s,b. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,b,h,s,l,p,a. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,b,h,m,s,l,p,a. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,t. Absents letters: i,b,h,f,m,s,l,p,a. ", "response": "bery", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,p,a,n. ", "response": "shake", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: n,l,p,b,a. ", "response": "sier", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: a,s,n,l,p,b,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: n,b,h,s,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "bry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,n. Absents letters: c,r. ", "response": "sna", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n,a. Absents letters: k,o,r,c,h. ", "response": "nuts", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,a,n. Absents letters: r,x,y,e,c,h,k,o. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n,a. Absents letters: x,y,r,e,c,h,k,o,p. ", "response": "ninas", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: t,s,y,n. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,e,n,s,t,l,p. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,a. Absents letters: y,e,n,s,t,l,p. ", "response": "camos", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,c,r. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,s,t,l,p. ", "response": "karat", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,o,e,l,w. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: e,h,w,s,o,g,l. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: e,h,w,s,o,g,l,t,u. ", "response": "bung", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,n. Absents letters: e,h,w,s,o,g,l,t,a,u. ", "response": "kro", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: c,e,d. ", "response": "kis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n. Absents letters: o,a,e,g,l,c,d. ", "response": "minis", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n. Absents letters: e,c,m,o,g,l,a,d. ", "response": "nix", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n. Absents letters: e,c,m,o,g,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "minos", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: h,w,g. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: t,r,y,g,p,h,w. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: y,r,h,w,p,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: r,y,c,h,w,t,g,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "sewer", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,t,u,n. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,r,n,s,t,u. ", "response": "bonie", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,r,n,h,s,o,t,f,u. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,r,n,h,s,o,a,v,t,f,u. ", "response": "cuvee", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: b,r,t. ", "response": "slily", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,e. Absents letters: a,r,t,b. ", "response": "loof", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,e. Absents letters: a,o,r,t,b,d. ", "response": "slily", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,l. Absents letters: r,b,o,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,e,u. ", "response": "bab", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,n. Absents letters: i,o,e,c,u. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,n. Absents letters: i,e,c,o,p,u. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,n. Absents letters: i,e,c,o,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "sna", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: c,h,u,e. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: y,e,z,c,h,g,a,u. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: y,e,z,r,c,h,g,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: r,y,e,z,c,h,w,k,g,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "bings", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,m,x. ", "response": "fests", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n. Absents letters: i,m,x. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n. Absents letters: i,x,r,c,m,o,g,a. ", "response": "seh", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n. Absents letters: i,x,r,y,c,f,m,o,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "sents", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,f,r. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,p,e. Absents letters: i,o,r,f,h. ", "response": "mated", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e,p,d. Absents letters: i,o,r,f,h. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e,p,d. Absents letters: i,o,a,r,f,h. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: m,p,r,e. ", "response": "boong", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y. Absents letters: r,e,c,h,m,p,u,d. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,y. Absents letters: r,e,c,h,m,p,u,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,y,b. Absents letters: r,e,n,c,h,m,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "boogy", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: m,w. ", "response": "sma", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,m,t,h,w. ", "response": "gales", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n. Absents letters: i,c,h,w,m,o,g,t. ", "response": "nes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n. Absents letters: i,c,h,w,m,o,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "nen", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,f. Absents letters: k,s,e. ", "response": "fiz", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,f. Absents letters: k,m,s,e,n. ", "response": "flick", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,f. Absents letters: e,n,k,m,s,l,a,u. ", "response": "tif", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,f,y. Absents letters: e,n,h,w,k,m,s,o,l,a,u. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: o,b,a. ", "response": "tiled", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: k,o,a,s,v,b. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n,d. Absents letters: k,o,v,s,a,z,b. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d,e,n. Absents letters: r,z,b,k,o,v,s,p,a. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,g. Absents letters: r,u. ", "response": "gains", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,g. Absents letters: r,e,n,f,u,d. ", "response": "gags", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,g. Absents letters: r,e,n,f,u,d. ", "response": "gags", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,g. Absents letters: r,e,n,b,f,u,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,d. Absents letters: q,u. ", "response": "sne", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,d. Absents letters: q,n,l,t,u. ", "response": "sad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,d. Absents letters: q,r,y,n,e,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "dad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,d. Absents letters: q,y,r,e,n,m,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "dh", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: o,d,e,n. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: o,g,e,n,l,u,d. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: e,n,c,h,o,g,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: e,n,c,h,k,o,t,g,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: c,o,b,e. ", "response": "bight", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: y,e,c,b,o,s,d. ", "response": "tif", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,t. Absents letters: y,e,c,b,k,o,s,d. ", "response": "patte", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,t. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,b,c,k,o,s,g,d. ", "response": "thaw", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: k,i,n. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,g. Absents letters: k,i,n,a,u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,g. Absents letters: i,n,h,k,l,a,u. ", "response": "gares", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,g. Absents letters: i,n,c,h,k,l,a,u. ", "response": "gares", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,b. Absents letters: s,e,d. ", "response": "blink", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,b. Absents letters: s,y,e,n,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,b,a. Absents letters: y,e,n,s,o,t,u,d. ", "response": "bh", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,b,a. Absents letters: y,e,n,s,o,t,u,d. ", "response": "borg", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,f,w,n. ", "response": "abode", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: r,e,n,w,v,l,f. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a. Absents letters: r,e,n,w,v,l,f,u. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,a. Absents letters: r,e,n,w,v,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,y,u,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: m,y,l,u,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: m,y,l,h,u,d. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: y,h,m,g,l,u,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e. Absents letters: j,b. ", "response": "sices", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e. Absents letters: a,y,r,j,b. ", "response": "sices", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,l. Absents letters: m,a,o,r,y,t,j,b. ", "response": "skie", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,l. Absents letters: r,y,n,j,b,m,o,t,a. ", "response": "shile", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,h,w. Absents letters: s,y. ", "response": "boh", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,h,w. Absents letters: k,s,y,e,l,a. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,o,h,w. Absents letters: y,e,k,s,l,a. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: w,o,h,r. Absents letters: y,e,k,m,s,l,a. ", "response": "warbs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n. Absents letters: i,k,g. ", "response": "lohan", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u,n. Absents letters: i,k,r,e,g,t,b. ", "response": "nulla", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,a,u. Absents letters: i,r,e,y,b,k,m,g,t. ", "response": "saris", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n,a,u. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,b,k,m,g,t. ", "response": "sna", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n. Absents letters: o,c. ", "response": "sents", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n. Absents letters: f,o,r,c,u. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n,d. Absents letters: f,m,o,a,r,c,u. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n,d. Absents letters: r,c,m,o,a,f,u. ", "response": "seend", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,o,f,w. ", "response": "gnats", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,o,v,t,l,f,w. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,y,b,w,o,v,t,l,f. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,y,j,b,w,o,v,g,t,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "sared", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: k,s,y,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: y,b,k,m,s,g,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,t. Absents letters: y,b,k,m,s,o,g,l,d. ", "response": "heame", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,t. Absents letters: i,y,b,k,m,s,o,v,g,l,d. ", "response": "niter", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: l,c,g,n. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,d. Absents letters: f,g,e,n,l,c. ", "response": "dud", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,u,d. Absents letters: e,n,c,k,s,a,g,l,f. ", "response": "dj", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,u,d. Absents letters: y,e,n,c,k,f,s,g,l,a. ", "response": "maril", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,s. Absents letters: m,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,s. Absents letters: i,m,k,r,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,l. Absents letters: i,k,m,r,b,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,l,p. Absents letters: i,r,e,b,k,m,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: l,m,h. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,u. Absents letters: m,e,t,l,h. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,u. Absents letters: i,e,h,m,o,t,l,f. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,u. Absents letters: i,e,n,b,h,m,o,t,l,f. ", "response": "gares", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: o,d,y,t. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,e. Absents letters: o,y,t,h,d. ", "response": "alate", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n,l,a. Absents letters: m,o,y,t,h,d. ", "response": "alane", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n,l,a. Absents letters: y,z,c,h,m,o,t,d. ", "response": "alane", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,k,y,l. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h,e. Absents letters: i,k,y,l,c,a,w. ", "response": "shale", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,b,h. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,w,k,l,a. ", "response": "bes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t,b,h. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,c,w,k,o,l,a. ", "response": "bets", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: w,h,r. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,n. Absents letters: s,r,a,h,w. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,n. Absents letters: r,b,h,w,s,t,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,n. Absents letters: r,y,b,h,w,s,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: k,s,b,u. ", "response": "naked", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: y,b,c,k,s,o,a,u. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: y,c,b,k,m,s,o,l,a,u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: y,b,c,w,k,m,s,o,l,a,u. ", "response": "ner", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: l,o,t. ", "response": "boons", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,n. Absents letters: i,o,t,l,d. ", "response": "shand", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n,a. Absents letters: i,o,t,l,j,b,d. ", "response": "nares", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n,a. Absents letters: i,y,j,b,o,t,l,p,d. ", "response": "sna", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: i,m,u,l. ", "response": "mungs", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,n. Absents letters: i,m,l,u,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,n. Absents letters: i,m,l,c,a,u,d. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,n. Absents letters: i,y,c,b,m,v,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,j,o,n. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,o,n,t,j. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,j,w,o,t. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,j,c,h,w,k,o,t. ", "response": "gales", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,m,o,r,p. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,r,j,m,o,g,p,d. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,r,j,m,o,g,p,d. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,a. Absents letters: i,r,j,k,m,o,t,g,l,p,d. ", "response": "seaze", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n. Absents letters: i,w,y. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n,t. Absents letters: i,y,a,h,w. ", "response": "seents", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t,s,e,n. Absents letters: i,y,r,a,h,w,u. ", "response": "tents", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,s,e,t. Absents letters: i,y,r,h,w,k,p,a,u. ", "response": "stent", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: d,u,n,z. ", "response": "loche", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: q,n,z,f,a,u,d. ", "response": "shog", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: i,q,y,n,z,a,f,u,d. ", "response": "shogs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h,e. Absents letters: i,q,y,z,n,f,g,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "shrug", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,g. Absents letters: l. ", "response": "sags", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,g. Absents letters: l,x,e,t. ", "response": "gagin", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,g,a. Absents letters: x,e,t,l,b. ", "response": "skags", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,g. Absents letters: x,e,t,l,b. ", "response": "skags", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,s,a,t. ", "response": "rorie", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,e. Absents letters: c,s,o,t,l,a. ", "response": "heath", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,e. Absents letters: c,o,s,t,l,a. ", "response": "heath", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,e. Absents letters: c,m,o,s,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "heath", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: l,m,p,y. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,h. Absents letters: m,y,r,e,l,p. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,h. Absents letters: r,y,e,x,m,o,t,l,p. ", "response": "shah", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,h. Absents letters: x,y,r,e,c,m,o,t,l,p. ", "response": "shah", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: m,y,z. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: m,o,y,e,z,w. ", "response": "tices", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: y,e,z,r,w,m,o,s,d. ", "response": "gil", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,c,a. Absents letters: r,y,e,z,w,m,o,s,p,d. ", "response": "biac", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: y,e,t,c,u. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,y,e,n,c,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "seifs", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,r,c,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o. Absents letters: i,r,y,e,n,z,c,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: p,y,e,t. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,w. Absents letters: m,o,y,e,t,p. ", "response": "warms", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,w. Absents letters: y,e,n,m,o,g,t,p. ", "response": "warbs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,w. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,m,o,p,g,t,d. ", "response": "swarm", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: m,s,b,t. ", "response": "boomy", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,d. Absents letters: i,m,s,t,l,b. ", "response": "doven", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,d. Absents letters: i,b,m,s,t,l. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,d. Absents letters: i,b,c,m,s,t,l,u. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,o,g. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e. Absents letters: o,g,l,a,d. ", "response": "tices", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e. Absents letters: f,o,y,g,l,a,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,k,r,e. Absents letters: y,c,o,a,s,g,l,p,f,d. ", "response": "kiter", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: p,d,t. ", "response": "bider", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: m,t,p,b,c,u,d. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e. Absents letters: c,b,m,o,v,t,p,u,d. ", "response": "bry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e. Absents letters: b,c,w,m,o,v,s,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "rej", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: s,t. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: s,y,n,t,b,u. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,a. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,b,s,t,u,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,l,c,a. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,b,s,t,u,d. ", "response": "molca", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,r,e,a,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: i,s,r,e,g,a,d. ", "response": "hunk", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: i,r,e,w,s,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,h. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,w,s,g,l,t,a,d. ", "response": "whim", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,s,r,e. ", "response": "fad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,e,c,m,s,l. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,e,c,m,s,o,g,l,t,u. ", "response": "hunk", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d. Absents letters: r,e,y,c,b,m,s,o,g,l,t,u. ", "response": "fad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m. Absents letters: a,n. ", "response": "munge", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s. Absents letters: o,n,c,a,u. ", "response": "bum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,s. Absents letters: o,a,r,e,n,c,u. ", "response": "sma", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,s. Absents letters: r,e,n,c,b,o,a,u. ", "response": "sma", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: s,a,e,t. ", "response": "brume", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n. Absents letters: i,s,e,t,l,a. ", "response": "boong", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u,n. Absents letters: i,e,b,c,s,t,l,a. ", "response": "porns", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u,n. Absents letters: i,e,c,b,h,s,t,l,a. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: s,y,d. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: s,y,r,a,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: r,y,s,t,p,a,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,e. Absents letters: y,r,s,o,t,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,y,g,a,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: y,m,o,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: y,m,o,g,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: y,m,o,g,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "bries", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n. Absents letters: k,e. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y,n. Absents letters: k,v,e,p. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,n,l,a. Absents letters: k,m,s,v,e,p. ", "response": "nud", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,y,n. Absents letters: i,r,e,k,m,s,v,p. ", "response": "nal", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: l,c,r,u. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,y,c,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: y,r,c,v,t,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "gides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,o,e. Absents letters: r,y,c,v,t,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "kops", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,b. Absents letters: i,k,t. ", "response": "bayed", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,b,a. Absents letters: i,k,s,e,t,f. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,l,b,a. Absents letters: i,k,s,e,t,f. ", "response": "brond", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,l,b,a. Absents letters: i,e,z,k,s,t,f,u. ", "response": "brond", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s. Absents letters: i,a,c. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,o. Absents letters: i,a,n,c. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,o,e. Absents letters: i,a,n,c,h,d. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,o,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,h,f,a,d. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: o,g. ", "response": "slily", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: o,v,e,g. ", "response": "slur", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: e,z,k,o,v,g,t,u. ", "response": "slunk", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: e,z,n,h,w,k,o,v,g,t,u. ", "response": "slur", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,y,u,g. ", "response": "nark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,e,n,g,l,f,u. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,e,n,m,g,l,f,u. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,e,n,r,b,m,g,l,f,u. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: i,f,e,g. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,u. Absents letters: i,a,y,e,g,p,f. ", "response": "birs", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,u. Absents letters: i,y,e,f,o,g,p,a. ", "response": "birs", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,u. Absents letters: i,y,e,o,a,t,g,p,f. ", "response": "skull", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,j,o. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: i,o,v,j,d. ", "response": "arvee", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,a. Absents letters: i,o,v,s,l,j,w,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: i,j,w,m,o,v,s,l,d. ", "response": "tater", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: k,p,o,s. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,w,k,o,s,l,p,d. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,e,h,w,k,m,o,s,l,p,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: y,e,n,h,w,k,m,o,s,g,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "maron", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a. Absents letters: s,o,n. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a,e. Absents letters: s,o,n,d. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a,e. Absents letters: i,y,n,z,s,o,p,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a,e. Absents letters: i,y,z,n,s,o,g,p,d. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: o,s,b. ", "response": "enact", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t. Absents letters: o,s,r,y,b,d. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,t. Absents letters: y,r,b,k,o,s,a,d. ", "response": "thymi", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n,t. Absents letters: r,y,b,k,o,s,a,u,d. ", "response": "tinas", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,p,a,n. ", "response": "sewel", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,n,m,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "titch", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: i,n,c,m,o,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,n,c,m,o,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "siler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,o,d,t. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: i,e,o,t,d. ", "response": "shams", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: v,h. Absents letters: i,o,y,e,t,c,d. ", "response": "shags", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: v,h. Absents letters: i,y,e,c,k,o,t,p,d. ", "response": "shags", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: m,o,s,t. ", "response": "sting", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: h,w,m,o,s,t,p,u. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: r,h,w,m,o,s,t,p,u. ", "response": "leaze", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e,d. Absents letters: r,y,h,w,m,o,s,t,p,u. ", "response": "lede", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u. Absents letters: d. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u,t. Absents letters: i,y,n,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u,t. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,w,v,d. ", "response": "taut", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t,a,u. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,h,w,o,v,d. ", "response": "sitar", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: t,s,c,n. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: f,s,n,l,t,c,h. ", "response": "aglee", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: n,c,h,k,s,o,t,l,p,f. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,y,n,c,h,k,s,o,t,l,p,f. ", "response": "agaze", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: c,r,e. ", "response": "stol", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: o,r,e,t,c. ", "response": "ala", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,h,k,o,t. ", "response": "gals", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,h,k,o,s,t. ", "response": "galvo", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: s,y,n. ", "response": "oj", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,b,r,e. Absents letters: s,y,n,a,d. ", "response": "boiler", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e,b. Absents letters: s,y,n,a,d. ", "response": "boke", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,b,r,e. Absents letters: y,n,s,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "boke", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s. Absents letters: i,a,n. ", "response": "bops", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,o. Absents letters: i,f,n,l,a,w. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,t,p. Absents letters: i,n,c,h,w,f,l,a,u. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,e,t,p. Absents letters: i,n,c,h,w,a,l,f,u. ", "response": "stoep", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: o,c,r,a. ", "response": "bling", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: r,n,c,o,a,d. ", "response": "tiled", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: r,n,c,o,s,a,u,d. ", "response": "leaze", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: r,n,c,o,s,g,a,u,d. ", "response": "leger", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,u. Absents letters: m,r. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u,e. Absents letters: i,m,r,y,l,h. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,a,u. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,c,h,m,o,l. ", "response": "sax", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,a,u. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,c,h,m,o,s,v,l. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,v,r,e. ", "response": "wuss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u,t. Absents letters: v,r,e,l,c. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u,t. Absents letters: i,s,v,r,e,l,c,d. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,s,v,o,l,d. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: l,m,a. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: m,y,n,l,c,a. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,y,n,c,f,m,l,p,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,c,b,m,a,l,p,f. ", "response": "shelf", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n. Absents letters: r,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,n. Absents letters: r,y,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,n,l. Absents letters: k,f,y,r,c,a,d. ", "response": "enols", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,e,n. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,k,a,s,g,f,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,a,u,t. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: m,n,t,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,e. Absents letters: m,y,n,t,a,h,u. ", "response": "sieve", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,e. Absents letters: y,n,h,w,m,t,p,a,u. ", "response": "loof", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: s,c,h,u. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: s,c,h,u,d. ", "response": "leish", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,e. Absents letters: s,o,b,c,h,u,d. ", "response": "leish", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,l. Absents letters: b,c,h,s,o,u,d. ", "response": "ler", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,m,p,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,y,c,m,s,l,p,d. ", "response": "aguti", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,y,c,m,s,t,l,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "aglee", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,a,e. Absents letters: i,y,c,m,s,t,l,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,t. Absents letters: u. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,s,t. Absents letters: e,g,n,b,u. ", "response": "boast", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,t,a. Absents letters: g,e,n,l,b,u. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,t,a. Absents letters: i,e,n,b,g,l,u. ", "response": "boart", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: s,v,u. ", "response": "karri", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,r. Absents letters: s,v,n,h,u. ", "response": "stalk", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,r. Absents letters: n,h,s,v,t,p,u. ", "response": "alary", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,l,a. Absents letters: i,n,h,s,v,t,p,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: o,h,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,t. Absents letters: o,g,a,h,d. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,r,e,t. Absents letters: o,g,l,c,a,h,d. ", "response": "metic", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,r,e,t. Absents letters: y,c,h,o,g,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "merit", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: s,o,b. ", "response": "bry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: s,o,c,b,h. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,r. Absents letters: y,n,j,b,c,h,s,o,u. ", "response": "karri", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,r. Absents letters: y,n,j,c,b,h,w,s,o,g,u. ", "response": "kro", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: m,o,c. ", "response": "gnats", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: m,o,r,t,p,c. ", "response": "boors", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,w. Absents letters: k,m,o,i,r,t,p,c. ", "response": "swads", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,w. Absents letters: i,r,c,b,k,m,o,t,p. ", "response": "warms", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: s,f,z. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: e,z,n,s,o,l,f,d. ", "response": "kib", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: e,n,z,c,h,s,o,a,l,f,d. ", "response": "biff", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: e,z,n,c,h,f,s,o,l,a,d. ", "response": "tich", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: m,o,c,u. ", "response": "bough", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,h. Absents letters: m,o,e,b,c,u. ", "response": "shags", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,l,p,h. Absents letters: r,e,c,b,k,m,o,u. ", "response": "hells", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,l,p,a,h. Absents letters: r,e,b,c,k,m,o,u. ", "response": "pals", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: l,p,i. ", "response": "shute", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: i,m,r,e,l,p. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u. Absents letters: i,r,e,m,g,l,p. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,u,b. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,k,m,s,g,l,p. ", "response": "boart", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,f,x,n. ", "response": "fax", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,x,n,s,a,f. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,x,n,c,f,s,t,a. ", "response": "bling", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,x,n,c,s,a,o,t,f. ", "response": "seamy", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: f,y,r,e,a. ", "response": "kills", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,y,e,h,f,s,a. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k. Absents letters: y,r,e,h,s,a,o,f. ", "response": "tik", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k. Absents letters: i,r,y,e,h,f,m,s,o,a,d. ", "response": "tik", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: s,c,u,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: x,n,c,s,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,o. Absents letters: x,n,c,h,s,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "bough", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,o,b,e. Absents letters: i,x,n,c,h,m,s,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "boke", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: s,b,r. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,s,r,g,b. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,r,b,c,h,s,g,t,u. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,b,h,s,g,t,f,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: k,y,r,z,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,p. Absents letters: k,y,r,z,n,t,a. ", "response": "spink", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,p,e. Absents letters: y,r,z,n,k,o,t,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,p. Absents letters: r,y,n,z,b,k,o,t,a. ", "response": "spine", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,n. Absents letters: i,s,h. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,l,e,n. Absents letters: i,s,o,z,a,h. ", "response": "nke", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,e,n,l. Absents letters: i,r,y,z,c,h,s,o,a. ", "response": "kend", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,e,n,l. Absents letters: i,y,r,z,c,h,s,o,a. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: i,r,e. ", "response": "tifts", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: i,m,o,r,e,n,j. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,j,c,w,m,o. ", "response": "thugs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,h,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,j,c,w,m,o. ", "response": "thale", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s. Absents letters: i,u,l. ", "response": "spy", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s. Absents letters: i,e,c,w,t,l,u. ", "response": "spume", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,a,r. Absents letters: i,e,c,w,v,t,l,u. ", "response": "paras", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,a,r. Absents letters: i,e,c,w,v,t,l,u,d. ", "response": "porns", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,b,f. ", "response": "sages", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,n,b,h,m,a,f,u. ", "response": "siler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,d. Absents letters: i,n,b,h,f,m,s,l,a,u. ", "response": "dared", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,r,e,d. Absents letters: i,n,b,h,m,s,a,o,t,l,f,u. ", "response": "preed", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: f,e. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,t,a. Absents letters: p,f,r,e. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,t,a. Absents letters: q,r,e,p,f,u. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,t,a. Absents letters: q,r,e,m,p,f,u. ", "response": "boast", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,k,m,e,l. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,u. Absents letters: i,k,m,e,l,b,h. ", "response": "trash", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,u. Absents letters: i,e,n,b,h,k,m,l,p. ", "response": "bards", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,u. Absents letters: i,e,n,b,h,k,m,v,l,p. ", "response": "dors", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a. Absents letters: o,c. ", "response": "mau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a. Absents letters: i,o,s,p,c. ", "response": "mau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a. Absents letters: i,o,s,p,c,u. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a,n. Absents letters: i,o,s,p,c,u. ", "response": "manna", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: m,h,r,u. ", "response": "pieta", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: r,y,h,m,t,u,d. ", "response": "pas", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: y,r,n,c,h,m,o,g,t,u,d. ", "response": "pales", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,l,a. Absents letters: r,y,n,c,h,m,o,g,t,u,d. ", "response": "plo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: r,e,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,a. Absents letters: r,e,g,b,d. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,a. Absents letters: r,e,n,b,g,p,u,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,a. Absents letters: r,e,n,b,o,g,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "loirs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,u. Absents letters: k,s,g. ", "response": "cuing", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,r,u. Absents letters: k,s,e,g,n,t. ", "response": "coral", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,c,u. Absents letters: e,n,k,s,p,g,t. ", "response": "corni", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,l,c,u. Absents letters: e,n,k,s,t,g,p,a. ", "response": "shirk", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: l,y,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: y,e,s,g,l,u,d. ", "response": "porns", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,b,r. Absents letters: y,e,s,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "boogy", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,n,c,b. Absents letters: y,e,s,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "boors", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: o,f,r,s. ", "response": "loche", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: r,e,o,s,a,l,f,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,g. Absents letters: r,e,n,f,o,s,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "gomer", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t,h,g. Absents letters: r,e,n,o,s,a,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "gith", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: s,c,u,t. ", "response": "tules", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,r. Absents letters: s,t,c,h,w,u. ", "response": "sting", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,r. Absents letters: i,n,c,h,w,s,t,f,u,d. ", "response": "leary", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,r. Absents letters: i,y,n,c,h,w,s,t,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "leare", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o. Absents letters: s,h,w. ", "response": "loath", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,e. Absents letters: s,r,h,w. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y,e,l. Absents letters: m,s,r,h,w. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y,e,l. Absents letters: i,m,s,v,r,h,w. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,g. Absents letters: j,o,n. ", "response": "tiger", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,g. Absents letters: e,n,j,w,o,t,a. ", "response": "gin", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,g. Absents letters: e,n,j,w,m,o,t,a. ", "response": "shog", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,g,p. Absents letters: y,e,n,j,w,m,o,t,a. ", "response": "gip", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: w,y,e,d. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,m,o,r. Absents letters: y,e,a,w,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,r,l. Absents letters: y,e,c,w,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "moyle", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,o,r,l. Absents letters: y,e,n,c,w,k,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: a,d. ", "response": "tires", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,r,e. Absents letters: t,c,a,d. ", "response": "shura", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,r,u. Absents letters: c,k,t,a,d. ", "response": "shier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,r,e. Absents letters: c,h,k,t,a,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: l,a,g. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: y,n,w,o,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: y,r,n,w,o,g,l,t,a,u. ", "response": "bes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: r,y,n,w,o,v,g,l,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "sices", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,e. Absents letters: l,b,h. ", "response": "cask", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,c,e. Absents letters: o,l,j,b,h,w. ", "response": "sces", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e,c. Absents letters: y,j,b,h,w,o,l. ", "response": "sace", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e,c. Absents letters: i,y,j,b,h,w,o,l. ", "response": "cared", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,e. Absents letters: l,a,t. ", "response": "bared", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b,e. Absents letters: k,g,t,l,a. ", "response": "bices", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b,e. Absents letters: k,g,l,t,a,u. ", "response": "bise", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,b. Absents letters: k,m,o,g,l,t,a,u. ", "response": "boise", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: p,s,o. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,s,o,v,p,d. ", "response": "karzy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,n,k,s,o,v,p,d. ", "response": "karzy", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,n,c,k,o,s,v,p,u,d. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: o,y,s. ", "response": "enact", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: i,y,o,s,l,d. ", "response": "tifts", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: i,y,n,w,o,s,l,d. ", "response": "pieta", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,w,o,s,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "bant", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: a,y,l,b,d. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: y,r,b,c,w,l,a,d. ", "response": "bum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: r,y,n,c,b,w,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "gog", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: y,r,n,b,c,w,g,t,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: p,s,y,n. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: y,n,s,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "shake", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: y,n,k,s,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: y,n,c,k,s,t,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: y,r,e,d. ", "response": "kus", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: m,o,z,r,y,e,d. ", "response": "stol", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: y,r,z,e,b,m,o,d. ", "response": "kills", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: r,y,e,z,b,m,o,g,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,i. Absents letters: k,s,n. ", "response": "oorie", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,i. Absents letters: x,e,n,k,s,o,t,d. ", "response": "vinyl", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,i. Absents letters: x,e,n,h,k,s,o,t,d. ", "response": "limax", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,i. Absents letters: x,e,n,h,k,m,s,o,f,t,a,d. ", "response": "seh", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: f. Absents letters: i,o,q,u. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: f,e. Absents letters: i,q,n,c,h,o,u. ", "response": "fidge", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: f,e. Absents letters: i,q,n,c,h,o,v,g,a,u. ", "response": "fyt", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: f,e. Absents letters: i,q,n,j,c,h,k,o,v,g,a,u,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: m,s,r,d. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,r,w,m,s,v,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,w,m,s,v,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,l,a. Absents letters: i,r,n,w,m,s,v,p,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,d. Absents letters: o,r. ", "response": "sod", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,d. Absents letters: i,f,o,r,b. ", "response": "ped", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,a,d. Absents letters: i,f,o,r,g,b,u. ", "response": "pests", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,a,d. Absents letters: i,r,b,k,o,g,f,u. ", "response": "sewed", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,y,a,r. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: m,r,y,t,p,a. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,n,m,t,p,a. ", "response": "skeg", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,u. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,r,m,t,p,a. ", "response": "skags", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,d. Absents letters: i,r. ", "response": "mated", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,d. Absents letters: i,t,r,x. ", "response": "dices", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,e,d. Absents letters: i,x,r,t,l,a,h. ", "response": "syed", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,e,d. Absents letters: i,x,r,h,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,n. Absents letters: v,e. ", "response": "gon", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,n. Absents letters: k,v,r,e,c. ", "response": "alans", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,n. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,b,k,v,f. ", "response": "alans", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,a,n. Absents letters: i,r,e,b,c,k,o,v,f,u,d. ", "response": "loans", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: f,s,b,r. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,d. Absents letters: r,y,e,b,w,s,t,f. ", "response": "cadgy", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,a,u,d. Absents letters: y,r,e,b,c,w,s,o,t,f. ", "response": "bun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,a,u,d. Absents letters: r,y,e,c,b,w,s,o,g,t,f. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m. Absents letters: i,a,y,t. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,g,t,p,a. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,t,g,p,a. ", "response": "omega", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,s,t,g,p,a. ", "response": "moep", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,p,o,e. ", "response": "slily", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,u. Absents letters: i,o,e,n,p. ", "response": "slur", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,u. Absents letters: i,o,r,e,n,p,f. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,u. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,m,o,a,p,f. ", "response": "slush", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: p,s,e. ", "response": "karzy", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: m,s,e,n,p,a,u. ", "response": "tic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,c,r. Absents letters: e,n,h,m,s,g,p,a,u. ", "response": "tic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,c,r. Absents letters: x,e,n,b,h,w,m,s,g,p,a,u. ", "response": "tic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,a,r,c,h. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: r,c,h,b,m,o,a,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,e,b,c,h,m,o,g,a,u. ", "response": "skull", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: r,e,n,c,b,h,w,m,o,g,a,u. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,a,n,g. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,r,e,n,b,g,a,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,b,c,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "shale", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,x,b,c,k,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "shale", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,g,n,u,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: o,g,n,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,n,o,s,g,u,d. ", "response": "plane", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,n,c,h,m,o,s,g,u,d. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: a,f,r,d. ", "response": "shake", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: a,s,r,n,f,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: r,n,k,s,a,g,f,u,d. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,y,e. Absents letters: r,x,n,h,k,f,s,g,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,r,e. Absents letters: a,t. ", "response": "corer", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,r,e. Absents letters: v,n,t,a. ", "response": "corni", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,r,e. Absents letters: v,n,t,l,a. ", "response": "bry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,c,r,e. Absents letters: s,v,n,l,t,a. ", "response": "crier", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,s,e,n,p. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u. Absents letters: i,s,t,e,n,p. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,u,d. Absents letters: i,e,n,m,s,t,p. ", "response": "maror", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,u,d. Absents letters: i,e,n,c,h,m,s,o,g,t,p. ", "response": "marra", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d. Absents letters: k,o,c,s. ", "response": "nid", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,d. Absents letters: c,k,o,s,l,u. ", "response": "heald", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,d. Absents letters: e,c,b,w,k,o,s,l,u. ", "response": "shift", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,r,d. Absents letters: e,b,c,w,k,o,s,l,u. ", "response": "heald", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: h,t. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: l,h,t. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,d. Absents letters: k,o,t,l,h,u. ", "response": "dared", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,d. Absents letters: r,h,k,m,o,t,l,u. ", "response": "wad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: d,c,n. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,g,a,u. Absents letters: m,n,l,c,d. ", "response": "enate", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,g,a,u. Absents letters: m,n,l,p,c,d. ", "response": "gou", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,g,a,u. Absents letters: n,j,c,b,m,o,l,p,d. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s. Absents letters: a,r. ", "response": "mumps", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s. Absents letters: r,e,n,a. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,o,t. Absents letters: k,r,e,n,a. ", "response": "motis", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,o,t. Absents letters: k,r,e,n,a,u. ", "response": "moyl", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: s,h,d. ", "response": "limen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: s,o,v,h,u,d. ", "response": "stair", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,l,a. Absents letters: s,o,v,p,h,w,u,d. ", "response": "limen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,l. Absents letters: h,w,s,o,v,p,u,d. ", "response": "limax", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,m,p,u. ", "response": "pengo", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: i,n,m,o,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r. Absents letters: i,n,w,m,o,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,a. Absents letters: i,x,e,n,w,m,o,l,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "boart", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: i,a,b,d. ", "response": "bh", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,t. Absents letters: i,a,s,b,h,u,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t,n. Absents letters: i,z,b,h,s,a,u,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,t. Absents letters: i,z,b,h,s,o,a,u,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: g,t,a,h,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: r,e,n,h,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "skull", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,b,h,f,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "skull", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,y,b,h,a,g,t,f,u,d. ", "response": "bungs", "reward": -6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: s,r,e,d. ", "response": "pengo", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: r,e,s,v,u,d. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y. Absents letters: r,e,x,s,v,p,u,d. ", "response": "pygal", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y. Absents letters: i,x,r,e,c,s,v,p,u,d. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,s,f,l. ", "response": "bride", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,r,e. Absents letters: i,s,o,l,f,h. ", "response": "mered", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,r,e,a. Absents letters: i,k,s,o,n,l,f,h. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,r,e,a. Absents letters: i,n,b,h,k,o,s,l,f. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: h,w,e. ", "response": "roopy", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: y,e,n,p,h,w. ", "response": "gry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: y,e,n,c,h,w,k,p. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: y,e,n,c,h,w,k,l,p. ", "response": "gry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,s. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,s,t. ", "response": "nark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,s,o,t,l,h. ", "response": "arame", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,h,s,o,t,l,d. ", "response": "karri", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: o,c,a. ", "response": "slily", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,e. Absents letters: m,o,a,r,c. ", "response": "kel", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,e. Absents letters: m,o,a,v,r,p,c. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,l. Absents letters: r,n,c,m,o,v,p,a. ", "response": "seels", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,t. Absents letters: l,h. ", "response": "stots", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,t. Absents letters: m,g,l,a,h,u. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,t. Absents letters: r,y,h,m,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,e,t. Absents letters: y,r,h,m,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: l,a,b. ", "response": "siers", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e. Absents letters: a,s,z,l,b. ", "response": "rogu", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e. Absents letters: i,z,n,b,f,s,l,a. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e. Absents letters: i,n,z,b,k,s,a,g,l,f. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y. Absents letters: k,o,l. ", "response": "sy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y. Absents letters: k,o,e,l,p. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,t. Absents letters: k,o,e,n,l,p,a. ", "response": "gyt", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,d,y,t. Absents letters: r,e,n,k,m,o,l,p,a. ", "response": "gourd", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: v,r. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: v,r,g,l,f. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: r,y,k,a,v,g,l,f. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: y,r,k,f,v,g,l,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: i,a,w. ", "response": "sne", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n. Absents letters: i,f,v,r,a,w. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u,n. Absents letters: i,r,b,w,f,v,t,a. ", "response": "unco", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u,n. Absents letters: i,r,b,h,w,a,v,s,t,f. ", "response": "moony", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,u. Absents letters: b,r. ", "response": "plo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,u. Absents letters: f,o,r,y,b,w. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,a,u. Absents letters: f,o,y,r,n,b,w. ", "response": "maril", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,a,u. Absents letters: i,r,y,n,b,w,o,t,l,f. ", "response": "sma", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: c,a,b,r. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e. Absents letters: k,m,r,c,b,a. ", "response": "shirk", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e. Absents letters: r,c,b,k,m,a. ", "response": "sices", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,p. Absents letters: k,m,a,o,r,c,b,w. ", "response": "spine", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: p,o,y,t. ", "response": "skull", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b. Absents letters: y,r,c,k,o,t,p,a. ", "response": "locks", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b. Absents letters: i,r,y,c,w,k,m,o,t,p,a. ", "response": "boors", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,b,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,w,k,m,o,g,t,p,a. ", "response": "bices", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: a,u,n. ", "response": "sties", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: y,n,p,a,u. ", "response": "stol", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t. Absents letters: o,y,c,n,p,a,u. ", "response": "skets", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t. Absents letters: y,n,c,o,p,a,u. ", "response": "skets", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e. Absents letters: i,n. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,h,e. Absents letters: i,s,r,n. ", "response": "meath", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e,l,h. Absents letters: i,s,r,n,t,a. ", "response": "melon", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,m,h,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,s,t,p,a. ", "response": "limax", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: s,h,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: s,r,t,f,h,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,a. Absents letters: r,z,h,w,s,t,f,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,z,n,h,w,s,t,f,d. ", "response": "oval", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,k,s,z,a. ", "response": "nark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b. Absents letters: i,e,z,k,m,s,a,u. ", "response": "boing", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,n. Absents letters: i,e,z,c,k,m,s,a,u. ", "response": "bungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,b,n. Absents letters: i,r,e,z,j,c,k,m,s,a,u. ", "response": "boing", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,f,r,e. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,w,d. Absents letters: o,r,y,e,l,f,u. ", "response": "warbs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,w,d. Absents letters: y,r,e,n,c,o,t,l,f,u. ", "response": "warbs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,w,d. Absents letters: r,y,e,n,c,o,t,l,f,u. ", "response": "warbs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e,t. Absents letters: p. ", "response": "salet", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t,a. Absents letters: p,o,y,m. ", "response": "sesta", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t,a. Absents letters: i,m,o,y,p,u. ", "response": "tares", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t,a. Absents letters: i,m,o,y,r,p,u. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,k,s,t,c. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,k,s,o,t,c. ", "response": "nal", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,e,c,k,o,s,g,t,u,d. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,k,o,s,v,g,l,t,u,d. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: k,a,f,l. ", "response": "bings", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y. Absents letters: k,f,r,l,a. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y. Absents letters: k,a,r,l,f,h. ", "response": "sy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y. Absents letters: i,r,h,k,f,l,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: w,y,z. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,o,a. Absents letters: s,y,z,l,w. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,t,c. Absents letters: s,y,n,z,l,w,u. ", "response": "troop", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,t,c. Absents letters: i,y,n,z,h,w,s,l,u. ", "response": "troad", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: o,c,h. ", "response": "bonie", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: f,m,o,y,l,c,h. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,c,h,m,o,s,l,p,f. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a. Absents letters: y,e,c,h,m,o,s,l,p,f. ", "response": "kui", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,a,v,g. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,e,n,v,g,l,a. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,o,v,g,l,a. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,r,c,o,v,g,l,a. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u,t. Absents letters: h,g. ", "response": "toups", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u,t. Absents letters: i,v,z,r,g,h. ", "response": "tute", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,u,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,z,h,m,v,g,l. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,t,u. Absents letters: i,r,e,z,h,m,v,g,l. ", "response": "tatus", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,p,v. ", "response": "gourd", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,v,y,l,p. ", "response": "gares", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,v,y,e,l,p,u. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,y,e,j,v,l,p,u. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: i,o,v,g. ", "response": "nards", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,r. Absents letters: i,o,v,s,g,t. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,r,u. Absents letters: i,o,v,s,g,l,t,a,d. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,r,u. Absents letters: i,e,m,o,v,s,p,g,l,t,a,d. ", "response": "nark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,m,k. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,r,y,e,b,k,m,l. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,b,k,m,o,l,p. ", "response": "pans", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,b,c,k,m,o,t,l,p. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o. Absents letters: v,e,d. ", "response": "loath", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o. Absents letters: i,y,e,k,v,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,a. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,k,s,v,f,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n,l,a. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,k,s,v,f,d. ", "response": "galvo", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: m,s,o. ", "response": "bunya", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: k,m,s,o,t,w. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,n. Absents letters: w,k,m,s,o,g,t,f,u. ", "response": "nal", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n,l,a. Absents letters: y,w,k,m,s,o,p,g,t,f,u. ", "response": "alane", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,x,e,t,a. ", "response": "rogu", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,x,e,r,n,t,a,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,x,e,n,r,s,v,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,r,x,e,n,m,s,v,t,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,u,d. Absents letters: g,n. ", "response": "dj", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,u,d. Absents letters: o,g,r,n,c. ", "response": "quids", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,l,u,d. Absents letters: o,g,a,r,y,n,c. ", "response": "seifs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,l,u,d. Absents letters: y,r,n,c,o,s,g,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,e,d. Absents letters: a,r. ", "response": "bked", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,u,e,d. Absents letters: o,r,g,a,h. ", "response": "bued", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,b,u,d. Absents letters: m,o,r,g,a,h. ", "response": "bued", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,b,u,d. Absents letters: r,n,h,m,o,g,a. ", "response": "sebed", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,e. Absents letters: o,r,d. ", "response": "heath", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,h,e. Absents letters: i,k,o,r,y,d. ", "response": "peels", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,p,h. Absents letters: i,k,o,y,r,l,j,d. ", "response": "shops", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,p,h. Absents letters: i,y,r,j,k,o,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "sze", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: k,u,d. ", "response": "lobus", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,s,e. Absents letters: k,i,m,t,u,d. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,r,e. Absents letters: i,n,k,m,t,p,u,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,r,e. Absents letters: i,n,h,k,m,g,t,p,u,d. ", "response": "roes", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: i,m,n. ", "response": "marsh", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,t. Absents letters: i,m,o,n,p,d. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t,a. Absents letters: i,r,n,m,o,p,f,d. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t,a. Absents letters: i,r,n,w,m,o,p,f,d. ", "response": "sesta", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,a,v,n. ", "response": "guss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,n,k,v,t,p,a. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s. Absents letters: i,n,k,f,v,t,p,a. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,d. Absents letters: i,n,k,a,v,t,p,f. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: r,b,h,y. ", "response": "noles", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: m,y,r,b,h. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t,a. Absents letters: m,r,y,g,b,h. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t,a. Absents letters: y,r,b,h,c,k,m,g. ", "response": "pests", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: p,s,e,d. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: s,e,p,b,d. ", "response": "boart", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a. Absents letters: e,b,s,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,o,a. Absents letters: e,b,s,v,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "moyl", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: p,o,w. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,d. Absents letters: o,e,l,p,w. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,d. Absents letters: e,w,o,g,t,l,p. ", "response": "dades", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,a,d. Absents letters: e,w,k,o,t,g,l,p,f. ", "response": "sards", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e. Absents letters: d,v,n. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,f,e. Absents letters: v,g,n,a,d. ", "response": "loof", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,f,y,e. Absents letters: n,c,s,v,g,a,u,d. ", "response": "lofty", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y,e,f. Absents letters: r,n,c,m,s,v,g,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,r. Absents letters: e,t. ", "response": "boors", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,r. Absents letters: i,y,e,t. ", "response": "gores", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,r,w. Absents letters: i,k,y,e,t,a. ", "response": "wow", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,r,w. Absents letters: i,y,e,b,k,t,a. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: i,t,h,g. ", "response": "slily", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o. Absents letters: i,r,c,h,g,t,u. ", "response": "loche", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o. Absents letters: i,r,c,h,g,t,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,s. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,h,p,g,t,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t. Absents letters: o,a. ", "response": "slant", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,t. Absents letters: o,a,u,n. ", "response": "guss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,t. Absents letters: n,b,o,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "syt", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,e,t. Absents letters: n,b,m,o,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: s,w,e. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: e,w,s,o,g,p,d. ", "response": "bough", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: r,e,w,s,o,g,p,u,d. ", "response": "thaw", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: r,e,b,w,s,o,g,p,u,d. ", "response": "maron", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: s,f,t. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: k,s,o,r,e,t,f. ", "response": "dj", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: r,e,k,s,o,a,g,t,f. ", "response": "hight", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: r,e,n,k,f,s,o,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "hight", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: s,h,y. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,n. Absents letters: s,y,g,p,h,u. ", "response": "renew", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,n. Absents letters: y,h,s,o,g,p,u. ", "response": "niter", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,n. Absents letters: y,h,s,o,t,g,p,u. ", "response": "renew", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,u. Absents letters: c,r. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,e,t. Absents letters: o,a,r,l,c. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,s,u,t. Absents letters: i,o,a,r,l,p,c. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t,u. Absents letters: i,r,c,f,o,l,p,a. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: o,c,y,e. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,n. Absents letters: k,o,s,y,e,c,h. ", "response": "nark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,n. Absents letters: y,e,c,h,k,o,s,g,t. ", "response": "bran", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,n,a. Absents letters: y,e,c,h,k,o,s,g,t,d. ", "response": "nark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,a,r,c,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,a,r,t,b,c,d. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,r,y,c,b,m,t,p,a,d. ", "response": "shme", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,l. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,b,h,m,t,p,a,d. ", "response": "leese", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: q,r,u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: q,r,m,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: q,r,h,m,o,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t. Absents letters: q,r,h,m,o,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: o,r,d. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: m,o,r,t,u,d. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e. Absents letters: r,c,m,o,a,t,f,u,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e,n. Absents letters: r,c,f,m,o,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "sine", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,c,n,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: i,s,n,l,c,d. ", "response": "agave", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: i,s,n,l,c,d. ", "response": "aguti", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,b,a. Absents letters: i,s,n,l,c,d. ", "response": "boart", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,s,n. ", "response": "loast", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,m,s,n,a,h. ", "response": "bed", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,t,d. Absents letters: i,m,s,n,p,a,h. ", "response": "tiled", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d,e,t. Absents letters: i,y,n,h,m,s,p,a. ", "response": "bride", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u. Absents letters: m,s. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u,n. Absents letters: m,s,o,l,w. ", "response": "niter", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,n,a,u. Absents letters: m,s,o,e,t,l,c,w. ", "response": "nra", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,n,a,u. Absents letters: e,c,w,m,s,o,v,t,l,d. ", "response": "nra", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b. Absents letters: o,h,s. ", "response": "boath", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,e,n. Absents letters: m,o,s,y,a,h. ", "response": "blent", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,b,e,n. Absents letters: y,j,h,m,o,s,a. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,e,n,b. Absents letters: y,j,h,m,o,s,l,a. ", "response": "bine", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: k,p,a,u. ", "response": "gung", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,e,n,k,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,r. Absents letters: i,e,n,k,f,g,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "loirs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,r. Absents letters: i,e,n,h,w,k,a,g,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "moots", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: s,t. ", "response": "karri", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: s,o,t. ", "response": "karzy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,a,d. Absents letters: s,o,t,u. ", "response": "dared", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,a,d. Absents letters: m,s,o,e,t,u. ", "response": "warad", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: l,b,c. ", "response": "nates", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: k,o,l,b,c,h. ", "response": "wanes", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: b,c,h,k,m,o,g,l,u,d. ", "response": "sass", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: i,n,c,b,h,k,m,o,g,l,u,d. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: w,a,y,t. ", "response": "gus", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: k,y,e,t,b,a,w. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,o. Absents letters: y,e,b,w,k,t,l,a. ", "response": "gos", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,o. Absents letters: y,e,b,c,w,k,t,l,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b. Absents letters: l,u,e,g. ", "response": "boors", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,t. Absents letters: e,n,s,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,t. Absents letters: y,e,n,k,s,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "bh", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: b,r,t. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,k,s,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,m,s,n,a. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,m,s,f,n,t,a. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,n,h,m,s,a,t,f. ", "response": "dared", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,n,h,f,m,s,t,a. ", "response": "deked", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c. Absents letters: y,o,r,a. ", "response": "tic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,e,n. Absents letters: o,r,y,g,a. ", "response": "encyc", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,e,n. Absents letters: y,r,k,o,s,g,l,a. ", "response": "brier", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,e,n. Absents letters: r,y,h,k,o,s,g,l,t,a. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,e. Absents letters: o,r,g. ", "response": "pated", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,e. Absents letters: r,b,o,g,a. ", "response": "peep", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,e. Absents letters: r,y,n,j,b,o,g,a. ", "response": "tapes", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,u,e. Absents letters: y,r,n,j,b,o,g,a. ", "response": "pique", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,j,v,e. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,a. Absents letters: m,s,v,e,l,j,h. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,c. Absents letters: e,j,h,m,s,v,l,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,a,c. Absents letters: r,e,j,h,m,s,v,l,d. ", "response": "boatch", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: q,e,n,a,u. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: q,r,e,n,c,a,u,d. ", "response": "tich", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,b. Absents letters: q,r,e,n,c,s,a,u,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,b. Absents letters: q,r,e,n,c,m,s,a,u,d. ", "response": "boing", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,m,z,l,t. ", "response": "fad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y. Absents letters: i,m,o,z,l,t,u. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,e. Absents letters: i,r,z,h,m,o,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "yeg", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,y,e,n. Absents letters: i,r,z,h,k,m,o,t,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "guss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,d. Absents letters: l,p,a. ", "response": "doups", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,d. Absents letters: t,l,p,b,a. ", "response": "dork", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,d. Absents letters: a,s,t,l,p,b. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,d. Absents letters: e,b,s,t,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "dorm", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,p,o. Absents letters: i,x. ", "response": "pling", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,p,o. Absents letters: i,x,e,t,c,w. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,p,o. Absents letters: i,x,e,y,c,b,w,g,t. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,l,p. Absents letters: i,y,x,e,c,b,w,v,g,t,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s. Absents letters: m,u. ", "response": "elope", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s. Absents letters: k,m,e,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,h. Absents letters: q,r,e,k,m,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "shps", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,s,h. Absents letters: q,r,e,n,k,m,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "shog", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,a,e,z. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,u. Absents letters: m,r,e,z,a,d. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,u. Absents letters: r,e,z,h,m,o,p,a,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,u. Absents letters: r,e,z,n,h,m,o,t,p,a,d. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,n. Absents letters: a,x. ", "response": "moony", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,n. Absents letters: i,x,r,e,a,w. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,n. Absents letters: i,x,e,r,w,t,a. ", "response": "moons", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,n. Absents letters: i,x,e,r,w,m,t,a,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: l,o,y. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,u. Absents letters: i,o,s,y,n,l,c. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,u. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,c,o,s,l,d. ", "response": "warst", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,u. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,c,o,s,t,l,d. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: l,a,e,t. ", "response": "brins", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: r,e,k,f,t,l,a. ", "response": "sungs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: i,r,e,k,a,s,t,l,f. ", "response": "fuss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,n. Absents letters: i,q,r,e,k,f,s,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "nud", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,d. Absents letters: o,t. ", "response": "dared", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,y,a,d. Absents letters: o,h,u,t. ", "response": "dray", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,r,a,d. Absents letters: i,q,n,b,h,o,t,u. ", "response": "dray", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,y,a,d. Absents letters: i,q,n,b,h,k,o,s,t,u. ", "response": "dared", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: k,d,l. ", "response": "sages", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a,e. Absents letters: k,o,s,l,w,d. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a,e. Absents letters: w,k,o,s,t,l,f,d. ", "response": "maced", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a,e. Absents letters: h,w,k,o,s,g,t,l,f,d. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,m,c,h. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,y,z,c,h,m,f,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,y,r,z,c,h,b,m,f,u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,y,r,z,n,c,h,b,w,m,o,f,u. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: k,m,o,u. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: y,e,n,k,m,o,u,d. ", "response": "bungs", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: y,e,n,h,k,m,o,u,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,h,k,m,o,t,u,d. ", "response": "pans", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,n. Absents letters: r,e. ", "response": "kinks", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,n. Absents letters: r,e,y,d. ", "response": "pans", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,a,n. Absents letters: y,r,e,b,o,d. ", "response": "pinas", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,n,a. Absents letters: r,y,e,b,o,f,u,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,n. Absents letters: b,r,g. ", "response": "niche", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t,u,n. Absents letters: f,r,y,g,b. ", "response": "unt", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,s,u,t. Absents letters: f,k,m,o,y,r,g,b. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,n,t,u. Absents letters: i,y,r,b,k,m,o,a,g,l,f. ", "response": "sunt", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: d. Absents letters: l,a,e,z. ", "response": "diz", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,d. Absents letters: m,e,z,l,b,a. ", "response": "boody", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,d. Absents letters: e,z,b,w,f,m,t,l,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,d. Absents letters: e,z,n,b,w,m,a,s,t,l,p,f. ", "response": "dork", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: d,h,g. ", "response": "noles", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: m,g,t,h,d. ", "response": "bise", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: m,o,g,l,t,h,d. ", "response": "sared", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: x,h,m,o,g,l,t,d. ", "response": "sared", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: f,o,b,y. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: i,y,n,b,h,o,g,t,f. ", "response": "buss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r. Absents letters: i,y,n,b,h,c,o,p,g,l,t,f. ", "response": "ars", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r. Absents letters: i,y,n,b,h,c,o,t,g,l,p,f. ", "response": "ars", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e. Absents letters: k,d,t. ", "response": "boors", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e. Absents letters: k,i,n,t,u,d. ", "response": "tore", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e. Absents letters: i,y,n,k,s,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "moor", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,e,p. Absents letters: i,y,n,h,k,s,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "porge", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: m,f,e. ", "response": "loof", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,h,r. Absents letters: m,e,f,w. ", "response": "shaly", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,l,a,h. Absents letters: i,e,n,w,m,s,f. ", "response": "haler", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,h,r. Absents letters: i,e,n,w,m,s,o,t,f,d. ", "response": "shul", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: m,s,a,t. ", "response": "tharm", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: f,m,s,t,a,u. ", "response": "shaft", "reward": -6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,e,d. Absents letters: f,m,s,n,t,a,u. ", "response": "heald", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,e,d. Absents letters: y,n,c,m,s,a,t,f,u. ", "response": "hewed", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: k,s,a,r. ", "response": "loipe", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: r,k,s,v,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,g. Absents letters: r,k,s,v,a,u,d. ", "response": "tig", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,g. Absents letters: r,n,k,s,v,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "gog", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: c,h,r,d. ", "response": "nalla", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y,t. Absents letters: f,o,r,c,h,d. ", "response": "tanga", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y,t. Absents letters: i,r,c,h,o,s,g,f,d. ", "response": "pyats", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,y,t. Absents letters: i,r,e,z,c,h,b,o,s,g,f,d. ", "response": "tug", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,i,t. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r. Absents letters: i,y,t,l,d. ", "response": "sar", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r. Absents letters: i,y,c,o,t,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "ars", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r,e. Absents letters: i,y,c,o,t,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "sare", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,e. Absents letters: l,y,u. ", "response": "cared", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,e. Absents letters: m,s,y,l,p,u. ", "response": "crier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,e. Absents letters: y,f,m,s,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "cask", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,e. Absents letters: i,y,m,s,a,l,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: i,m,k,n. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,n,c,k,m,p,u. ", "response": "bower", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,n,c,k,m,s,o,p,u. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: i,n,j,c,k,m,s,o,t,l,p,u. ", "response": "rej", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: l,b,u,t. ", "response": "pores", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: x,b,o,t,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "nards", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: x,y,b,m,o,a,t,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "reef", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,e. Absents letters: y,x,b,f,m,o,t,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "siler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: y,t,l,c,u. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: y,e,c,k,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "dj", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: y,e,r,c,k,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: r,y,e,c,k,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a. Absents letters: h,u,t. ", "response": "maron", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a. Absents letters: g,r,t,h,u. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a. Absents letters: r,h,g,t,u. ", "response": "pash", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a. Absents letters: r,b,h,w,o,p,g,t,u. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: q,e,n,a,u. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: q,e,n,h,o,v,a,u. ", "response": "stich", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: q,r,e,n,h,w,o,v,g,a,u. ", "response": "stich", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: q,r,e,n,h,w,o,v,g,p,a,u. ", "response": "stich", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,m,t. ", "response": "arval", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: i,m,o,t,f. ", "response": "bares", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,a. Absents letters: i,m,o,t,f. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,a. Absents letters: i,m,o,t,l,f,u. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: m,b,u. ", "response": "maror", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: y,b,h,w,m,s,o,u. ", "response": "tater", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,r. Absents letters: y,e,z,n,b,h,w,m,s,o,u. ", "response": "tic", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,r,l. Absents letters: y,e,n,z,b,h,w,m,s,o,g,u,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: l,r,g. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,n. Absents letters: r,e,g,l,c,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,s,n. Absents letters: r,e,c,w,m,g,l,a. ", "response": "tines", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o,s,n. Absents letters: r,e,z,c,h,w,m,g,l,a,u. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: l,b,u,e. ", "response": "roopy", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: m,s,e,t,l,b,u. ", "response": "kef", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,r. Absents letters: e,b,m,s,t,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "arvee", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,a,r. Absents letters: e,b,m,s,o,t,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "arame", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,o,g,n,w. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t. Absents letters: i,o,g,n,c,w. ", "response": "pests", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t. Absents letters: i,n,c,b,w,o,g. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,t,a. Absents letters: i,n,c,b,w,o,g,l,p,d. ", "response": "setes", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,d,g. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: t,g,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e. Absents letters: h,o,p,g,l,t,u,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,e. Absents letters: n,h,o,t,g,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "shise", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,a. Absents letters: m,e. ", "response": "galas", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,a. Absents letters: i,m,r,e,b. ", "response": "boals", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,y,b,c,k,m,p. ", "response": "boets", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,a. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,n,b,c,w,k,m,p. ", "response": "pales", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u. Absents letters: r,l,y,g. ", "response": "fuck", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,u. Absents letters: y,r,o,g,l,f,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,u,e. Absents letters: i,r,y,n,c,o,g,l,p,f,d. ", "response": "sax", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,a,u. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,c,o,s,t,g,l,p,f,d. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: s,r,g. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u. Absents letters: s,r,e,g,b,f. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u. Absents letters: r,e,b,m,s,g,f. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,u. Absents letters: i,r,e,b,m,s,g,l,p,f. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: l,c,t. ", "response": "sices", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s. Absents letters: g,r,e,t,l,c,d. ", "response": "kiers", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,n,h. Absents letters: r,e,g,l,t,c,d. ", "response": "shin", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,y,n,h. Absents letters: r,e,c,g,l,t,u,d. ", "response": "shiny", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: i,h,e,t. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: i,r,e,h,k,s,t,f. ", "response": "jugal", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n. Absents letters: i,r,e,y,h,k,s,a,t,f. ", "response": "bungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,n. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,h,k,f,s,v,t,a. ", "response": "moong", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n. Absents letters: l,s,r. ", "response": "bant", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n. Absents letters: r,s,o,t,l,p. ", "response": "bing", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,n. Absents letters: i,r,m,s,o,t,l,p. ", "response": "niter", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,n. Absents letters: i,r,m,s,o,t,l,p,d. ", "response": "niger", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: l,o,g. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: o,g,l,p. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: m,o,t,g,l,p,h. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: h,m,o,g,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "bries", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m. Absents letters: o,c,s,a. ", "response": "bum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m. Absents letters: e,c,b,h,o,s,t,a. ", "response": "decks", "reward": -6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,p. Absents letters: e,b,c,h,k,o,s,t,a. ", "response": "porge", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,p. Absents letters: i,r,e,c,b,h,k,o,s,t,a. ", "response": "maror", "reward": -6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,a,n,c,h. ", "response": "sebum", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: i,m,a,n,c,h. ", "response": "gou", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,t. Absents letters: i,m,a,k,n,c,h. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,t. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,h,k,m,a. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: p,o,b,y. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: y,b,c,k,o,s,t,p. ", "response": "arame", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: y,c,b,k,o,s,t,p,d. ", "response": "leach", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: v,e,a. Absents letters: y,b,c,k,o,s,t,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "vina", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: s,o. ", "response": "ree", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: s,o,n,u,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: w,r,e. Absents letters: n,k,s,o,g,a,u,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,w,e. Absents letters: y,n,k,s,o,g,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "warre", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,o,r,c,u. ", "response": "gatch", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: r,e,c,w,m,o,a,u,d. ", "response": "tich", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: r,e,c,h,w,m,o,s,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: r,e,c,h,w,m,o,s,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "bling", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: w,o,r,d. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,e. Absents letters: o,s,r,y,b,w,d. ", "response": "bule", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,u. Absents letters: y,r,b,h,w,k,o,s,d. ", "response": "cuvee", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,e,n. Absents letters: r,y,j,b,h,w,k,o,s,d. ", "response": "enule", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,f,s. Absents letters: i,l. ", "response": "fuss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,f,s. Absents letters: i,e,n,l,c,a. ", "response": "bofs", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,f,s. Absents letters: i,e,n,c,h,l,a,u. ", "response": "loof", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,f,s. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,h,t,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,t. Absents letters: s. ", "response": "tol", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,t. Absents letters: i,s,y,g,p. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,t. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,s,g,p,a. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,t. Absents letters: i,y,r,n,c,s,g,p,a. ", "response": "boite", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,e,t,h,d. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: r,e,c,h,o,t,a,d. ", "response": "gil", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: r,e,y,c,h,k,o,t,a,d. ", "response": "boll", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,g. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,c,h,k,o,t,a,d. ", "response": "gil", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l. Absents letters: m,o,a. ", "response": "slily", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,i. Absents letters: m,o,r,j,a,h. ", "response": "seifs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,i. Absents letters: r,e,j,h,m,o,a,d. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,i. Absents letters: r,e,j,c,h,m,o,t,a,d. ", "response": "locks", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,n. Absents letters: k,s,r. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p,a,n. Absents letters: k,s,r,t. ", "response": "panax", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n,p,a. Absents letters: k,s,g,r,t,b,d. ", "response": "enep", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n,p,a. Absents letters: r,b,k,s,g,l,t,u,d. ", "response": "nappa", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: o,h,r,u. ", "response": "stich", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: o,r,l,c,h,u. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,a. Absents letters: r,c,h,b,o,t,l,u. ", "response": "gares", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: r,b,c,h,o,t,l,u. ", "response": "gares", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,a. Absents letters: c,e. ", "response": "s k", "reward": -13.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,a. Absents letters: s,e,n,c,h,u. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,a. Absents letters: x,e,n,y,c,h,s,o,p,u. ", "response": "kaval", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,a,r. Absents letters: y,x,e,n,c,h,s,o,t,p,u. ", "response": "karri", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: y,e,t. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,y,e,c,h,g,t. ", "response": "gou", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,c,h,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "skull", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,c,h,k,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "fuss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p. Absents letters: i,t. ", "response": "gyppy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p. Absents letters: i,a,r,t,b. ", "response": "pling", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p. Absents letters: i,r,z,b,h,g,t,a. ", "response": "preps", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: p. Absents letters: i,r,z,n,b,h,m,g,t,a. ", "response": "lep", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,p,u,d. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: k,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "tride", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: y,k,v,t,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: y,b,k,v,t,l,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,a,h,d. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e. Absents letters: s,r,a,h,d. ", "response": "mesoh", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,w,e. Absents letters: s,o,r,y,l,a,h,d. ", "response": "meower", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,w,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,h,s,o,l,a,d. ", "response": "warms", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h. Absents letters: o,s,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,e. Absents letters: o,s,r,a,d. ", "response": "heath", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,e. Absents letters: r,z,o,s,g,a,d. ", "response": "heuch", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,e. Absents letters: r,z,m,o,s,g,p,a,d. ", "response": "heuch", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,u. Absents letters: p,n. ", "response": "boets", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,u. Absents letters: p,b,n. ", "response": "skets", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,u. Absents letters: m,v,e,n,p,b,d. ", "response": "skugs", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,s,r,u. Absents letters: e,n,b,m,o,v,p,d. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,p,o,e. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: e,c,h,o,l,p,f. ", "response": "gad", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: e,c,h,o,s,l,p,f,u. ", "response": "karri", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: x,e,c,h,o,s,l,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "karri", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: s,c. ", "response": "arval", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,s,g,t,c,h. ", "response": "marae", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: i,y,c,h,s,g,l,t,f. ", "response": "arena", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: i,y,c,h,s,g,l,t,f. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,t. Absents letters: p. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,t. Absents letters: i,a,r,p,c,h. ", "response": "tonne", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,g,t,u. Absents letters: i,a,r,e,p,c,h. ", "response": "tugs", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,g,t,u. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,c,h,v,l,p,a. ", "response": "goust", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: w. Absents letters: p,y,e. ", "response": "wuss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,o,a,w. Absents letters: s,y,e,n,p. ", "response": "awash", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,a,w. Absents letters: y,e,n,s,l,p,d. ", "response": "boart", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: w,o,a,r. Absents letters: y,e,n,s,l,p,f,u,d. ", "response": "warre", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: m,o,r,s. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: r,m,o,s,l,f. ", "response": "tween", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: r,y,z,m,o,s,l,f,d. ", "response": "nix", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: y,r,z,m,o,s,v,l,f,d. ", "response": "cuvee", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: k,p,a,h. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: i,h,k,f,l,p,a. ", "response": "torot", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,s. Absents letters: i,z,h,k,m,a,l,p,f. ", "response": "roj", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,s. Absents letters: i,z,h,k,m,f,l,p,a. ", "response": "sewer", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: k,a,e,t. ", "response": "nurls", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h. Absents letters: i,e,z,k,t,a. ", "response": "shy", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,h. Absents letters: i,e,z,n,k,t,a,d. ", "response": "shy", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,o,h. Absents letters: i,e,n,z,b,k,t,l,a,d. ", "response": "booh", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: j,a,t. ", "response": "seaze", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n. Absents letters: m,t,c,j,a,h,u. ", "response": "sena", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n. Absents letters: j,c,h,m,t,a,u. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,n. Absents letters: i,j,c,h,b,m,t,l,a,u,d. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,n. Absents letters: k,a,e. ", "response": "roosa", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,l,r,n. Absents letters: k,v,e,c,a. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,n,l. Absents letters: k,a,v,s,o,e,c,h. ", "response": "liner", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,n,l. Absents letters: e,c,h,k,s,v,o,a. ", "response": "niter", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: f,b,r. ", "response": "sista", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: f,r,e,l,b,d. ", "response": "boons", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,t. Absents letters: f,k,r,e,l,b,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,t. Absents letters: r,e,b,c,h,w,k,l,f,d. ", "response": "salet", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: k,s,a,y. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,d. Absents letters: k,s,y,l,a. ", "response": "trend", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,d. Absents letters: i,y,k,m,s,l,a. ", "response": "dord", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r,d. Absents letters: i,y,b,k,m,s,l,a,u. ", "response": "dork", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s. Absents letters: i,t,g,n. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,g,t,h. ", "response": "fests", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,s,e. Absents letters: i,o,g,r,n,t,h,d. ", "response": "leves", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,l. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,h,o,g,t,f,d. ", "response": "sewel", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e. Absents letters: s,f,w. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: k,s,o,l,f,w. ", "response": "tater", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r,e,a. Absents letters: k,s,o,l,f,w,d. ", "response": "reef", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r,e. Absents letters: b,h,w,k,s,o,t,l,f,d. ", "response": "arvee", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,p,o,u. ", "response": "bark", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,a. Absents letters: o,s,e,l,p,w,u. ", "response": "ky", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,a,t. Absents letters: e,n,w,o,s,l,p,u. ", "response": "tik", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,a,t. Absents letters: e,n,w,s,o,l,p,u. ", "response": "tik", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: l,w,y,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,y,j,w,g,t,l,d. ", "response": "bough", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,j,w,k,g,l,t,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,y,e,r,n,j,w,k,s,g,l,t,d. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: s,w,e,t. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,d. Absents letters: s,o,g,e,t,w. ", "response": "cadgy", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,d. Absents letters: e,w,s,o,p,g,t. ", "response": "cadgy", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,d. Absents letters: r,e,w,s,o,p,g,t,u. ", "response": "cadgy", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,p,e. ", "response": "alib", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,o,s,r,e,t,p. ", "response": "galvo", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,o,s,t,p. ", "response": "plane", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,o,s,t,p. ", "response": "galvo", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: g. Absents letters: o,y,e. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: g. Absents letters: o,s,y,e,t. ", "response": "clung", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,g. Absents letters: y,e,c,o,s,t,l. ", "response": "gou", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,g. Absents letters: y,e,r,c,o,s,t,l,d. ", "response": "gou", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: o,q,r,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: q,r,n,h,o,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: c,e. Absents letters: q,r,n,h,o,s,a,u. ", "response": "brier", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,c,e. Absents letters: q,r,n,h,o,s,t,a,u. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: j,a,h. ", "response": "sewer", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: j,a,h. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: n,j,a,h,b. ", "response": "gry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e. Absents letters: k,m,a,n,j,b,h. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: l,o,c. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y. Absents letters: i,r,c,o,s,l,a. ", "response": "deary", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,d. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,o,s,l,a. ", "response": "deity", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,d. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,o,s,t,l,a. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i. Absents letters: l,s,b,t. ", "response": "niger", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n. Absents letters: b,c,h,s,o,g,t,l. ", "response": "bines", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,d,n. Absents letters: r,c,b,h,k,o,s,g,l,t. ", "response": "dj", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,n,d. Absents letters: r,e,b,c,h,k,o,s,g,l,t,u. ", "response": "nid", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a. Absents letters: l,o,e,z. ", "response": "arame", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,h,t. Absents letters: o,e,z,l. ", "response": "shags", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,t,a,h. Absents letters: r,e,z,k,o,l. ", "response": "sitar", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,h,t. Absents letters: r,e,z,b,w,k,o,l. ", "response": "shog", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,t. Absents letters: r,p,y. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,u,t. Absents letters: y,r,n,l,p. ", "response": "tules", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,u,t. Absents letters: r,y,n,e,w,k,l,p,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,m,s,t,u. Absents letters: y,r,e,n,w,k,l,p,a,d. ", "response": "tume", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,u. Absents letters: o,c,s. ", "response": "munge", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a,u. Absents letters: k,o,s,v,c. ", "response": "amuck", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a,u. Absents letters: i,y,c,b,k,o,v,s,t. ", "response": "deism", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,a,u. Absents letters: i,y,e,n,b,c,k,o,v,s,t. ", "response": "maru", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,t. Absents letters: s,c. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,t. Absents letters: i,s,r,n,g,c. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,t. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,m,s,g,u. ", "response": "patte", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e,t. Absents letters: i,r,n,c,k,m,s,g,u,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: p,s,a,r. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,e. Absents letters: s,r,g,p,b,a. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,y,e. Absents letters: r,b,f,s,o,g,p,a. ", "response": "meany", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,y,e. Absents letters: r,n,b,s,o,a,t,g,p,f. ", "response": "mealy", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s. Absents letters: p,g. ", "response": "loids", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,e. Absents letters: r,y,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "bows", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,e. Absents letters: y,r,w,m,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "sices", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,e. Absents letters: r,y,c,w,f,m,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,h. Absents letters: c,e. ", "response": "halos", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,t,l,a,h. Absents letters: c,e. ", "response": "toll", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,t,l,a,h. Absents letters: c,e,n. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,t,l,a,h. Absents letters: m,r,e,n,c,d. ", "response": "loath", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,g,t. Absents letters: e. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,g,t,a. Absents letters: p,r,e. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,g,t,a,h. Absents letters: o,r,e,p,b. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,g,t,a,h. Absents letters: k,o,r,e,p,b. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: m,o,h,e. ", "response": "baw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: f,y. Absents letters: m,o,r,e,t,h. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: f,y. Absents letters: i,r,e,h,m,o,g,t,a. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: f,y. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,h,m,o,s,g,t,a. ", "response": "fy", "reward": -4.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: l,o. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: o,e,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "sats", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: y,e,c,o,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "sats", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,t. Absents letters: y,e,n,c,o,l,f,u,d. ", "response": "thaw", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,p,a. ", "response": "tes", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,r,c,l,p,a. ", "response": "dared", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,d. Absents letters: i,r,c,g,l,p,a. ", "response": "bides", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,e,w,d. Absents letters: i,a,r,g,l,p,c. ", "response": "wked", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,d. Absents letters: b,e. ", "response": "dun", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,d. Absents letters: i,p,e,n,t,b. ", "response": "gourd", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,g,d. Absents letters: i,e,n,b,w,s,t,p,f. ", "response": "boing", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,d,g. Absents letters: i,r,e,n,b,w,s,t,l,p,f. ", "response": "boody", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,e. Absents letters: l,o,w. ", "response": "shags", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,e. Absents letters: m,o,r,l,w. ", "response": "sared", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,a. Absents letters: m,o,r,l,f,w. ", "response": "sis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e,a. Absents letters: r,n,w,m,o,g,l,f. ", "response": "sista", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n. Absents letters: s,a,w. ", "response": "rhy", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n. Absents letters: c,h,w,s,p,a. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n. Absents letters: i,c,h,w,s,o,l,p,a. ", "response": "ennog", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t,e,n. Absents letters: i,r,c,h,w,s,o,l,p,a. ", "response": "enact", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,t. Absents letters: y. ", "response": "siler", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,t. Absents letters: y,r,g,a,d. ", "response": "loast", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,o,s,t. Absents letters: i,r,y,g,a,d. ", "response": "sting", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,s,n,t. Absents letters: i,y,r,e,m,g,a,d. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: m,o,a,t. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,d. Absents letters: m,o,t,c,a. ", "response": "dared", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,d. Absents letters: k,m,o,a,t,c. ", "response": "sared", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,d. Absents letters: k,m,o,a,g,t,c. ", "response": "dared", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: p,o,r. ", "response": "bals", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,t. Absents letters: m,o,s,r,e,p. ", "response": "tah", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,y,t. Absents letters: r,e,k,m,o,s,p,d. ", "response": "tally", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: y,t,l,a. Absents letters: i,r,e,k,m,o,s,g,p,f,d. ", "response": "bant", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e,d. Absents letters: l. ", "response": "dme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e,d. Absents letters: l,a,r,t. ", "response": "dme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e,d. Absents letters: f,r,y,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "sume", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,e,d. Absents letters: y,r,n,a,g,t,l,f,u. ", "response": "dum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r. Absents letters: e,d. ", "response": "gri", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,t. Absents letters: k,e,d. ", "response": "trunk", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a,r,t. Absents letters: k,e,l,f,h,d. ", "response": "tarts", "reward": 10.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,s,r,t,a. Absents letters: k,e,l,f,h,d. ", "response": "tares", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: o,s,t,l,c. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: r. Absents letters: e,c,o,s,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "bry", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,u. Absents letters: e,c,o,s,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "brier", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r,u. Absents letters: e,c,b,o,s,t,l,p,a. ", "response": "shirk", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: p,v,e. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: k,s,v,r,e,n,p. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: r,e,n,k,s,v,p,f. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,o. Absents letters: r,e,n,k,s,v,p,f,d. ", "response": "loipe", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,a. Absents letters: k,h,n. ", "response": "gath", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,a. Absents letters: k,h,n. ", "response": "sma", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,a,p. Absents letters: k,r,e,n,h. ", "response": "pms", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,p,a. Absents letters: k,r,e,n,h. ", "response": "pms", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: s,h,t. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y. Absents letters: s,g,t,a,h,d. ", "response": "boody", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: w,o,y. Absents letters: h,s,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "loony", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,o,y,w. Absents letters: r,e,h,s,g,t,a,d. ", "response": "loony", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: a,r. Absents letters: s,u. ", "response": "gor", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,r. Absents letters: s,f,u. ", "response": "galah", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,r. Absents letters: s,f,u,d. ", "response": "galvo", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,r. Absents letters: i,h,k,s,t,f,u,d. ", "response": "metal", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: p,s,a. ", "response": "rifle", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: s,c,p,a,u. ", "response": "stire", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: c,b,s,t,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "kiers", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: i,r. Absents letters: b,c,w,s,t,l,p,a,u. ", "response": "stire", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: i,m,s,n,p. ", "response": "titch", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o. Absents letters: i,m,s,n,l,p. ", "response": "boo", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: i,e,n,m,s,l,p. ", "response": "rogu", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,r. Absents letters: i,e,n,b,h,m,s,l,p,u,d. ", "response": "tride", "reward": -4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "bub", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: l,a,h,f. ", "response": "fuss", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,e. Absents letters: f,s,v,r,l,a,h. ", "response": "bonie", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,u. Absents letters: r,c,h,s,v,a,l,f. ", "response": "bonie", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: u,e. Absents letters: r,c,h,f,s,v,l,p,a. ", "response": "tau", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gaw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,d,y,t. ", "response": "nis", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: k,y,t,l,j,u,d. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: y,j,k,t,l,u,d. ", "response": "sells", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,r,e,a. Absents letters: k,m,y,t,l,j,u,d. ", "response": "smerk", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,u. Absents letters: g,y,n. ", "response": "taw", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,m,u. Absents letters: g,y,n,p,b,a. ", "response": "kums", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,m,u. Absents letters: y,n,b,c,h,t,g,p,a. ", "response": "kum", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,m,i,u. Absents letters: y,r,n,c,b,h,g,t,p,a,d. ", "response": "kume", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "gyn", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: l,c,y,u. ", "response": "bate", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: t. Absents letters: y,r,c,h,w,o,l,u. ", "response": "gents", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,t. Absents letters: i,r,y,c,h,w,o,l,u. ", "response": "heids", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: n,e,t. Absents letters: i,y,r,c,h,w,o,l,a,u. ", "response": "enate", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: s,e. Absents letters: a,b,d. ", "response": "sme", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: m,s,e. Absents letters: a,y,t,b,d. ", "response": "mesal", "reward": 4.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,m,s,e. Absents letters: i,a,y,r,t,b,d. ", "response": "kms", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: k,m,s,e. Absents letters: i,y,r,b,o,t,p,a,d. ", "response": "mecks", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Absents letters: t,s,u,g. ", "response": "niger", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: n,s,v,g,t,a,u. ", "response": "bonie", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y,e. Absents letters: n,k,s,v,g,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,c,y,e. Absents letters: i,r,n,k,s,v,g,t,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a. Absents letters: x,g. ", "response": "alary", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,c,a. Absents letters: b,x,e,g. ", "response": "cask", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,a,c. Absents letters: x,e,r,b,v,g,u. ", "response": "alic", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: l,c,a. Absents letters: r,x,e,n,b,s,v,g,f,u. ", "response": "cag", "reward": -3.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "brug", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: l,s,b,a. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: q,r,y,b,s,l,a,u. ", "response": "tiler", "reward": -2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e. Absents letters: q,y,r,j,b,s,o,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "niger", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: h,e. Absents letters: q,r,y,j,b,s,o,t,l,a,u. ", "response": "heath", "reward": 2.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters. ", "response": "tungs", "reward": 0.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: e,n. Absents letters: c,u,d. ", "response": "enew", "reward": -1.5, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y,e,n. Absents letters: t,p,c,u,d. ", "response": "enzym", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y,e,n. Absents letters: c,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "ennog", "reward": 8.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
{"prompt": "Please guess a word with five letters.Exists letters: o,y,e,n. Absents letters: r,c,s,t,p,a,u,d. ", "response": "lozen", "reward": 6.0, "step": 0, "ref_response": "", "ref_reward": 0}
